Thank you so much.
Thank you very much, New York.
Holy shit.
This is Madison Square Garden.
Oh, my God.
Bring the house lights up for a second.
Let's just see everybody here a second.
Bring the house lights up.
Thank you. Thank you so much
to all 12,000 of you
predominantly white people
that showed up tonight. I really--
No, there's minorities in the mix.
I'm just kidding. Yeah.
Uh, I'm a...
I'm a minority, and I am...
Yeah, I am the first generation
in my family that was born in America.
Anybody else first-generation people?
Yeah? Clap, yeah?
Yeah!
Pretty amazing thing
our parents did, right?
They came to this country.
They maybe didn't know anyone,
maybe didn't even speak the language,
and they figured it out.
Very brave, courageous thing.
And I feel like we never sit down
and thank them for it.
And we should, 'cause that's
such an amazing thing, you know,
for someone in your family
to at some point,
to just be like,
"You know what? Fuck China!
Let's get out of here. Let's go.
Let's get out of here. I'm tired of living
in this village. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's move to America.
I've seen photos online, it looks dope.
Let's go. Let's go."
'Cause you know they had
friends that were dicks
that were like, "What?
You can't move to America.
You don't know anyone there.
You don't speak the language.
What are you gonna do for work?"
"I don't know, man.
We'll figure it out.
Worst-case scenario, we'll cook food
and we'll sell it to white people, okay?"
"You got a Master's degree in Chemistry.
You don't know how to cook."
"They don't know
what Chinese food tastes like!
I'll just put some chicken in a box
with some orange sauce
and I'll serve it to 'em."
"Ooh! What are you gonna call that dish?
Orange chicken?"
"Yeah! Maybe I will
call it orange chicken!
Maybe I'll call it Number 36.
We'll see!"
Pretty amazing, though, right?
Like, all those stories,
they're amazing to me.
Amazing stories.
I hear immigrants say stories like,
"Oh, I came to Brooklyn
with $20 in my pocket."
That's incredible.
Is our generation that amazing?
I don't think we are.
I don't think we're as amazing
as our parents are.
I don't think we can
pull that kind of shit off.
Like, could you imagine if you sent me
to Brooklyn with $20 in my pocket?
I'd get there the first day and be like,
"Oh, man, I'm out of money!
I just bought too much
fresh pressed juice!
Guess I gotta move back."
"Hey, Dad.
Yeah, I'm coming back to India, huh.
Things didn't work out here.
Uh, I made a bad investment in juice."
My parents told me
a little bit about their struggles.
They moved to South Carolina.
That's where they chose-- Yeah!
'Cause they were trying to find a place
that combined racism...
and horrible public schools...
and they're like, "Ooh, South Carolina!
You're right in the middle of this
very unnecessary Venn diagram.
Let's do this!"
And, you know,
they told me a little bit about it.
And, you know, my mom told me
her first day in America
was the scariest day of her life.
And I was like,
"Wow, why do you say that?"
She's like, "Well, I got here.
I didn't know anyone.
I was so far away from
my friends and family.
Uh, I barely even knew your father."
They had an arranged marriage
and she'd known him for, like,
a week at that point.
This is serious.
And she said she got here
and she's in this small apartment,
it's empty and
she didn't know what to do,
and she felt so scared.
I was like,
"What did you do that first day?"
She's like,
"I didn't know what to do.
I was all alone.
Your dad was at work the whole day.
And I just sat on the couch
and I cried."
I was like, "Oh, that's so sad.
How did you get through that?"
And she's like,
"It was just one of those moments
where I just knew
I had to be brave and figure it out.
You ever had moments like that,
Aziz, where you were so scared,
but you knew you had to be brave
and figure it out?"
And I was like...
"No!
My life is super easy
'cause you did all the struggling.
So, my shit's really easy."
I'm not gonna have any struggles
to tell my kids about.
What's my story gonna be like?
"Oh, son, once, when I was flying
from New York to LA...
my iPad died."
My kid will be like, "Fuck you, Dad.
We're teleporting to Mars!"
My dad told me
a little bit about his struggles.
My dad's a doctor.
And he said when he first got here,
it was very hard
'cause the head of the hospital
was very racist
and would never send him patients.
He'd always send patients
to another doctor
that lived three hours away.
And I was like, "Oh, that stinks.
How did you figure that out?"
And he said,
"Well, what eventually happened was
the head of the hospital got very sick
and he had a stomach problem."
My dad is a stomach doctor.
And so he called for my dad.
He's like, "Oh, send that Indian guy in.
I don't want to go to the guy
three hours away."
And my mom was like,
"You shouldn't go.
That guy's racist,
he never sends you patients.
Why should you go?"
My dad was like,
"No, I'm gonna go,
'cause I think we need to be
the bigger people here."
So my dad goes
and he starts treating the guy.
And then my dad
poisons him and kills him.
And then my dad became
the head of the hospital.
And that's what you gotta do
when you're an immigrant!
Handle your shit!
Kill some racist motherfuckers
if you need to!
How many of you guys--
Clap if you don't eat meat.
Anyone here not eat meat?
Okay.
Now, clap if you don't eat meat
'cause, um, you saw a documentary
or you read a book that freaked you out
about the meat industry.
Clap if that's the situation.
A few people.
Now, clap if you've just
seen that stuff in general.
Like, video of a factory farm
or read something that, like,
freaked you out
about the food industry.
Clap if you've seen that stuff, yeah?
That's a lot of people.
Now, clap if you saw that stuff
and you're like,
"Oh, my God, that's disgusting.
It's cruel, it's inhumane.
The government definitely needs to
properly regulate the meat industry.
There's no excuse for this.
The government definitely needs to
properly regulate the meat industry.
But, in the meantime...
I kinda still gotta eat meat
'cause I don't want to feel
weird and hungry all the time."
Isn't that so frustrating?
'Cause no one wants to support that stuff.
But you know what the problem is?
Salads need to
step their game up, okay?
Like, salads aren't
bringing it hard enough.
Vegetables aren't
If food is a basketball game,
meat is killing it.
Meat is just like, "Ribs!
Fried chicken!
Steak!"
Meanwhile, vegetables are like,
"Uh, does anyone want any cauliflower?
What about some snow peas?
Does anyone like Brussels sprouts?"
"Yeah, I'll take those Brussels sprouts
and I'll wrap 'em in some bacon!"
That's how powerful meat is, right?
You go into a kitchen,
you smell bacon and go,
"Are you cooking bacon right now?
Is that bacon you're making right--
Is there any way you have
a second piece of bacon
that I could eat as well?
Is there any..."
No one's ever walked
into a kitchen like,
"Are you steaming carrots right now?
Are you steaming carrots?
I can smell the steam
from the other room.
Is that some broccoli and cauliflower?
Are you making a medley right now?
Are you making a motherfucking
steamed vegetable medley right now?
Oh, don't tell me that's
brown rice in that bowl!
Don't tell me that's brown rice!
You better fix me a plate now!"
Even if you don't eat meat,
even if you're just eating vegetables,
do you know everything
that goes into the vegetables?
There's all this messed-up stuff
with vegetables, too,
like child labor
and all these issues.
Like, how come every vegetable's
always in season, right?
Every vegetable's
You never go to the grocery store
and they're like,
"We don't have asparagus at the moment.
They're just not growing."
No, no, no.
They have everything all the time.
'Cause if it's not growing here,
they just go to South America,
and there's some guy with a sword
going up to little kids like,
"Dígame, dígame! Pick the asparagus!
Pick it! Pick it! Pick it!
People in America need to eat it
and see if it really
makes their pee smell weird!"
Just never google how anything
you consume is created.
Just never google it,
'cause it's always gonna bum you out.
I used to buy this orange juice
called Simply OJ,
'cause I'm dumb and I see
words like "simple" and "natural,"
and I'm like,
"Mmm, okay, well, clearly,
there must be a grandma
squeezing oranges into a bucket,
and, you know,
then she pours that in a little bottle."
No, no, no, no, no.
That's what was happening
for, like, three months,
and then Coca-Cola
bought the company.
They slit the grandma's throat...
and now a bunch of little Asian kids
just jizz into a banana peel,
and that's Simply OJ.
Something like that.
I can't...
quite remember the specifics, but...
something like that.
Everything, man! Eggs!
You know how they make eggs?
This is how they make eggs, okay?
They genetically engineer
two different types of chicken.
One type of chicken
is called the layer chick.
Just lays eggs, right?
And they have another type of chick
called a broiler chick.
This is the chicken they, like,
pump up with a bunch of hormones
so it has, like, huge breasts and legs,
and that's the one they use for the meat.
And I'm reading this, I'm like, "Well,
what happens to the male layer chicks?"
They serve no purpose, right?
They can't lay eggs.
They can't be used for meat.
What happens?
They just get murdered!
In insane ways.
Like, they'll take
all the male layer chicks
and they'll throw 'em
into a big chicken woodchipper.
Um, another thing they'll do
is they'll put 'em in a big plastic vat
and just put a lid on it
and suffocate 'em to death.
And, yeah, it's a bummer.
Like, none of us is into that.
Like, we'd all check "No" on that box.
But the problem is,
this kind of information,
this kind of footage,
it just hasn't been seen
in the right context
to elicit the kind of mass outrage
that would actually result
in some changes, you know.
Right now, it's in these obscure
documentaries or books or whatever.
But what if it was
in a different context?
Like, what if there was a CNN camera crew
that did a raid at rapper Ja Rule's house?
And they saw
he had a big plastic vat
where he was just suffocating
chickens to death.
We'd all be like, "Ja, you monster!
What are you doing?"
And he'd be like, "I'm sorry,
I just wanted some eggs!
I had to make ethical compromises
in order to achieve economies of scale!
♪ It's murda!" ♪
I'll admit,
when I first wrote that joke,
I was like,
"But will people remember Ja Rule?"
Oh, how foolish I was!
If you're not familiar with Ja, um...
he had a strange string of hits
a few years ago, where...
every song followed
this very strange formula
where they'd have a woman
with a very beautiful voice,
like Jennifer Lopez or Ashanti,
and they would sing the hook.
And then Ja would come in
and sound like
someone that was getting stabbed
in the stomach through their ulcer.
Like, every single song
was just like,
♪ R-U-L-E ♪
♪ What's my motherfucking name? ♪
♪ And what am I doing here? ♪
I feel like I gotta do that whole bit
on a talk show or something.
'Cause whenever you do
a bit like that on a talk show,
the person always
gets in touch with you.
So I feel like I have to do it,
just so I can get that amazing phone call
one day, where it's just like, "Aziz?"
- "Yeah. Who is this?"
- "Ja Rule, baby!
Saw the way you integrated me
into that bit about factory farming
in the egg industry!
I never knew that shit!
I'm never eatin' meat again!
You know where I can get
some more literature on this subject?
Maybe a pamphlet on how to adjust
to a vegan or vegetarian lifestyle?
♪ Put it on me!" ♪
Soon, Ja starts getting
really passionate about the cause.
He starts filming his own PSAs.
"Every day,
millions of chickens
are living in tiny cages
the size of a piece of paper.
They're shittin' all over each other
in these disease-ridden factory farms.
This is the meat
we're puttin' in our mouths!
This is the meat we're puttin'
in our children's mouths!
If you think the government should
probably regulate the meat industry,
♪ Holla, holla!" ♪
Guys, if only you knew
how long it's taken me
to find the perfect
stand-up bit to showcase
my frustrations
with the meat industry...
and my flawless
Ja Rule impersonation...
then you'd know my struggle.
You know what
I've realized recently?
Creepy dudes are everywhere...
and they're so much more prevalent
than I ever realized.
And it really sucks, 'cause women have
to worry about creepy dudes all the time.
And it's very unfair because
men never worry about creepy women.
Like, men never are concerned
about creepy women.
That's not a thing.
There's never been two dudes,
walking alone,
late night in a park, like...
- "Hey, man, I think we should speed up."
- "Why, what's going on?"
"I'm pretty sure that woman
behind the tree is masturbating to us!"
"Oh, God! Oh, God! Should we get a cab?
Should we just keep running? Ahh!"
No two dudes have
ever faced that dilemma.
There's never been a dude
who's told a story like this,
"Yeah, so I'm at the club, like,
minding my own business, right?
And then this creepy woman
comes up to me. She's like,
'Hey, can I buy you a drink?'
I'm like, 'No, I'm fine.'
'Let me buy you a drink.'
'No, I'm fine.'
She's like,
'Let me buy you a drink!'
I'm like, 'Okay, okay, okay.'
And so, you know,
she buys me a drink
and I take a sip to be polite,
and then she's just like...
that's a nice set of balls
you got down there.
What do you think about me
sucking on one of those bad boys later?'
And I was like,
'Uh, that's quite all right.'
And she's like,
'Oh, but you'll drink the drink, though!
You'll drink the drink, though!
To be clear, I can't suck the balls,
but you'll drink the drink, though!
You'll drink the drink, though!
You're twisted!
Ladies, let's get out of this club!
Dudes here are busted!'"
No dude has that story.
No dude's ever barged up into
his friend's apartment in a panic, like,
"Oh, my God! Dude, I'm so sorry!
I didn't know where else to go!
This is so crazy!
Oh, my God!
I'm so freaked out right now!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
I was walking down Third Avenue,
and this woman just
whipped her pussy out at me.
And she just started chasing me like,
'Ahh! Do you wanna touch it?'"
No guy here has any story like that.
Every woman in here has
at least three stories like that.
I promise you, they do.
Creepy dudes are everywhere, man.
They're on the Internet.
Oh, they love the Internet so much!
Such a great showcase for them.
It's really startling
if you look at the difference
between the way
men are treated on the Internet
and women are treated on the Internet.
You know, me as a guy,
let's say I tweet something like,
"Hey, guys, I'm doing a show in Phoenix.
Get tickets!"
I might get a mean tweet,
where some guy's like,
"Oh, yeah? I'm never coming to Phoenix,
'cause you suck!
Yeah, I got him.
I did it, yeah!"
If a woman tweets that, though,
her mean tweet will be different.
Like, if a woman tweets,
"Hey, I'm doing a show in Phoenix.
Get tickets!"
Her mean tweet will be like,
"Oh, yeah? Instead of going to Phoenix,
why don't you come to Buffalo
and suck my dick?
Yeah! I got her!
I did it, yeah!
Let's go watch Transformers again! Pshh!"
No women are harassing me like that.
Women just don't harass dudes in that way.
I never get tweets like that.
No women are ever writing me stuff like,
"Oh, hey, Aziz,
I bet you give good head!
Yeah! Suck my pussy, Aziz!
Suck my pussy, Aziz!"
No women are out there
writing me like,
"Oh, hey, Aziz,
I wanna take your head
and squeeze it in between my titties
till your beard pops off. Yeah!"
No women are saying that.
No women are out there like, "Oh, Aziz,
you're putting out a new stand-up special?
Why don't you put your fingers
in my pussy instead?
Finger me, Aziz!
Let's go watch
Dirty Dancing on Blu-ray!"
Pshh!
No women are saying that 'cause,
in general, women don't
do dumb shit like that.
That's not a thing they do, really.
Men do this shit all the time,
and it's so dumb.
I did a show with
a female comedian once.
She got on stage
and the first thing that happened
is some idiot in the front just yells,
"Take it off!"
If you're a dude, never yell,
"Take it off."
Unless a woman has placed a tarantula
or a scorpion on one of your shoulders,
there's no reason for you to yell,
"Take it off!"
I've seen dudes yell
"Take it off" in a strip club!
She has a routine planned.
She's trying to tease you,
you dumb motherfucker!
What would you rather her do?
Just, like, walk out there
completely naked?
Another thing...
Another thing creepy dudes do...
they'll just follow women.
You know what I'm talking about?
Like, they'll just see a woman
and be like, "Okay!"
And just follow 'em around
for, like, a really long time.
Terrifying.
Raise your hand if you're a woman
and you've ever been
followed around by a creepy dude.
Raise your hand high!
Raise it really fucking high!
Everyone just look around and see
how many hands are raised right now.
Yeah, that's way too many people.
That should not be happening.
One woman told me
she eventually got rid of the guy
by walking into a pet store
where you needed to get buzzed in.
I'm not sure why this pet store
had such intense security...
but, um...
she said, she went in there and said,
"Hey, there's a creepy guy following me.
Don't buzz him in."
They're like, "Okay."
And she said she just
waited there until he left.
And I was like,
"Wow, how long did you have to wait?"
And she was like, "Mmm, 45 minutes."
Forty-five minutes of her day gone
'cause this creep decided to follow her.
God! But I get it, man,
you gotta be safe.
These guys are crazy.
You never know,
they may follow you to your home
or your apartment where you live.
And if you're a creepy dude doing that,
what's your dream scenario at that point?
Like, what's your best-case situation?
Like, what do you think's
really gonna happen?
Like, the woman's
just gonna get to her door
and just turn around,
just like, "So...
are you just gonna stand there...
or are you gonna come up
and fuck me?"
That's never happening.
That's never happening!
There's a greater chance of a tornado
grabbing a woman
and blowing her into your penis
than there is of you somehow seducing
a woman that way, you fucking creeps.
What can you do for real, though, man?
One woman told me a story
that was kind of cool.
She said, one time, she had
a creepy guy following her
and, uh, she saw another dude
that she thought was like a good dude,
and said, "Hey, can you
pretend to be my boyfriend?
I think there's, like,
a creepy guy following me.
Can you pretend to be my boyfriend?"
And the guy did it.
And it helped her out
and the creepy guy went away.
I was like,
"Oh, man, that's really cool," right?
She had faith that this other guy
would be a decent human being.
And he was, and he rose to the challenge
and it helped her out, you know?
I would do that.
If any woman in here was like,
"Hey, Aziz, could you pretend
to be my boyfriend?"
I would do that shit,
I would get into it.
I'd be like, "I got this!
What's the situation?"
"There's a creepy guy following me."
- "Where is he?"
- "He's right behind us."
"Oh, fuck! He's really creepy.
He's rather large as well.
Are you sure we shouldn't be
seeing other people?
Just kidding, I got this."
"What are you gonna do, Aziz?"
"Oh, I'm gonna beat the shit
out of this guy!"
- "Really?"
- "Yeah.
But first, I need to run a quick errand."
- "What is it?"
- "I gotta buy a dog.
Let's go in this pet store
and wait about 45 minutes."
Clap if you're in a relationship
right now. Relationship folks.
You know what I love
about relationship people?
I love how they tell the story
of how they met their person.
You know what I'm talking about?
It's a very specific type of
storytelling where it's like, "Oh...
...and we've been together ever since."
That's like a fun way
to tell a story, right?
But I don't think it's fair
that frustrated single people can't share
their stories in the same manner, right?
Like, those are more relatable stories.
Like, I would love to hear
a woman tell a story like this,
"So, Rachel's like, 'Come get a drink.
Come get a drink. Come get a drink.'
I'm like,
'No, I'm not coming out tonight.'
She's like, 'You never come out.
How are you gonna meet someone
if you never come out?'
So, I'm like, 'Fine!'
So, we go to the bar
and there's this really cute guy.
He's sitting by himself
and he's drinking a whiskey.
And Rachel's like,
'Go talk to him. Go talk to him.'
I'm like,
'No, I'm not saying anything.'
And she's like, 'You go talk to him
or I'm gonna talk to him for you.'
So, I'm like, 'Fine.'
So, I walk over...
and I go,
'Hey, are you waiting on someone?'
And he goes,
'Yeah, I'm waiting on my girlfriend.'
So, I sat back down...
and I haven't seen him ever since!"
That's a story
we can all relate to, right?
Or what about a story like this,
"So Bryan's like, 'Come on, man.
Let's go to one more bar.
Let's go to one more spot.'
I'm like,
'I'm pretty beat.
I think I'm just gonna call it.
It's like 3:45 in the morning.
I'm gonna go home.'
He's like, 'No, no, no, no.
This is a late night spot.
There's always girls there.
You never know, you never know,
you never know.'
So, I'm like, 'Fuck it.'
So, we head to the bar and,
uh, it was closed.
Guess it was a slow night,
so, uh, that was that."
Or what about a story like this?
"So, me and her,
we've always been really close,
but, you know,
nothing's ever happened,
never hooked up or anything,
just been friends.
And we're out this one night,
she's just broken up with her boyfriend
and we're having a couple of drinks,
and it starts getting a little flirty.
Then it starts getting
a little touchy-feely.
Next thing you know, we're back
at my place and we're having sex.
And this is, like, amazing sex.
It's been, like, pent-up for years.
And it's one of those things
that just felt right, you know?
And at one point, she just looks me
right in the eyes and she just says,
'I don't think we should do this!'
So...
I pulled my penis out...
we went to sleep,
and it's been
an awkward situation for...
it'll be a year in August."
Those are the stories we can relate to.
Being in a relationship, it's tough.
It's a lot of work.
But I think being single is even harder,
especially right now.
Very odd, frustrating time
to be a single person.
And I like the idea
of being single in theory.
But what does that mean?
You meet a bunch of different people,
you get to know 'em,
you find someone you really connect with,
hmm, maybe pursue
something more serious.
That sounds good,
I would sign up for that.
But that's not what
being single is anymore, right?
This is what being single is now,
"Hey, it was great meeting you.
We should get together sometime."
"Yeah, that'd be great.
Be in touch."
- "All right. Bye."
- "Cool."
"Hey, what's up?
You wanna grab some drinks tonight?"
"Yeah, yeah, I'm with some friends
in this neighborhood."
"Oh, cool.
We'll be down there soon."
- "Can't wait to see you. Cool."
- "All right. Bye."
"Hey, what's up?
We're almost there."
"Shit, we just left."
Why? Why'd you just leave?
Isn't that a rude,
shitty thing to do?
You invited me somewhere
and then you left before I got there.
"Maybe we'll meet up tomorrow."
"Tomorrow is perfect.
Text you later and make a plan."
- "All right. Bye."
- "Cool."
"Hey, what's up?
Should we grab those drinks tonight?"
"Oh, drank way too much last night.
Gonna stay in today."
That's not what was
discussed yesterday!
Would you like a transcript
of our conversation?
You may scroll up on your phone.
"Maybe we can meet up on Thursday."
"Thursday's perfect.
Text you later and make a plan."
- "All right. Bye."
- "Cool."
"Hey, what's up? It's Thursday.
Should we get together tonight?"
And that's what being single is now.
All that garbage.
That's what it is a lot of times.
It's pretty much like you're a secretary
for this really shoddy organization...
trying to schedule the dumbest shit
with the flakiest people.
And I've realized this flakiness,
it doesn't even have to do
with dating or anything.
It's actually a symptom
of a bigger problem we all have.
You know, we're all part of the rudest,
flakiest group of people ever.
Like, if you're alive right now
and you have a phone,
you're a rude, shitty person.
You just are.
Like, has anyone here tried to make plans
with anyone in the past couple of years?
Has anyone tried
to make plans with anyone?
It's the most frustrating experience.
'Cause what happens anytime you ask
someone to do something nowadays?
It's like,
"Hey, you wanna do this fun thing?"
"Maybe. Maybe, I could try.
We could see about...
maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe."
No one wants to commit to shit.
'Cause they're terrified that
something better is gonna come along.
It is so rude.
Why do we do this?
I think it's 'cause we're also part
of the least lonely generation,
the least isolated generation, you know?
It used to be a big deal when you finally
got to see your friends in person, right?
Nowadays, it's not as much,
'cause you're always connected
with your friends, you're always--
Wherever you are, work,
school, whatever,
you're always texting,
e-mailing, joking around.
So, when you see them in person,
it's not as big a deal as it used to be.
You know, now it's like,
"Oh, man, it's so good to see you.
I just went on this crazy vacation!"
"I know, I saw all the pictures.
Leave me alone."
It used to not be like that.
It used to be a big deal
when you saw your friends, right?
Think about what you'd be doing,
like, 40 years ago, you know.
Think about what that would be like.
What you'd be doing, like,
on a Thursday night.
You know, you're just sitting
in your house, by yourself...
you're in a wooden chair...
eating a can of beans.
You have nothing.
You're not connected to anyone.
No entertainment.
"Oh, uh, maybe I'll listen to some music."
All right, just the music you own,
or you can sit around and hope
a song you like comes on the radio,
and then grab a cassette
and run over like a little bitch.
"Oh, I missed the beginning!"
Maybe you'll stay in
and watch a movie.
All right, what's it gonna be?
Home Alone, Jurassic Park
or Mrs. Doubtfire?
That's all you have.
You have nothing!
And then,
in the corner of the room,
you have your one outlet
to the outside world, right?
Your landline.
And if you were lucky, at some point
it would ring and you'd be like,
"Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hello!
Who is this?
Phil, thank you
so much for calling.
What would you like to do?
That sounds great!
I'll see you there at 8:00."
And you would be there at 8:00.
And Phil would be there at 8:00.
And if Phil wasn't there by 8:15,
you'd be like,
"Oh, my God! Phil is dead.
Phil has died!
We were supposed to see
Police Academy and now he's dead!"
'Cause that was the only polite way
to cancel on people back in the day.
You had to die.
Now what do your shitty friends do?
They'll call you like an hour before.
"Hey, you know,
I'm feeling kind of tired.
So, I think I'm just
gonna stay in tonight."
"Oh, you're tired?
What, were you doing
a bunch of manual labor?
Were you, uh, building a habitat
for humanity? Or..."
"No, I just did
one of those online surveys
that tells you what character you are
from a particular TV show.
And I've done, like, seven of them,
so I'm feeling kind of tired.
And, you know, I'm just so tired,
I don't feel like driving and everything."
Hold up!
You're too tired to drive?
The car moves.
You don't do shit, you just sit there.
How is this a valid excuse?
Did you recently purchase
a Flintstones -type vehicle
where you need to run along?
I don't believe you did.
So now, when you make plans,
you got to remember
how flaky everyone is, right?
You got to factor that in.
You got to change your approach.
You know, you look
at my phone on a Sunday,
when I'm trying to find
someone to get brunch with,
I look like a psychopath.
It's just like,
"Hey, you wanna get brunch?
Hey, you wanna get--
Hey, you wanna-- Hey, you wanna--
Hey, you wanna-- Hey, you wanna--"
And it's this weird list
of my best friend
to the shittiest person
I'd eat pancakes with.
But I get it.
I get it, man.
I understand why we're like this.
We all have the same nightmare.
You know the nightmare.
The nightmare is you do commit
to doing the thing with Phil, right?
And you get there, like,
"This is fun, Phil. I'm glad I came.
We're getting to catch up and stuff.
It's good."
Then you get that phone call.
"Dude, where are you?
Biggie and Tupac faked their deaths.
They're doing a show right now.
I have an extra ticket. Where are you?"
"I'm upstate picking apples with Phil!"
We all have that nightmare,
and I do think there's a new thing,
where we always want the best, you know?
Whatever we're doing,
we wanna do the best, funnest thing.
Whatever we're buying,
we want the best.
We have all these options,
and we have all this information
at our fingertips to research it.
And we always want the best.
Why not have the best?
And a lot of times
it's very useful, right?
I made some more
educated decisions in my life.
But, at a certain point,
doesn't that stuff become debilitating?
Like, now it's gotten to the point
where before I make
any choice or decision in my life,
I have to google something
to make sure I'm not fucking it up.
You know what I mean?
Like, the other day,
I had to get a toothbrush.
Before I left my house,
without even thinking about it, I googled,
"Best toothbrush."
That's right, I'm about to get
the best toothbrush.
Why? Why do I need
the best toothbrush?
Every other toothbrush
I bought on a hunch has been fine.
Like, what is the big fear now?
Have you ever run
into someone with no teeth,
and be like,
"What happened?"
"Bought the wrong toothbrush.
Should've done more research!"
And when you take
these kind of mentalities
and you throw 'em in the dating world,
things get crazy, man.
Things get really weird, you know.
You people that are married,
been in long relationships,
you have no idea
what it's like out there right now.
Everything has changed.
Take your most basic problem
as a single person.
What is it? You like someone,
they don't like you back.
Or the reverse, someone likes you,
you don't like them back.
Okay, at one point in time,
that used to be kind of a weird thing.
It was awkward,
it was a conversation,
it was something
you had to deal with, right?
Now, what do people do?
Someone likes you,
you don't like 'em back?
Just pretend to be busy forever.
That's what people do now.
They pretend to be busy forever,
and then they conduct this
strange psychological experiment,
where it's like, "Mmm, how much
hope does this person have?
How many times do I need to pretend
to be busy before they realize
this many scheduling conflicts
is statistically impossible...
and something else is going on?"
Now, look, I don't think
it's coming from a bad place.
I think you're trying not to hurt
someone's feelings, right?
What are your other options?
Um, you could say nothing
and give people silence.
Or you could just be honest with them.
Those are your big three options, right?
Clap if what you do is pretend to be busy.
Clap if that's your move.
Okay.
I'd say that's my move as well, okay.
Clap if what you do is, you say nothing.
You give people silence.
Okay, and finally,
clap if you're just honest with people.
Okay, now let's say
the situation is reversed
and someone else is dealing with you.
How do you prefer
they handle the situation?
Clap if you prefer
that they pretend to be busy.
All right.
Clap if you prefer that they say nothing,
that they give you silence.
Why the fuck would you prefer that?
This is a hypothetical thing.
That's your preference?
You're into confusion?
Sorry, this isn't
a good way to do polls.
I shouldn't shit on people
after certain responses.
I apologize.
And finally, clap if you prefer
that they're just honest with you.
I'd say I'm in that camp as well.
Well, well, well, I think
our findings are pretty clear, right?
We're all really shitty people.
Whenever we're dealing with others,
we're like, "I'm gonna pretend to be busy.
I don't wanna say anything."
When other people are dealing
with us, we're like,
"Why must we all play these games?
Can't we all just be
honest with one another?"
And the other thing is, we all say
we prefer honesty, myself included,
but can we really handle honesty,
you know?
I talked to a woman once, she's like,
"Oh, I'm just honest with people.
I don't mess around.
I'm just honest with people."
I was like, "Really? All right.
I'm a guy, I ask you out for dinner,
you don't wanna go,
what would you say?"
She said, "I would say, 'I'm not
interested in getting dinner with you.'"
And on one hand,
that's really nice, right?
There's no games there,
you know exactly where you stand,
you're not wasting your time.
On the other hand, though,
could you imagine
actually receiving a text like that?
"Hey, you wanna get dinner sometime?"
"I'm not interested in getting
dinner with you."
God damn!
What are you, a demon?
That's the meanest, coldest shit
anyone's ever said to me, okay?
I'm a person.
I have feelings, okay?
I'm just a fellow human being
that wanted to break bread with you
and get to know you a little better.
Is that such a horrifying situation?
I was basically like,
"Hey, you want some free food?"
You're like,
"Not if your presence is involved.
You got a gift certificate?
I'll go with my friend."
I don't know what the best way
to deal with it is, man.
I do think it's tough.
I do think silence
might be the worst, though.
Silence to me seems like the rudest,
most cowardly way to handle a situation.
And it's also the one that hurts
the other person the most, right?
We've all been on the other end of that.
That's the worst, man.
The worst is when you meet
someone you're really into
and you feel that connection.
You know what I'm talking about?
When you meet that person...
"Oh, my God. We both felt that.
No games this time, deep connection.
No games, deep connection.
No games...
deep connection."
You send the first text,
you're all confidence.
"Forget about it, it's done.
Wrap it up, put it in a bag,
write my name on it...
'cause it's done."
Twenty minutes later,
no response.
"Okay, well, I'm sure she's just
busy with a couple of things,
and any minute now..."
Three hours later, "Fuck!
I put too many
exclamation points in my text!
What was I thinking?
I should have said 'Hey'
with two 'Y's, ' not three 'Y's.'
I'm so stupid!"
Three hours earlier.
You're looking up
vacation packages on Orbitz,
you're planning birthdays,
holidays, a whole life together.
And now it's all gone away,
and you have no idea why.
And this is when people
start going crazy.
'Cause in the past,
let's say you're in a situation like this,
someone doesn't call or write you back,
you get over it with time, right?
Out of sight, out of mind.
The problem now is,
we don't give ourselves the luxury
of out of sight, out of mind.
'Cause what happens now when
you get into one of these situations?
We all become detectives.
We start opening up tabs:
Facebook, Twitter, Instagram.
"All right, let's see every single thing
this motherfucker's doing
instead of texting me back.
GPS on screen two!
Instagram on screen three!
Let's see what
they're looking at right now!"
And it's a brutal thing
to do to yourself.
You should not do it
because, ah, you're in the most
vulnerable position, right?
You put yourself out there.
You're like...
♪ I like you, baby
You like me ♪
Any guy or girl in that situation,
that's what they're feeling.
And you're just waiting
for something to put your heart at ease,
but instead,
you're getting nothing.
Then you go on the Internet,
you're reading stuff like,
"Mmm, eating ice cream
and watching Dexter.
Hash mark, I really need a man."
"What? I just asked you out!
You know I follow you!
You know I'm reading this.
What kind of evil is inside of you?"
And it seems like an area
where we could all be
a little bit more thoughtful, right?
Uh, 'cause, look,
anytime someone asks you out,
whether it's a guy asking a girl or girl
asking a guy, whatever the scenario,
that person is paying you
a huge compliment, right?
They're basically saying,
"Hey, out of the infinite number of things
I could do with my time,
what I'd like to do is spend
some time with you,
'cause I think there's
something special about you,
and I'd like to get to know you better
and see if there's a connection there."
That's a very nice thing
for someone to say,
I feel like you should
respect that a little bit.
So, maybe don't post your
dumb photos and stuff up.
Like, you wouldn't treat people
that way 20, 30 years ago.
Twenty, 30 years ago,
if someone asked you out
and you weren't interested,
you wouldn't send
a package to their house,
"Here's some photos of me
and my friends at the beach.
Here's a photo of a puppy
I saw on the street.
Here's a bunch of photos
of me and some other guy.
Am I fucking him?
Maybe. Why don't you think
about that for a few hours?"
So, that's it, man.
Anyone here that's single,
they have some version of that
nonsense in their phone, right?
Clap if you're single and you met
someone in the past few days,
past week or so,
and you've been texting back and forth.
Clap if that's your situation.
Clap right now.
Okay...
If you're in that situation,
do me a favor right now.
Pull out your phone
and scroll to the very, very first message
that you have with this person.
And when you get to
the very, very, very first message,
come on to the front stage over here
through this aisle here.
So, go ahead,
pull out your phone,
scroll to the very first message,
when you get to the first message,
come to the front, right here,
in front of this gentleman here.
Miss, you at the top message?
Yeah?
All right, so how long ago
did you meet this person?
Uh, September 2nd.
September 2nd.
Okay, so let's see what happened, okay?
So... he sends the first message.
He sends it Tuesday,
September 2nd at 11:26 p.m.
Odd time to send a first message.
He says,
"Hey, Ashley, dot-dot-dot, it's Chris."
He said his last name,
but I don't wanna repeat it
in case he gets murdered.
"Hey, Ashley, dot-dot-dot."
I like that, "dot-dot-dot."
"Hey, Ashley..."
"It's Chris.
It was nice to hang-- It was--"
It started so smooth.
"Hey, Ashley,
dot-dot-dot, it's Chris."
And then he goes,
"It was nice to hanging with you..."
Chris, no! Proofread!
"It was nice to--" His voice changes
for the rest of the bit now, after that.
Earlier, it was,
"Hey, Ashley, it's Chris."
Now it's,
"Hey, Ashley, it's Chris.
It was nice to hanging with you at BM.
Hope you're recovering well.
Let's grab a coffee sometime."
And then, you send
a text back the next day
at 1:05 p.m.
You say,
"Hey, exclamation.
Glad you made it out alive.
Headed to Soho House with Erica now.
I'm also around after 6:00 tomorrow
or in the afternoon Friday."
Whoa! You must really like this guy!
Who the fuck...
Who the fuck opens up
their schedule that much?
If the Dalai Lama was like, "I really
wanna get tea with you sometime, Aziz,"
I'd be like, "Uh, let's just check in
next week, Dalai Lama."
And so, then he sends a message
Thursday at 11:55 a.m.
and he goes,
"I thought I'd see you
at Marquee last night."
And then, he tries to send...
Sorry, all these places
sound kind of douche-y.
I'm really sorry.
No judgments here, but...
It's not like, "I thought I'd see you
at that MoMA exhibit."
It's like, "Why weren't you at the club?
There was a foam party!"
And then... you guys text
back and forth, you get the coffee.
Did you guys get the coffee?
- Uh, yeah.
- And how was the coffee?
- Did you have fun?
- It was okay.
Yeah? It was okay?
All right, so let's see where
things are right now, okay?
Yesterday, 9:44 p.m.
"So, what did we miss
at Marquee last night?"
God damn it, Ashley,
go to some better places.
Quit wasting your life
in these shitty clubs.
No, no, no, it's fine.
And then he says,
"Is that what you're up to tonight?"
And then you say, "I'm on my way
to the Aziz show at MSG."
And he goes, "Oh, okay,
dot-dot-dot. Enjoy."
Ashley, I think I speak
for everyone here when I say,
"Fuck this guy."
Thank you very much for
sharing that with us, Ashley.
So, that's it, man.
That's what everyone
has to deal with now.
When they meet someone,
they have to engage in that kind of stuff.
And I was in that world for a long time.
And it can be fun,
but it can get frustrating.
And now I'm in a different world,
now I'm in a relationship,
and the rela--
Don't do that shit.
Don't clap.
That is so rude
to all the single people here.
I used to do stand-up
where I said I was single,
no one ever clapped,
no one said shit.
No one was like, "Get it, Aziz!
Fuck everybody! Now is your time!"
Both things are very fun.
It's fun being single,
it's fun being in a relationship.
They're both fun, all right?
But I'm in the relationship right now
and the relationship's going great.
But it's also fairly new,
it's about a year and a few months.
I feel like whenever you talk to people
in longer relationships,
they're always like,
"Oh, my God.
Those first few years
are such a magical time.
You have to enjoy that,
it's so amazing."
And it's weird being
in the magical zone,
and knowing that the magic
is gonna change soon.
You know what I mean?
Like, right now, things are crazy.
Like, right now, um, you know,
last time I was in New York,
there was a bad snowstorm,
and I stepped in this huge puddle
of sludge and my foot got soaked.
And the first thing I did
was I sent her a text.
I said, "You know
how you feel days like today,
when you step in a puddle of sludge
and your foot gets soaked?
Every second with you,
it feels like the pure opposite of that."
Aw!
And yes, that's a little
cheesy or whatever,
but I'm just sharing that so you know,
that's where my heart is, right?
But what's weird is knowing that
that text will eventually change, right?
Like, people in long relationships,
doesn't that text eventually change?
Doesn't that text
eventually become like,
"Fuck! I stepped in some sludge.
Do we have to get dinner
with your friends?
Can you tell them I died
in a hovercraft accident?
I never wanna see 'em again.
Why do we always
hang out with my friends?
'Cause they're better people!"
But I hope we're able to maintain
some version of that love as things go on,
'cause it's an amazing thing.
It's so beautiful
to get messages like that.
She sent me a message one time,
she said, "You feel like home to me.
Even if we're in a hotel or something,
I feel like I'm home, 'cause I'm with you.
And when I wake up and I see your face,
I remember that I'm home.
That's one of the reasons
I love you so much."
She sent me that when I went away
for five minutes to take a shit.
You realize how awesome
it is to be shitting
and to read a message like that?
It was like waste was leaving my body
and love was coming in.
It was... an amazing feeling.
Did you guys know there's actually
two different types of love?
There is, it's true.
There's two different types of love.
There's passionate love
and companion love.
Passionate love is like the crazy love
you feel when you first meet someone
and you're going crazy,
you're just like, "Ahh!"
But that eventually calms down
into something different
called companion love,
which is not worse,
it's just different, less intense.
And, you know,
it's kind of a bummer, but I get it.
I understand why we have
the two different types of love.
You couldn't just have
the crazy love your whole life,
'cause then society
wouldn't function, right?
We'd all just be in our homes,
just staring at each other like...
And the streets would just be filled
with homeless children eating garbage,
riding large animals. I get it.
So that's why we have
two different types of love.
But when I first heard
about that, I was like,
"Wouldn't it be interesting to just have
the crazy stuff for a while?
What would that be like?"
Maybe, instead of having
one long relationship,
you have a bunch of
shorter relationships.
Your graph of love and happiness
is just like,
boom, boom, boom!
But, you know,
I don't think you can do that graph.
I've tried to do that graph,
I've seen friends try to do that graph.
And, yes, it can be
a lot of fun for a while,
but eventually
that graph gets weird.
You know, eventually that graph
becomes something like this.
You know, it's like, "Oh, shit!
Me and the boys, we're going out tonight.
This bar's gonna be crazy.
Oh, my God,
there's so many hot girls here.
Yeah, this one girl is really into me.
Yeah, we're going home together.
Yeah, we're having sex.
Yeah, I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I came!
This feels empty, this feels empty,
this feels empty.
I gotta get out of here!
This feels empty, this feels empty,
this feels empty.
Okay, okay, okay!
I got out of there. I got out of there.
I just got some brunch.
I'm drinking some water,
I'm drinking some coconut water.
I'm getting hydrated.
That's right, I'm getting hydrated.
I'm ready to run it back!
That's right!
Night two, me and the boys,
we're going out tonight!
This bar's gonna be crazy.
This bar's gonna be--
Okay, no one's really out tonight.
Okay, so, uh...
More of a low-key type situation.
Okay, me and the boys will just
get drunk by ourselves. No shame there.
Okay, it's getting little bit weird, uh...
We'll just get some tacos.
Tacos are delicious."
You wake up the next morning,
"Oh, my God! Why did I eat
three quesadillas then a bowl of cereal?
That was really unnecessary.
Okay, well...
I'm just gonna go back to bed.
I feel like garbage, and uh...
God, you know, this is fun, hooking up
with these hot girls or whatever,
but frankly, I wish...
I just had someone I really cared about,
that I could hold.
But I don't have that person, so...
I'm just gonna jerk off and go to bed."
So now, I'm trying the relationship graph.
But the relationship graph
is fucked up too.
Like, if you take the traditional
definition of a successful relationship,
and you put it in that graph,
that graph is fucked up too.
This is that graph, okay?
You meet the person...
"Oh, my God,
all these experiences are amazing!
All these experiences are amazing!
All these-- Okay.
Some of the experiences
are getting repetitive.
But you know what?
I love this person so much.
We're getting married!
Yeah! We're getting married!
Oh, my God, we have a wedding!
All our friends came!
This is so fun!
I can't believe it!
I'm a husband. I have a wife.
Oh, my God, this is the great--
Oh, my God, we just had a kid!
Oh, my God, this is so hard!
Oh, my God, this is the hardest thing
I've ever done in my life.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Okay, okay, okay!
The kid's walking around and talking
and saying stuff. This is amazing.
I've never felt so proud
of anything in my entire life.
Oh, my God, we just had another kid!
Why did we stop using the birth control?
That was so stupid!
And why did we think it would
be easier the second time around?
This is not analogous at all!
There is now two goddamn people
at the same goddamn time!
It's so much harder!
We gotta-- Oh, my God,
we gotta pay for all the stuff!
How does anyone afford children?
We gotta get them into
a good kindergarten.
What the fuck's a good kindergarten?
They just sing songs!
Who is fucking that up?
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
we got them into the good kindergarten.
We got them into the good kindergarten.
We got them in.
Now they're in elementary school.
They're drawing pictures and stuff,
this is pretty cool.
Okay, now they're in adolescence.
Oh, these kids are fucking pricks!
I fucking hate these kids!
I want them to die!
I want my whole family to die!
I don't really want them to die.
I just wanna feel
what it would feel like
to murder every single person
I live with.
Okay, I can't do that.
I can't do that.
Okay, now they're in high school.
They're in high school now.
This is good, they're in high school,
a little bit older.
I can hang out with them.
Oh, God.
One of the kids might be having sex.
Yeah, he might be doing drugs.
I gotta put spyware on his phone
to make sure he's not messing around.
This is my life now.
I gotta read this mess
whenever I get home from work.
'Hey, what's going on?'
'Nothing.
You wanna come hang out later?'
'Maybe.' 'All right.' 'Well--'
Will you fucking buy some weed already
so I can justify this use of my time?
Okay, okay!
One of the kids is going to college.
He's gone, he's gone.
Oh, shit, the other kid's gone.
They're both gone.
It's just us in the house together again.
We're spending time together again.
We've refound our passionate love!
Finally, we can travel the world!
I'm too tired to travel the world.
Let's just take it easy.
Let's just take it easy in the house.
It's fine.
We got the house to ourselves.
This is good.
You know, it's okay.
It's kind of boring, but it's good.
We don't have to work and stuff.
It's okay.
It's fine, the kids come to visit
every now and then, it's okay.
Okay. Oh, God.
Oh, God, my wife is sick.
Oh, no, my wife's sick.
Oh, no, my wife just passed.
Oh, God, I'm all by myself.
I'm so alone.
Oh, God, I'm sick now too.
I'm sick now too.
I can't even walk.
I've walked my entire life,
and now I can't even walk.
But now I get to get
one of those Rascal scooters!
I'm gonna drive that
motherfucker everywhere!"
New York, thank you so much!
Thank you again for coming out,
I really do appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
You guys can sit down.
Thank you so much.
Um, serious question here.
Has anyone here ever seen a ghost?
I love ghost stories.
Someone once told me and my girlfriend
this really scary ghost story
about a little boy.
And it was so scary,
and she gets really scared of ghosts.
So, I started doing this thing where
every now and then we're asleep,
I'll just wake her up in the middle
of the night and I'll just be like,
"Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, boo...
what's that little boy
doing over there?"
And she hates it!
And I love it!
And I do it all the time.
What I'd really like to do, though,
one day, is...
And this is like something...
I don't know if it might be
too messed up to do, but, um...
She's, like, the nicest,
sweetest person.
Anytime I need a drink
in the middle of the night,
she's always like,
"Oh, I'll go down and get it."
I'm always like,
"No, no, it's fine. I'll get it."
But what if, one night, I was like,
"Yeah, can you go down and get it?"
And then she goes downstairs,
and there, unbeknownst to her...
I've hired a little boy.
And he's wearing, like,
old-timey clothes.
And as soon as she gets downstairs,
he's just like,
"Mommy, where have you been?"
I wanna do it so bad!
But I can't.
I've thought it through,
there's three reasons why I can't do it.
One, I would never wanna
scare anyone that bad, right?
That's a terrifying thing.
Two, if I did pull it off,
I'd live in eternal fear
over what the fuck she was gonna
do to get back at me.
'Cause I'm pretty sure
she's not gonna let that one slide.
And three, this is probably
the biggest reason not to do it,
she would murder the little boy.
Like, the little boy's dead.
So, I don't think I can do it.
I'm a good boyfriend, though.
She's never really been upset with me
about anything, that I can think of.
The only time I remember
she was kind of mad was once,
when I was flying from
New York to New Zealand.
I was gonna be gone for a while
to go to a wedding.
I was calling her when I was on the plane
to talk to her before we took off,
and I got her voicemail, so I texted her.
I was, like, "Hey, it's me.
Just wanted to talk
before the flight took off."
And she texts me back and says,
"I called you four hours ago."
And I could tell she was upset,
'cause she also included
the emoji of the Indian guy
with the gun beside his head.
This tipped me off.
So I called her back and I was like,
"What's up with that?
Why you gotta say that?
What did I do?"
She's like,
"I called you four hours ago."
I was like, "I know.
I was busy packing and everything.
I knew I'd have time to call you
when I got on the plane.
That's why I waited."
She's like, "Oh, you were busy?
You were busy.
Well, I looked on
your friend's Instagram
and he posted a photo of you
hanging out by the pool,
snapping Polaroids.
So, I feel like, if you have time
to hang out by the pool
and play with your Polaroid camera,
I think you have time to call me back."
And I was like, "Okay, I'm sorry."
Cut to a week later.
It's Valentine's Day,
I've done all this romantic stuff,
and it's time for us
to exchange gifts.
I have her gift, it's all wrapped up,
and I'm just like, uh...
"So, hey, remember, like,
a week ago, you were upset that...
I didn't call you back and
I was hanging out by the pool,
playing with a Polaroid camera?
Well, the reason I was doing that is,
I bought you this nice
vintage Polaroid camera
and I just wanted to make sure
it worked before I gave it to you.
So, here's your gift."
Fuck you!
And she felt horrible,
which is the greatest
Valentine's Day gift I've ever received.
New York, thank you again!
This was awesome.
Thank you guys again so much
for coming out.
Thank you very, very much.
Thank you so much. I really appreciate it.
This was fucking awesome. Thanks.
Good night.
These are my parents.
Thank you again. Good night.