Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
- [rock music plays]
- [crowd cheering]
[crowd cheering]
Thank you.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Thank you for clapping.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you. That's cool.
All right.
This is a good crowd.
This is...
All right. Thank you.
That guy has a high voice.
- [laughter]
- [laughs]
All right, I got a lot of jokes,
so I'm just gonna start
telling them. Here we go.
I went to a baseball game
last summer in a stadium
and they had a huge TV
in the stadium. A Jumbotron.
And this guy proposed to his
girlfriend using the giant TV.
He put her name up there,
said, "Will you marry me?"
She said yes.
The crowd went wild.
They found the couple
in the audience.
I was sitting there thinking,
"God, that's so romantic.
That's so cool."
And then I remembered thinking,
you know, you could also
use a screen like that
if you're having trouble
breaking up with somebody.
Be like, "Hey, I'm gonna
grab a hot dog.
But you should definitely
look at that screen."
That's a smooth way out of it.
I think my favorite sign
that I've seen
is "Bridge May Be Icy."
'Cause it's so honest, you know?
It's just like,
"Bridge... may be,
I don't know. I'm...
...a sign. I don't have
a conscious mind. I'm...
...a tilted yellow square.
What are these shapes
on the front of me?
I mean, bridge may be chocolate.
Whatever you want.
I don't care."
"Bridge may not be icy."
That means the same thing
as "Bridge may be icy."
That's... even better, you know?
More optimistic.
That's a better sign.
"Bridge may not be icy."
Hey, I like your attitude, sign.
"Bridge probably not icy.
Give it a shot." Even better.
It's August, bridge probably
not icy. You're right.
One sign I don't like
is "Please use other door."
You're a fucking door,
you don't get to take a break.
Just be a door.
Just swing.
This door thinks it's a wall.
This is ridiculous.
When I see
"Please use other door,"
I wish I had a sign with me
to put on the other door
that says "No, no, no.
Use... first door.
First door pulling bullshit.
First door lazy.
Use first door. Trust me,
find way to use first door."
Yeah. Okay.
[chuckles]
I like that sign
"Beware of dog."
I saw that at Staples,
they had them.
They look really professional.
I just wanted
to buy a pile of them.
Just put 'em up
in stupid places, you know?
Like... like in the men's room
of a fancy restaurant.
Guy gets up to go
to the bathroom,
"Oh, shit. There's a...
There's a dog in the men's room.
I think I'm..."
Just hang one
around a dog's neck.
What a vicious, considerate
poodle we have here.
Look at that.
Or maybe, you know,
like if you get a massage,
they lay you down
on that table,
and there's a hole
that you look through.
Just centered under the hole
on the floor.
Guy's like, "Oh, I'm gonna
get a massage. Great.
Oh, shit.
There's a freaking dog
in this room."
Pets are animals
that are not delicious.
I don't think that
was by mistake.
I think we probably
tried to eat all of them.
Like, "Okay, these don't taste
good, so we'll give these
first names and sweaters
and we'll hang out with them.
And then, uh, let's eat
the rest. Let's eat these."
[laughs]
We even eat birds. I can't
believe we eat birds.
How did that start? Somebody
was like, "You see that
flying up there?
I wanna put that in my mouth.
Yeah, that looks good."
"It's covered in feathers."
"No, no, no.
I'll do some shit to it.
I'll make it good."
"What if it doesn't taste good?"
"Well, then I'll capture it,
and I'll put it in a cage
and it'll live in my kitchen.
And I'll have it shit
on old news."
I think we're mean
to birds, man. Like...
I mean, turkeys,
we break the wishbone.
We've killed the bird,
we've cooked it,
and we've eaten it.
Then we're like,
"You wanna break
its fucking bones, man?"
"Yeah. Yeah, let's...
let's break its bones, man.
We'll make a wish."
"What did you wish for?"
"Death to all turkeys."
It seems like there's
a fine line between having a pet
and having a hostage
from a different species.
You go to somebody's house,
they're like, "Close the door.
He'll get out. Close the door!
He'll get out!"
Okay.
What kind of relationship do you
have with this dog exactly?
Owner walks away,
the dog's like... [pants]
"He's not looking. Open
the door, let me out. Come on.
I can't shit when I want to.
Open this door!
This woman put sunglasses
on me last week.
I'm gonna eat her
when she's sleeping if you don't
open the goddamn door
right now."
I saw a poster that said
"Missing cat."
They had a picture of the cat
and a whole description.
Missing, huh?
I think that's
from the human perspective.
The cat made that poster,
it would say, "Free cat.
Finally." Picture of the cat
would be like...
"Cat is hunter, cat gets own
food, cat has no first name,
don't look for cat, fuck off,
leave cat alone, fuck off."
Okay, cat, we get it. Jesus.
The hairless cat,
that's a weird looking animal.
Looks like somebody
procrastinated when they were
designing animals or something.
Like, "Okay, animals
are due for earth today."
"I thought they
were due Monday."
"No, they're due today."
"Oh, shit. Uh...
Yeah, no, I am finished. Uh...
It's, uh...
The hairless cat,
what do you think?"
"I think it looks
like a meth addict.
Let's see what God says,
come on."
I wonder what the hairless cat
looks like to regular cats.
Just walks by
and they're like, "Whore."
I've learned that there's a fine
line between killing a fly
and applauding a fly.
There was one in my living room,
I was trying to kill it.
But I was too slow.
So was I just...
...following the fly
around my house,
clapping for it.
Sending the exact wrong message
to the fly.
He's like, "Oh, this guy, uh...
he likes what I'm doing.
Huh, you like that?
You think that's impressive,
let me fly right up to your face
give you a close-up
of some of this.
Oh, now he's waving at me."
I have an L-shaped sofa.
Lowercase.
- [applause]
- Thanks.
Soap scum seems like a really
harsh term for that stuff.
Maybe we overreacted
a little bit with that one.
"Look at this soap scum."
"I think that's just
dried soap, man."
"No.
This shit betrayed me.
This used to help me clean,
now I have to clean it?
It's the lowest form
of soap there is, man.
You're looking at scum
right there."
When I was little,
I learned that "please"
was the magic word.
Then I got a little older,
and I learned that "abracadabra"
was the magic word.
Then I learned that they're
never interchangeable,
under any circumstances.
"For you, sir."
"I will have the grilled cheese
with tomato, abracadabra."
"Okay, here's your
grilled cheese. Enjoy."
"Will you abracadabra
just look at me
when I'm talking to you?"
"Bitch, abracadabra."
And there's a fourth example,
but I can't say it
'cause I'm a white comedian.
[laughter]
Those are the rules.
White privilege does not extend
onto the stage, you see.
One thing you don't see
that often is a black magician.
There aren't that many
black magicians.
Probably because of racism.
If a black guy makes something
disappear, they're like,
"Hey, get him!"
"It's magic."
"No, you're black."
White guy can make
a whole woman disappear.
They're like, "Ah, she's fine.
He's white.
Don't worry about it."
People get so mad when you run
and try to catch the elevator.
I can't get over how angry
they get.
What they really hate
is when you run and catch it
and you go, "I just wanna say
hey, everybody.
Have a good ride. Okay?"
They don't like that.
People are crabby in elevators.
One time I was in an elevator
and I hit the wrong floor.
And then I hit my floor.
And people looked at me
like I stabbed a baby
in front of them or something.
I just...
I just made a mistake, you know?
Longest moment of my life was
when we got to the first floor
that I hit...
The doors opened, and nobody
got on, nobody got off.
I was like...
[humming nervously]
The elevator was like,
"Oh, this asshole messed up.
I'm gonna stay open
extra long."
I had to, like, improvise
some sort of a cover, you know?
I just leaned out, I was like,
"Bobby? Pssh.
He said he was gonna met me
on four. That's weird.
[makes farting sound]
Anyway..."
If you ask somebody how they're
doing, sometimes they'll say,
"A-OK." It's like
they're giving you the beginning
of a weird multiple choice
answer or something.
"How you doing?"
"A-OK.
B-suicidal. Uh...
C-horny." "Okay,
I think I'm gonna head out."
"D-all of the above.
Hold on."
I was in the supermarket
and I saw they
had prune juice for sale.
And I had to stop 'cause I was
like, "Prune juice?
I thought prunes
were dried plums.
What the hell is prune juice?
How hard are we squeezing
these prunes?"
"Come on, you little shit.
We'll get some juice out of you.
Come on."
"Okay, that's 97 prunes,
we have one glass.
Should we keep going?"
There's no such thing
as prune juice. That's bullshit.
That's plum juice.
That's the reason you're a prune
is that we took the juice
from the plum, leaving you.
And then you took credit...
...calling it your juice?
What a dick move, prunes.
I've never seen raisin juice
for sale.
Prunes are pushy.
I mean, that's their nature.
You eat a prune... [laughs]
- That's like...
- [applause]
...sending a cop
into your stomach
to break up the party.
Food's digesting, having
a good time, you eat a prune.
"Lights on. Let's go.
Everybody out.
Come on, move. We gotta go. Go."
Piece of broccoli,
"My friend's still in there."
"I don't give
a shit. No pun intended.
We gotta clear the room."
Freaking prunes.
You ruin everything.
I like French toast way better
than toast.
I think a French kiss
is nicer than just a plain kiss.
So I guess the rule is
if you make something French,
- you make it better.
- [woman cheers]
- Except for people.
- [laughter, applause]
It's the...
it's the one exception.
But, you know... [laughs]
I'm just saying
they're not better.
They're equal,
they're the same as us.
French people...
A souvenir is a funny thing
to me.
What an interesting concept.
It's like, "Hey,
I got you something to remember
the time I went to Paris
and you didn't.
Yeah, put this on your mantle
so you can remember the time
that I had a great vacation
and you stayed home
'cause you couldn't afford
to go. There you go, enjoy.
A piece of garbage
from another continent.
Do what you want with it."
I like airports, though,
'cause they have
those flat escalators.
People never look more
like groceries
than when they're going
through an airport.
Just going by. I wanna get one
of those rubber dividers
in the supermarket,
just put it on the thing there.
"This is my stuff,
that's your stuff.
Don't try to make me carry
your shit, okay? That's mine."
I don't like when I'm stopped
at a stoplight,
I'm sitting there in my car,
the light changes,
and people in the crosswalk,
and they don't, like,
hurry up to get out of the way.
And sometimes it'll be
like a tough guy in the group,
and he'll, like,
slow down almost.
Just to show how tough he is.
He's like looking at my car
like he's gonna fight it.
You know?
I think you should be able
to hit one person a year
- with your car.
- [laughter, applause]
Not to kill,
just to communicate.
Just to say, "Hey, you know,
it was my turn."
Then as he rolls over the top
of your car,
maybe he'd be thinking,
"God, this guy used
his one hit for the year on me.
Maybe I'm a dick."
Yeah.
If I'm in the crosswalk
and the light changes,
I'm not saying I run
out of the way,
but I make a gesture
to the driver who's waiting
to let them know that I'm not
a dick. Know what I mean?
The light changes, I don't run,
but I do a thing with my arms.
I go...
Just so they can see,
"Oh, his torso's running. Look.
He's trying.
This guy's...
He's a good person.
You see that?
The top half is considerate."
I like that
at a lot of crosswalks
they have a countdown.
It's like they tell you exactly
when it will be funny to push
your friend into traffic.
Just like, "Here we go."
One time I was at a crosswalk
and I saw a guy
wearing the same shirt
that I was wearing.
It was kind of a specific shirt
and I looked at him,
and he was a dork.
Just like a dorky looking guy.
And I thought, I've got
the same taste as a dork.
That makes me a dork.
That sucks. You know?
Two months later,
I'm in a restaurant.
It happened again. I see a guy
wearing the same shirt
that I'm wearing,
but he was really good-looking.
He was with a beautiful woman.
And I just looked at him
and I thought,
"I'm the dork."
[laughter]
Can't win.
I bought a box of crackers,
took out the first cracker,
and I looked at it, it had holes
throughout the cracker.
I was trying to figure out,
why are there holes?
For aerodynamics maybe?
Just... whoosh! Oh.
Look how quickly I can
eat these crackers.
[whooshing]
I'm so glad they perforated
them with that tiny drill press.
That's like [whooshing]
Without those, ugh! Fucking wind
resistance on these crackers.
That joke never does well,
but I like it.
- So I don't give a shit.
- [applause]
I believe in it. You know,
there were like six people
in here who liked it,
so that's, you know,
that's my demographic
for the crackers joke.
And it's... I stand by it.
How bad does a guess
have to be
for it to be
an uneducated guess?
"Do you know the temperature
outside?"
"Uh, carrots?"
"Did you say carrots?"
"Yeah, I was just guessing.
I don't know, carrots?"
"Are you educated?"
"No. No, I'm not." "Okay.
Well, that makes sense because
it's never been carrots outside
and never will be carrots.
So you need to get an education,
go to school, then come back
to me, maybe you can
make an educated guess."
"Okay."
I wonder what a walrus vampire
would look like.
Probably a lot like the other
walruses, I don't know.
Be hard to pick it out
of a crowd. [laughs]
I like the word "folks"
'cause it's so positive.
You know, black folks,
white folks, Asian folks.
It's just got a good feel to it.
You never hear,
"I was at a party and these
fucking folks showed up.
Folks are the worst, man."
You never hear on the news,
"22 folks were killed
when a bus hit a train."
"Oh, those poor folks!"
Quesadilla, that's a word
that you never
see the English translation for.
You never see that in English.
You know? They just keep it
in Spanish.
I guess 'cause maybe it's too
awkward or something.
You know, "And for you, sir?"
"I will have the quesa...
'cheese female small, ' please.
One little cheese girl for me,
that'd be great."
[chuckles]
"Okay. You want any peppers
or chicken in there?"
"No, I think she's
been through enough.
I'll just have the... [laughs]"
I feel like they could bring
fajitas out from the kitchen
a little bit later.
There's a lot of showboating
going on with fajitas.
Seems unnecessary,
a fire emergency coming
through the dining room.
"Ah, it's fajitas,
they just need attention.
Fuck 'em."
I was eating some fajitas
and I burnt the roof
of my mouth.
And I was like, "Ow! The roof
of my mouth, that hurts.
It's really tender. Wait
a minute. The roof of my mouth?
This is the ceiling of my mouth.
The roof of my mouth
is way up here.
Whoever named this was not using
the attic of their mouth
at all."
[laughter, applause]
Thanks.
I love applause
for head architecture.
This is a good crowd.
I took Super Shuttle
from the airport.
I think they forgot to put
the word "slow" in the middle
- of their name.
- [scattered applause]
Hey, if I'm eating
some Tic Tacs,
and you want some,
I'm happy to give you some.
Just don't give me
a specific number.
It's too stressful.
You know?
You want two?
Okay, one... 11. Fuck.
No, I don't want those back.
Just...
They're in your palm,
just keep them. Okay? Thank you.
When I was in high school,
I took karate.
One time I lost my temper
in class.
That's when I learned that
there's a difference
between taking karate
and receiving karate.
I received the shit
out of that karate.
I like when people use
the term "color scheme."
'Cause it sounds so sneaky.
"Okay, we're gonna
make this room look great,
and here's how
we're gonna do it.
Blue. Beige. Green.
Sh! Somebody's coming.
Don't talk about colors.
Hey, how you doing?
What's up?"
[chuckles]
Sometimes the opposite
of something bad is also bad.
It's confusing.
Like pickpocketing. That's bad.
But I found that putting thing
in people's pockets
is also bad.
So pickpocketing
and its opposite, put-pocketing,
are both bad.
Logic is tricky.
When we talk to babies,
sometimes we use baby talk.
I guess to relate to the baby,
we try to sound more
like a baby.
You know, we'll be like,
"Hello, goo-goo, boopie."
We should do that
with old people too.
"Oh, hello, Grandpa.
Come here, you tired?
Oh, hello. Yes, oh. Hello."
If I live long enough,
that joke is gonna haunt me.
[laughter, applause]
We should do that with teenagers
too. "What's up, asshole?"
"What are you doing?"
"I'm talking teen. Teen talk.
Don't worry about it."
I parked my car in
a grocery store parking lot.
I got out of my car, and I
was walking towards the store
and this guy stopped me, goes,
"Hey, Demetri."
I said, "Yeah?" He said,
"Hey, um,
could I be in one
of your jokes?"
I said, "Uh, sure.
How about this one?"
[laughter]
He was like, "Okay.
What does it entail?"
I was like,
"That's pretty much it.
That's the joke."
He was like, "Then no.
I'm cool. No thanks.
I don't think I wanna
be in that joke."
I was like, "Too late.
I just told it."
He's like, "Seriously?"
I'm like, "Yeah. You're in it."
He was like, "Shit."
He walked away,
he was pissed off.
I was like, "You know,
fictional people
can be so moody,
it's ridiculous."
It's interesting that we say
"a head of lettuce"
but not a "dick of cucumber."
[laughter, applause]
"Yeah, give me, uh...
give me a dick of cucumber.
That'd be great.
You know what?
Two tits of cantaloupe.
Throw those in the bag too.
Are kiwis in season? They are.
Okay.
Three testicles of kiwi
and I think we're good.
Good.
And a rectum of fig.
That sounds delicious."
[laughs]
I'd say based on their behavior,
cherry tomatoes are not
interested in participating
in the salad.
Kind of like, "Whoa! Nice try.
I don't think so.
Watch out. Whoa! Whoa!"
How evasive are you gonna be?
It's like I'm trying to stab
a rubber ball in this salad.
This is ridiculous.
It's just too much work.
Then I get to the bottom
of the salad and it's just like
a bowl
of defiant small tomatoes
that are like...
"We're no longer a salad.
We're tomatoes. Now what?"
Well, then I'll just eat you
with my hand.
Then I bite it,
so much drama.
It's like... pssh! Blood! Ahh!
Salad is just too much work.
You know?
You gotta get the ingredients,
wash everything,
dry everything,
mix it together, dress it.
Then I go to eat the salad,
now I have to make a small copy
of the salad on my fork.
For every bite. I have to be
like, "Okay. Lettuce,
onion, cherry tomato, cherry...
Forget it.
Mushroom, pepper.
Gotta make another
small salad. Here we go.
Lettuce..."
"How's your salad?"
"It's 17 small salads
that I had to make."
That's probably why in a
restaurant the waiter's like,
"Are you still working
on that salad?"
"You're goddamn right
I'm working.
I'm exhausted.
Take this thing away from me."
I think if a recipe
is unhealthy for you,
they should change their tone
in how they describe the steps.
I feel like the tone
never changes.
It's just like a sociopath
telling you what to do,
and they don't care
if it's like quinoa
or cheesecake.
They're just like,
"Just do this, I don't care."
But if it's unhealthy, if it's
like cinnamon sticky buns,
"Step one: run seven miles.
Step six: before combining
brown sugar and caramel in bowl,
take off all of your clothes and
stand in front of the mirror.
You sure you wanna do this?
[sighs] All right.
Step 14: contact your doctor,
you have diabetes."
[laughs]
I can't believe people
can still die
from complications
in today's day and age.
That that counts
as a valid medical reason.
I mean, how's that
even acceptable?
"So what happened exactly?"
"Well, we got him into the OR,
and, uh, we opened him up,
and, uh, it was complicated.
You know?
It's, uh... it's a lot of blood
in there, all over the place,
and the organs are pretty
tightly packed.
Brenda didn't have a good lunch,
my phone went off twice,
it's just...
it was complicated. He's dead.
Okay? Forget about it."
If you get cremated,
is it all or nothing?
Can you make requests?
I wonder if you can be, like,
half or something.
Like, "What does he want?
Okay, says he wants
to be cremated
from the waist down. Okay?"
"Anything else?"
"Yeah, open casket.
He wants his torso
at the one end,
then the ashes,
and they lead to a lamp,
and, uh, he's dressed
as a genie."
[laughter, applause]
"Well, good for him.
He's having some fun with it.
I think that's cool."
I was thinking maybe
I'd get cremated.
But instead of having him put me
into an urn,
I'd have him put me
into, like, an hourglass.
Then I could still participate,
you know what I mean?
It'd be like my grandkids could
be playing a board game,
they'd be like, "That's my
grandfather on the mantel there.
Grab that. Yes.
He's like six minutes.
Flip him over. Bonus round,
Scattergories. Here we go."
Jokes that end in death
don't usually end happy.
Kind of like life.
- [laughs]
- [audience laughs]
I might just stick
to the prepared material
for the rest of the set.
I thought... I thought I could
freestyle a little bit,
but the insides came out
a little too much there.
"How was the show?"
"I'm sad."
When they say someone is gone
but not forgotten,
it's such a nice sentiment.
You know what I mean?
Forgotten but not gone...
that just sucks.
"Did he die?"
"Who are we even talking about?
I don't remember."
Oh, that sucks.
When something goes wrong,
people send you their thoughts
and prayers.
And, uh, it's a nice idea,
but it's kind of weird.
You know what I mean? I
understand sending the prayers,
but the thoughts...
that's kind of strange.
"What do you got there?"
"Demetri sent us his thoughts
and prayers."
"How do they look?"
"Uh, the prayers look
appropriate. Um...
The thoughts are kind of weird.
He's...
...thinking of clipping
his toenails tonight
before he goes to bed.
I don't know why we need to know
that. We're grieving here.
But thanks."
I was walking on the beach
in California,
and a volleyball rolled up
by my feet.
And this guy yelled,
"Little help!"
So I just kicked it
a little bit towards him.
I like watching volleyball.
I think it's a good sport
to watch.
'Cause most sports
it looks like all the players
really want the ball.
But volleyball is different.
That looks like nobody
wants that thing.
Like, "Okay, we don't want this.
You guys take it.
Here you go." Each player's
like, "I don't want it.
You take it.
I don't fucking want it!"
"Let's try this again.
We don't want this."
It looks like a game
for people
who don't like volleyballs.
Football, on the other hand,
that looks like
everybody wants that thing
so badly. Know what I mean?
All the players are like,
"Give me the ball.
I'll catch it, I won't drop it.
I'll covet it, I'll protect it,
it's mine," you know?
They should make the football
look like something
that you would protect
and covet and hold.
A baby. A football should look
like a baby.
Imagine if they were shaped
like babies.
Those guys would
look like such heroes,
like throwing and catching
the baby
and protecting it, you know?
Until they get to the extra
point, then it looks like,
"I'm sick of this
freaking baby." [thudding sound]
- [chuckles]
- [applause]
Baby just goes
through the uprights.
"It's okay." [laughs]
Indoor sports don't look
as cool as outdoor sports.
Pool looks pretty cool.
But I've seen that in movies
where the guy's like... boof!
And the lady walks in,
he's just kind of
looking smooth.
But I don't even know what's the
second coolest indoor sport.
It's like a distant second.
Maybe darts?
She walks in the bar
and you're like... [laughs]
Air hockey?
Foosball.
That's the worst.
You don't wanna do foosball.
Are sheep pubes
also wool?
How much of my turtleneck
is pubes?
I don't know if I want
to wear that thing anymore.
Pubes on my neck.
I don't like that.
You can say
"Mind your own business,"
or you can say
"Mind your own beeswax."
I think that's the only time
you can really substitute
"beeswax" for "business."
"Is your trip beeswax
or pleasure, sir?"
"It's, uh,
it's a beeswax trip, actually.
[laughs] It's personal beeswax.
I'd rather not talk about it."
"What are you doing
after college?"
"Um, applied to beeswax school.
So we'll see what happens.
My dad's
a small beeswax owner."
I like the word "nope"
because it's really specific.
That's for when you
wanna say "no,"
but you're also happy about it.
"Are you guys still
serving breakfast?" "Nope."
'Cause you never hear
"Unfortunately, nope."
"Nope" is for dicks.
Sometimes when I have to fart,
I feel like my stomach
is like a pushy attorney
and my butt is like a judge.
They're going back and forth
having this furious debate,
just back and forth,
more and more heated,
and eventually my butt is like,
"I'll allow it."
[laughter, applause]
"Sustained.
This better be silent,
counselor."
It's so frustrating.
I don't know why,
but I think
of so many fart jokes.
I'll sit down to write some
jokes, we go for a walk,
fart jokes just float
into my head.
I'm prolific with fart jokes.
But it's frustrating
because I can't tell them all,
because it's a bad style
to have as a comedian.
You know what I mean?
You don't wanna be the guy
who tells a lot of fart jokes.
So I end up having
to hold them in.
I actually have to hold in...
...jokes about farts, even.
And it hurts.
Then I get home, and I just
tell one giant fart joke...
[laughs] ...to my place
when I'm alone,
and that's terrible.
I don't know a lot about
the laws of the universe,
but I will say this,
just on the topic.
If you're a man
and you're alone somewhere,
and you fart,
a woman will appear.
Just bam! Just like that.
It's like they know
and they just send one.
"He just farted. Get over there.
You're attractive? Even better.
Go, go, go.
Stand next to him!
Embarrass that dude!" [laughs]
My friend said,
"I'm way better with faces
than I am with names."
It's like, yeah, me too.
Everybody is.
If I see somebody, I'm like,
"That's his face, right there.
The fleshy part on the front.
That's his face. Yeah."
I heard somebody say,
"He's like a brother to me."
I said, "Oh, I'm so sorry.
So he stole a bunch of money
from your mom and he tries
to fight you whenever you
go back to New Jersey?
I can relate." [laughs]
- Too real, guys, too real.
- [laughter]
I was in a jewelry store
and they had this necklace,
it was like cursive writing
in gold.
And it said "Diane."
And I went up the saleswoman
and I said, "You know, if you
had one that said 'Not Diane, '
I think you'd have
a bigger market."
And then I heard somebody go,
"Oh, that's a good point."
I turned and it was the guy
from the parking lot
at the grocery store.
- [applause, laughter]
- Just like...
What are you doing here?
He said, "I just wanted to stop
into another mediocre joke."
[laughs]
People say "shotgun"
when they want the front seat.
You should say "shotgun"
when you're eating rice
and you have to sneeze.
[laughter, applause]
'Cause there's that moment
where there's no turning back,
where you're just like,
"Snowstorm's about to come out
of my face, I don't know
how else to tell you this.
Just watch out."
I've heard people talk
about their private parts.
I'd like to hear someone
talk about their public parts.
"You okay?" "Yeah, yeah, I just
hurt my publics on that door.
I'm fine."
"Your publics?" "My hands, man,
my publics. You see?"
Sometimes I'll be
in an awkward situation,
and I'll try to save it
really quickly
by saying something fast, but
often it just makes it worse.
I was at a party
and this woman said,
"Excuse me, your fly is open."
I said, "For business."
And... "I mean, thank you.
Sorry, excuse me."
If you're on the phone
with somebody
and they're looking up
some information for you,
I don't know why,
but they often
make a soft laser sound
while you're waiting.
You know what I mean?
They'll be like, "Okay,
sir, let me just look up
your account number.
[softly] Too-too-too-too...
Too-too-too-too...
Too-too..."
What the hell was that?
Totally acceptable.
Only if it's a soft laser.
It can't be like, "Okay, sir,
just one minute.
[makes loud laser sound effects
and explosions]
There it is. 628...
Bum-bum-bum-bum..."
When they came out with
the Phillips head screwdriver,
I wonder if the guy who did
the flathead was like,
"What?
We can get credit for this?
Shit!"
If I see a scary movie
and then I come home,
and there's a noise in my house,
it sounds scary.
I've seen a lot of funny movies,
I wish it would work
the same way.
Like, "Did you hear that
in the kitchen?" "Yeah.
That was fucking hilarious."
"There is somebody hilarious
in this house." [laughs]
"I hope they bump
into some more stuff."
I don't like the way they write
on food packaging.
I think it's condescending.
Because they use euphemisms
where they really shouldn't.
You know? Like,
it'll say
"best before April 3rd."
Best before?
Is this the time
to be discussing excellence?
How about
"dangerous starting on"?
"Diarrhea at."
Food is tricky.
Like, milk starts out good,
then it becomes bad.
Then it becomes disgusting.
Then it becomes dangerous.
Then it becomes cheese.
Way to turn it around, milk!
[applause, laughter]
Who figured that out?
"Man, your place
smells terrible.
You gotta get rid of this crap."
"Hold on.
I just... wait.
I wanna see where this is going.
This vomit-shit smell
might turn into the thing
I wanna melt
over everything I eat.
So just wait."
If I were inventing foods,
I would have never come up
with the hot dog.
That is a very counterintuitive
food design.
"Okay, what do you got?"
"All right. Uh, we start
with the intestine of a dead
animal. We take all the meat
byproduct you were gonna
throw away, grind it up,
shove it into the intestine."
"I'm listening.
What does it look like?"
"A severed penis."
"How is it served?"
"On a bun that looks like
partially spread apart
ass cheeks. What do you say?"
[laughter, applause]
"You're calling it dog.
Hm, very appealing."
"It'll work in America."
When I was in grade school,
they had the alphabet
on the wall above
the chalkboard,
kind of going around
the corner,
and it was interesting
'cause you could see
the uppercase and lowercase
letter for each letter.
It looked like a parent
and child from each family.
You know what I mean?
And with some of them,
you could really see
the resemblance.
Like with "X" I was like,
"That's definitely your parent.
I mean, I can see you're like
a carbon copy.
'C', I totally get it.
'Z, ' 'S, ' I mean... identical."
Others, like, harder
to really see, you know?
Like "A", like is that...
I don't know.
I don't really see
the resemblance.
Looks like an "O" with like
a crutch or something.
But okay.
"R"... did you smoke while you
were pregnant or something?
'Cause... that kid
looks unfinished.
That's kind of a weird-looking
child you have there.
And "Q", did "P" and "G"...
...kind of have an affair
or something?
And then they were
like, "Oh, what are we gonna do
with this kid?"
And "Q" was like,
"I hardly get used.
I could adopt it
and look after it, just...
We'll call it a 'Q'.
Don't worry about it."
If you're in a restaurant
and you wanna get the check,
you just go like that
and they bring you the check.
I think you should be able
to do that at your job too.
You know?
If your boss walks by, you be
like, "Can I get the check?
Can I... I need the check now.
Yeah, for the...
Thank you, yeah."
The only time it's okay
to throw a hamster
is if it's out of the window
of a burning building.
Then you're a hero.
You're like, "Live!
[sighs] That felt great.
It's the perfect size
and weight. I've always wanted
to flick one of those."
My smoke alarm is so annoying.
I hate that
that's how safety works,
is that they're gonna
annoy me into being safe.
I wanna put, like, microwave
popcorn around my house.
If I wake up in the middle
of the night, I'm like,
"That smells great.
I gotta get the fuck
out of here.
Get a snack on the way.
That's a good idea."
When you're trying to tell
somebody a letter on the phone,
you'll be like, "B as in boy.
M as in Mary."
That's what people do. They
always pick the first letter
of the word.
You could mix it up.
"O as in tango.
F as in deaf.
R as in fart." [laughs]
"Okay, sir, we get it."
I don't like fitted sheets.
I feel like
that's a very
passive-aggressive design
we're dealing with there.
Does it have to be
the exact same size
as my mattress? Couldn't you
give me a little bit
of wiggle room?
I do my laundry and I'm already
in a bad mood
as I approach my mattress.
Do the first corner,
then the second.
By the time I get to the third,
I'm looking at the fourth like,
"You son of a bitch."
I get over there and it's just
such a struggle. I'm like,
"I can't do it!
Come on, come on."
My fingers are killing me.
I'm just pulling that thing down
the side as far as I can go.
I get halfway down, I'm like,
"That's enough. It's fine."
Four in the morning.
"Surprise, bitch!"
"Get off me! Get off me!
Fine, I'll use you
as a thin blanket.
There you go. Now what?"
I find that athletic clothes
are perfect
for just sitting around in.
[applause, cheering]
These are pajamas that make me
look ambitious. I like this.
- [laughs]
- [whistling]
I'm an athlete.
I'll even watch sports.
There we go. I'm so close.
When I was in high school,
I couldn't decide
whether I wanted to be
on the debate team or not.
And that was frustrating.
Happy birthday, by the way.
- [woman] I just turned 30!
- Hey, I used statistics.
- Happy birthday.
- [laughter, applause]
That's great.
Thanks for coming.
You just turned 30.
That's cool. How's it going?
- [woman] Great.
- What are you doing?
Like life-wise? Job-wise?
I messed up that question.
I could just "What do you do?"
- She left. Oh, shit.
- [laughter]
She's like, "I'm 30, I don't
have to deal with this shit."
What's the minimum number
of people you can have
and it still counts
as a surprise party? I wonder.
It seems like it's gotta be
greater than one.
If you come home
and just one friend jumps out
from behind your couch,
"Surprise!"
"Get the hell out of my house!"
"It's a party."
"No, you're an intruder."
If I robbed people's houses,
I would just bring
a lot of people and a cake
just in case
the person came home.
They walk in, you're like,
"Surprise!
Hey, we got you all your stuff.
We put it in bags.
Okay, we're gonna go.
Enjoy the cake.
Bye."
I think what I like the most
about people
who are very religious
is how open they are
to other people's
points of view.
It's nice.
I like atheists
because you don't really
ever hear about, like,
an atheist, like,
blowing up a school or,
you know,
a restaurant or something.
They're never like,
"Science!" [imitates explosion]
"Logic!" [imitates machine gun]
I heard this R&B song.
It came on the radio.
I was in a rental car.
I turned the radio on.
This song comes on.
This guy's, like,
kind of telling a story,
he's kind of whining.
But okay, I'm listening.
All of a sudden,
in the middle of the song,
a rapper shows up.
Guess these guys are friends
or something. He shows up,
he does a whole rap
of just his own thing.
Finishes up, he takes off.
We never hear from him again.
He's gone. First guy comes back
and he finishes the story,
and then the song's over. I just
thought that was hilarious.
'Cause I've never seen that
in any other art form.
You know? Not like
in literature, you know,
you're reading a book. "What'd
you think of that novel?"
"Pretty good, you know, like,
I got into the story,
first seven chapters.
Then in the middle,
there was a really angry
first person essay...
This other writer, I guess.
I don't know if they're friends
or something, but... You know,
this guy has a big dick,
he's gonna sleep with all these
women, it's a whole thing.
And... he's not gonna
by them stuff, though.
He made that clear.
He'll sleep with them,
but he's not, you know,
not looking to get tied down.
All caps. Very confident. Uh...
A lot of it rhymed,
and then the essay was over.
And then went back to the story.
Yeah, it was all right."
When I was a kid,
I could climb trees.
That was a thing I could do
that I can't do anymore.
I lost that privilege. You know?
If I go down a street and I see
a bunch of kids in trees,
I'm like, oh,
they're having fun.
If I go down the same street
and there are adults in all
the trees,
I'm like, "I need to get
into a fucking tree now."
[applause]
"Something bad is happening
on this street.
There's like a wolf or something
around here."
That's how you know you're
a grownup,
if someone sees you in a tree
and they're like,
"Get help!"
I don't know why, but if
somebody's smelling something,
and they also close their eyes
while they're doing it,
I just wanna smack them
in the face.
"Open your eyes.
You can do both.
You can look and smell
at the same time.
Don't do that."
Sometimes they have a bottle
and they'll have
a little ship inside.
Looks cool. It's like the ship
in the bottle, you know?
That would probably
be the worst thing
to have float up to an island
that you're stranded on.
"This is no time for irony!"
People only mention
that it's a free country
when they're
doing something shitty.
[laughter, applause]
- It's like...
- [cheering]
"Hey, that's my seat."
"It's a free country."
[mutters] Motherfucker...
People should mention it's
a free country when they're
doing something nice too. Hold
the door for a bunch of people
"Thank you, sir."
"It's a free country."
"Yes, it is, and you
are a patriot. Thank you."
- [cheering, whistling]
- Yeah.
I wonder if you're in prison,
if the other inmates
judge you based on
what you're in for.
Like, when they're organizing
events or activities, you know.
Like, "Should we get Joey
on the committee?"
"No, he's in
for attempted murder.
I feel like he doesn't really
see things through."
[laughter]
On your tombstone...
stay with me.
[laughs]
On your tombstone,
they have the birthdate,
and the death date.
And in between, your whole life,
everything you experienced,
joys, triumphs, defeat,
love, heart break...
Pshht!
Your whole life is just
a little dash after all this.
That's a bummer.
I'm not doing that.
I'm gonna have an ellipsis.
I'm gonna have three dots.
Somebody looks at my tombstone,
there'll be suspense.
They'll be like, "He was born...
Then what?
Uh, he died. There it is.
Right there."
- But then...
- [cheering]
...three more dots,
and a third date.
"Holy shit, this guy rallied!
Whoa! What an interesting
dead person."
I would never go
tandem skydiving.
If something goes wrong, you're
getting dry-humped to death.
What a terrible way to go.
"What happened?"
"Uh, looks like he got
dry-humped going about 200 miles
per hour into the earth."
I got an email from someone
that said, at the bottom,
"Warmest regards, Steven."
That's when I realized that's
as warm as you can go
with regards.
You know what I mean?
Like, "Hot regards, Steven."
That's no appropriate, Steven.
"Steaming hot regards." What,
did you just take a shit
in my email?
Warm or room temperature regards
will be just fine for me. Okay?
Regards are strange, 'cause you
can only really send them.
It's very hard to give them
in person.
You tell somebody, "Hey,
give him my regards."
And they can kind of be
the middleman
and pass the regards along.
You show up at a friend's house,
they open the door,
you're like, "Hey, regards."
"What the hell was that?"
"I'm regarding you."
"Don't do it, it's awkward.
I don't know
how to deal with this.
Please send them through
someone else in the future,
okay?"
I like buying shoes
because you go the store,
and they have those
little mirrors,
they have those
little slanted mirrors.
So funny, you know?
"How do those feel?"
"These feel good. I was just
wondering, do you have anything
that could show me what
they'll look like to dogs?"
"Uh, yes, we do. We have these
ridiculous small mirrors
all over the room, so...
Yeah, these."
"Oh, those are perfect,
yeah, 'cause I don't want to be
involved in the reflection,
I don't want my identity
linked to the shoes at all.
I just want new shoes
and severed shins,
just floating around the room,
like,
as if I'm four-fifths ghost
or something
would be perfect for me."
It's weird, 'cause, like,
when you buy gloves,
they don't have mirrors off
to the side where you're like,
"Oh, that's good. Just...
...the glove and my wrist.
That's all,
the forearm and the glove
is all I really needed there."
I saw a TV commercial
for a TV.
The basis of the commercial
was, "Look at how amazing
the picture is on this TV."
I looked at it and I was like,
"That looks remarkably
identical to the resolution
of my TV.
I think I'm good, thanks."
I like the term "sexual favor"
'cause it's
a really funny understatement.
You know?
"Anything else
I can do for you?"
"Uh, yeah. Just, um...
...if I could ask a favor."
"What, you need a ride
or something?"
"Yeah, kind of."
All right, I wanna get
something offstage now.
But I don't want there to be,
like, a dead space
in the middle of this special,
so...
I wonder if I, um...
if I use editing,
if I go from right here,
if I could suddenly appear
over there.
Cool, that worked. All right.
[laughs]
- They can't see me right now.
- [plays harmonica]
[cheering]
[playing harmonica]
[chuckles]
- [strums chord]
- All right.
- Yeah, that was...
- [cheering]
That was almost smooth.
It was so close. [laughs]
[plays guitar melody]
I love playing guitar.
I find it so relaxing.
I'm not great at it,
but, you know,
I still play
'cause I enjoy it.
I've tried to write songs,
but it's not my gift.
I wrote a protest song, but it
was an instrumental, so...
So very ineffective.
My friend called my other friend
a night owl,
and I was like, "You know,
owls are nocturnal.
You could probably just
call him an owl
and that would cover it."
I think it's cool that flash
mobs came and went so quickly
as a phenomenon.
I find that it's a lot less
creepy to ask a woman to dance
with you than for you.
What happened
with number one pencils?
I feel like they really blew it.
My friend's really good
at doing the robot.
I'm pretty good.
If you can imagine a robot
that's so technically advanced
that it moves exactly
like a regular human being...
...who's standing on the side
of the dance floor
being a judgmental asshole.
[plays harmonica]
Stuffed animals are cute...
...unless they once lived.
I wanna see a snake
eat spaghetti.
I saw that it was Shark Week.
So sharks get a week every year.
So black people get only
three more weeks than sharks
in this country.
That's messed up.
I know we're afraid of both,
but I don't think
that's appropriate.
[plays harmonica]
My friend has a beach body.
Kind of like a sea lion.
I wanna open an optical store.
I'll make the sign
really blurry.
I think the best form
of birth control
is correcting
other people's grammar.
Works every time.
I like that they came up
with the word "crafts."
'Cause I think art
and shitty art
just sounds too mean.
One restaurant that doesn't
deliver that should
is a food truck.
Just drive it to my house.
Come on, you're perfectly
equipped for this.
Taste buds sound like
they get along
really well with each other.
I think most people who describe
themselves as a people person
should maybe check with others
before they give
themself that title.
[plays harmonica]
One place I would not want
to be chased is Kenya.
I think my favorite thing
of all time ever,
of everything ever,
is exaggeration.
No, I'm sorry.
I like second guessing the best.
I prefer second guessing.
That's the best.
If I had a safe in my house,
the only thing I would
put in there is a note
that says,
"Nice try, asshole."
I feel like most people
are assholes
because if I see a group
of people and I go,
"Hey, asshole,"
they all turn and look.
Sometimes I'm worried
that I might be an asshole.
I feel like I'm a good person,
but, at the same time,
if I see somebody trip,
I feel like,
"Yeah." [laughs]
"Wasn't me. Awesome."
Fall is the only season
that has another name.
It's like that one had a sex
change or something, you know?
"Have you seen fall recently?"
"You mean autumn?"
That joke is not offensive.
Sometimes instead of saying
"for example,"
I'll say something such as,
"such as," for example.
I go to the gym religiously.
About twice a year
around the holidays.
[laugher, cheering]
All right.
I think Jesus was probably
one of the first scarecrows.
- [plays harmonica]
- [crowd gasping]
Thank you, harmonica.
I don't like
double-decker busses.
I think that's a bad idea.
There's a situation where you
can get in a car accident
and fall down the stairs
at the same time.
Way too dangerous.
If you're in a drum circle,
I wonder if there's a moment
where you're like,
"I'm never gonna be rich."
I think "balls" is a terrible
nickname for that part
of the male anatomy.
Balls?
That implies all these things
we don't want done to them.
You throw balls and you bounce
them and you kick 'em.
All bad. Terrible.
They should have named them
something better.
Mints.
"You okay?" "Yeah, yeah,
my lozenges just got grazed.
I'm fine."
When I was in high school,
I experimented sexually.
The experiment was to never
have sex with anybody,
no matter how hard I tried.
Success.
When you've having sex
with somebody, you can say,
"Yes" or "Yeah"
or "Uh-huh."
But for some reason,
you can't say "Yep."
"Oh, yep, baby. Ooh!
Yep. Yep, yep. Yep, yep!
Yep, yep, yep!
Indeed!"
[plays harmonica]
- [song ends]
- Thank you so much, everybody.
- Thank you.
- [cheering]
Thanks. Thank you.
[cheering]
[soft rock music plays]
[cheering, applause continues]
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com