("O Canada" playing)
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
Jim Gaffigan.
(cheers and applause)
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Oh, my gosh! Thank you, Canada.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you.
(cheering)
Oh. That...
That feels good.
You know, I don't wanna sound
like I'm pandering,
but I've been lucky enough
to perform throughout the world,
and I have to tell you,
the best audiences
are here in Canada.
They really are. (cheering)
They are.
And to be honest, to be honest.
I say that about every country
I perform in.
But it made you feel good.
That's why people lie.
'Cause lying works.
I've had so much fun touring
in Canada.
Last weekend, I was in
Saskatchewan.
Saskatchewan. That place is
filled with perverts.
(laughter)
They're all perverts!
The capital is Regina?
(laughter)
That's not necessary.
Regina. They could have
pronounced it Re-gene-a.
They did that on purpose,
'cause they're perverts.
Everything in Regina
sounds sexual.
Their football team,
the Rough Riders.
(laughter)
That's inappropriate.
I'm just relieved their mascot
wasn't a beaver.
You know what I mean?
It's not me, it's them.
They're perverts.
Regina is where the Mounties
are. Of course.
That's where they train
the Mounties to mount.
Every Mountie has to go
through Regina.
(laughter)
It's just... it's just
inappropriate, right?
Even the most innocent
thing said in Regina
comes across wrong.
Like, I can't ask like,
"Hey, where can a guy
eat out in Regina?"
(laughter)
You know?
I can't... That's them.
I'm a good Christin man...
trying to find out where a guy
can eat out in Regina.
Did you know the original name
of Regina
was Pile of Boners?
(laughter)
That's gross!
By the way, it's the whole
province.
Saskatchewan? That sounds
like an STD.
"My last boyfriend gave me
Saskatchewan."
"Really?"
"Yeah, now I have to take
all this penicillin."
Saskatchewan. You know,
it's cause of Saskatchewan
that moose antlers
are called a rack.
Now you can't even give a moose
a compliment,
like "Hey, nice rack!"
"No, lady, I was talking
about the moose."
"Well, then that lady should
know she looks like a moose."
(laughter)
I saw a moose. Have you seen...
I saw a moose in person.
I mean, or in moose.
I'm a person who saw a moose.
And I tell you, I don't feel
like I was ready.
I don't know how big I thought
a moose was gonna be,
but I was way off.
I was way off.
I was... It was huge.
And I feel like I should have
been warned
Like, someone should have
been like,
"You might see a moose.
Get ready."
But my friend was like,
"You might see a moose.
Have fun."
Like it was a butterfly
or something.
"You'll see a moose."
So I was, like, in shock
when I saw it.
I was like, "Wow! Whoa!
"Are they shooing
a Star Wars movie up here?
"How many people are in
that moose costume?
At lease three!"
(laughter)
It was huge. It was the size
of, like, a transformer.
It was gigantic.
And then my friend was like,
"Don't get close,
it'll kill ya."
What?
At that moment, I realized
my moose knowledge...
didn't exist.
I knew nothing about moose.
Like, my moose knowledge
comes from cartoons.
In cartoon, moose are like,
"Hey, now you doing?
Da-duh, da-duh, da-duh."
But in real life,
"I'm gonna kill you!"
How did that translate?
You never hear a moose in
those animal songs, right?
♪ The cow goes moo,
the cat goes meow ♪
♪ The moose goes "I'm gonna
stomp you to death!" ♪
(laughter)
Did you know that the plural
of moose is Reginas?
(laughter)
That surprised me.
Wasn't ready for that.
I performed in
Lethbridge, Alberta.
If you don't know anything about
Lethbridge, don't feel bad.
Neither do people in Lethbridge.
I asked them, I was like,
"Hey, what should I know
about Lethbridge?"
and they're like,
"I don't know."
Oh, my God.
"Is there anything I should
know about Lethbridge?"
"Mm...
Calgary's two hours away."
Is this, like, a temporary city?
Did everyone just show up
a month ago?
"We got, like, a bridge."
A lot of those western
Canadian cities
have a bridge that
they tell you about.
"We got the longest
land bridge over
the smallest body of water."
I don't know if you should
brag about that.
That-that sounds like a mistake.
An engineering error.
"We got a highway with no exit."
(laughter)
That might be on purpose. Yeah.
Kitchner. Kitchner.
Schnitzel.
Kitchner, or, as I refer to it,
Berlin.
'Cause Kitchner's very
German, right?
Any Germans here?
(low cheering) Yeah?
That's about the extent
of German pride.
It helps that we're in the dark.
"I don't want to lose my job."
It's worldwide.
I was in Vienna, Austria,
and they were, like, insistent
that they were not German.
"We're not German.
We're not German.
"We're totally different.
"I mean, we speak German
and-and, you know...
"our culture's German
but, you know...
"in every war we've fought
with Germany but...
we're not German."
I almost believe you.
That's sad.
But I stated my Canadian tour
in the Maritimes.
I started in Halifax.
(cheering) Halifax.
The first thing I did is
I ate a donair.
(cheering)
And the second thing I did was
have explosive diarrhea.
(laughter)
I should have known something
bad was coming.
When I walked in,
the guy was like,
"You don't even look drunk."
(laughter)
I'm not.
"Here you go."
Did you know that donair was
started by a Turkish immigrant
who moved to Halifax
and wanted to open
a toilet paper company.
(laughter)
It's really a beautiful,
Canadian story.
Really.
Those donairs are amazing.
You know, that...
that spicy meat
with that sweet sauce
which I'm almost positive
is just melted ice cream.
"I'll have a donair.
Make it cookies and cream."
That donair meat.
I still can't find out
what it is.
It's like ♪ You know Dancer
and Prancer ♪
♪ And donair and Blitzen ♪
♪ But do you recall ♪
♪ The most tasty
diarrhea-causing meat of all ♪
♪ It's the donair ♪
I'm convinced that the donair
was just created
so we can digest poutine.
Right?
Some guy went, "I had poutine
a month ago."
The doctor's like, "I'm gonna
prescribe you a donair."
(laughter)
"Is that gonna work?"
"I'm also gonna give you
a prescription for a diaper.
"Very important you put
the diaper on
before you eat the donair."
Poutine. Oh, my gosh, poutine.
At this point, are there any
Canadian restaurants
that don't serve poutine?
I picked one up at...
what was it?
It was a Booster Juice.
(laughter)
"Yeah, I'll have the kale
poutine smoothie."
(laughter)
It was delicious!
Poutine, I know some of you
pronounce it "pou-ten,"
but you're still saying "poo."
(laughter)
I love poutine.
And I eat unhealthy,
and some would say,
I've built a career out of
eating unhealthy.
But, you know, poutine?
It's a little irresponsible.
I mean, after all,
I don't wanna die.
(laughter)
It's almost very...
Someone was just tying to make
French fries more unhealthy.
"What if we cover it with
everything
that causes heart disease?"
(laughter)
"Let's do it.
We have free health care."
(laughter, applause)
In Edmonton, I had
perogie poutine.
Yeah, yeah, I had to sign
a waiver and everything.
(chuckles)
The first food I had to provide
an emergency contact for.
It was delicious, but do we need
perogie poutine?
Has anyone ever eaten poutine
and be like,
"You know what this needs?
Carbs."
(laughter)
Poutine.
Fascinating. It started
in Quebec, right?
And now it's everywhere
in Canada.
But you know there was probably
a part of Canada
that was like, "Wait a minute.
"As a country, we're going
with the French fry thing?
"Not salmon, or beaver tail?
I guess that's better
than syrup."
Did you know that poutine in
French means Vladimir Putin?
(laughter)
I'm just saying.
I love how poutine is different
in different provinces.
Like, in Ottawa, there's
the squeaky cheese
that goes on the poutine, right?
There's the squeaky cheese.
The first time I performed
in Ottawa,
it was in April during
a poutine fest,
and I learned later on it was
the second poutine fest
of the year.
(laughter)
Which means sometime in January
or February
someone was at a poutine fest
and was like,
"Why don't we do this
next month?"
(laughter)
If it happens every month,
that's not a festival.
That's a habit.
Last time I was in Ottawa
was during Winterlude.
(cheering) Winterlude.
Of course a very...
It's an outdoor festival...
in February!
Okay.
You know, in America, when
there's horrible weather,
we-we cancel events.
You guys kinda plan around 'em.
"Hey, you know how it's
the coldest month of the year?
What if we had a party outside?"
(laughter)
"Uh, why would we do that?"
"It could be like an interlude
between the poutine fests."
(laughter)
I have to admit,
I'm a little disappointed
by the number of
Tim Hortons in town.
(laughter)
There's some. But you go to
some cities in Canada,
and the number of Tim Hortons
is uncomfortable.
Like, you drive by
the fifth one and you're like,
"Uh, is this a Tim Hortons
theme park?"
(laughter)
"Are we sure they're only
selling coffee and doughnuts?"
Canadians, you guys are
always like,
"That's our Dunkin' Donuts.
That's our Dunkin 'Donuts."
Yeah, in America, we don't
have Dunkin' Donuts
on every block.
Tim Hortons is like America's
stop sign.
(laughter, applause)
Now-now I've seen some
Tim Hortons in America,
and whenever I see
a Tim Hortons in America,
I always have this same thought:
Don't force your culture on us.
(laughter) Yeah.
(applause)
But you wouldn't know
how that feels!
Last week, I went to
a Canadian tire store.
I don't wanna brag, uh...
I was kinda surprised
to find out
they sell more than tires.
I don't know why I would think
they'd only sell tires.
It's not like the store's
called Canadian Tire.
How important are tires
to you people?
(laughter)
"You know people love
shopping for tires?
"We lure them in with the tires.
And then boom,
we sell 'em a blender."
(laughter)
Nobody in Canada even
sounds like that guy.
Of course there are differences
between Canada and America.
It's not just health care
and bacon.
Your airport codes
make no sense.
And I love how you're
so proud of them.
"YW-pound sign representing!
Yeah!
We're YW-pound sign!"
It's weird. Toronto: YYZ.
I don't know why.
"Well, it makes sense.
'Y' is, you know, why not.
"And then 'Y", the second 'Y',
is why are you askin'.
And the the Z is like...
zzzzz you later."
"This guy's a jerk."
Of course, Canada's the home of
the Caesar cocktail.
The Caesar cocktail.
You're very proud of that.
The Caesar is kinda like
a Bloody Mary
but with clam juice
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Mmm, mmm!
Clam juice, wow.
I didn't know that was
an ingredient.
Or a liquid.
"You know that thing
from the ocean
"that looks like a snot?
What if we made it into
a juice?"
"Think about it.
"Say you just went joggin',
all right?
"You're parched, you're thirsty.
"I hand you a tall glass
of clam juice.
"You chug it. Glup, glup, glup.
And then we're ready
to go to the club."
"He has never met
a Canadian before."
(laughs)
It has nothing to do...
The Caesar was created
in Calgary,
landlocked Calgary,
which has the finest clams.
(laughter)
I just love how you guys,
how Canadians...
like, complain about
the Bloody Mary.
You're like, "Oh,
the Bloody Mary..."
(gagging)
"Oh, that's so disgusting!
That drink that doesn't have
clam juice in it?"
(gagging)
"The clam... Oh!"
We're having an election
in America,
so there's bound to be
some Americans
that threaten to move to Canada.
"If that person gets elected,
I'm moving to Canada."
I don't remember Canada
extending an invitation.
(laughter) It's like...
(applause)
And I've been coming
to Canada for years.
Been recruited zero times.
You know? No one's ever gone,
"Hey, you live in the States?
"You ever thought about
making a move?
How you feel about clam juice?"
"He better stop with
the clam jokes.
It's getting too much."
In my hotel, there is a youth
hockey team staying there.
There is a youth hockey team
staying in every Canadian hotel.
(laughter)
(applause)
Are they allowed to go home?
How long are these tournaments?
Every hotel!
Every time I'm in an elevator
in a Canadian hotel,
I feel like someone's in
the other room, like,
"Send in the kids with the
smelly hockey bags."
(laughter)
"There's not enough room."
"Just do it. Just do it.
Tell him we'll give him
clam juice."
"That better be the last
clam juice joke."
(laughter)
But of course,
the youth hockey league,
that's all about the Canadian
hockey dream, right?
You know, parents drive their
children all around Canada
because there's the dream
that maybe their child
might be just, by chance,
maybe the next Wayne Gretzky,
right?
And I'm here to tell you,
probably not.
(laughter)
There's only one Great One,
and I think he lives in Phoenix.
(laughter)
Let's kill him.
I remember the first time
I came to Canada.
The big difference I noticed
was that, uh,
things are measured differently.
Temperature and distance.
I remember at the time
being like,
"Well, that's annoying."
And then eventually I realized
it wasn't just Canada,
it was the entire world...
(laughter)
that uses the metric system...
except for us!
And I tell you, it was strange,
as an American,
to realize every other country
on the planet...
was wrong.
Right?
And you should change for us.
'Cause we all know that God
loves America more.
And that love is measured
in feet.
(laughter)
So here's how I can tell.
The way American's measure
things is annoying.
Because occasionally you'll
run into a British person
who will announce their
weight in stones.
(British accent)
"I'm only 12 stone."
(regular voice) "I'm sorry,
are you a caveman."
(English accent, indistinct)
How do the English say "stone"
with a straight face?
How do you condescend
to the entire world
when you're weighing yourself
in boulders?
"We're going to leave the EU
and return to our
pebble economy."
(laughter)
I do love doing
international shows.
It's different with Trump
as president.
I know you guys are
all fans of his, but...
No, it's different with Trump
as president.
It's kinda like having a parent
that's an alcoholic.
Show up in a country like,
"Sorry about my dad."
(laughter)
"We don't know what
to do about it."
(applause)
"Trying to get the phone
from him.
Proving harder than we thought."
I find Canadians are the least
phased by Trump.
Because, you know,
within the world,
you know, it's like...
'cause Canadians,
you know, Trump is just an
exaggeration
of the American stereotype.
Americans are known as
obnoxious.
Trump is just
turning up the dial, right?
That's the American stereotype,
obnoxious.
The Canadian stereotype? Polite.
Which is not a stereotype,
it's a compliment.
But you guys still get angry.
"We're not polite,
we're passive-aggressive."
(laughter)
But what you don't realize,
to an American,
passive-aggressive is polite.
But everything about Canada
is pleasant.
Even the Canadian flag.
Most national flags have
all these macho symbols,
like, Mexico's an eagle
eating a snake,
American's the stars and
stripes,
and Canada's is like,
"Just put a leaf up there."
(laughter)
"One for every province?"
"No, just one maple leaf."
As a result,
everyone likes Canadians.
Everyone likes Canadians,
you know?
Not liking Canadians is an
indication of a mental problem.
(laughter)
"I don't like Canadians
or puppies."
Remember when China was mad
at Canada?
The whole world was like,
"Come on, China."
(laughter)
"That's a red flag.
"Put the star in the middle."
"How many flag jokes?"
I do feel like the map of Canada
looks unfinished.
It's so detailed on
the east coast,
and then it's just
wide open spaces.
It's almost like someone was
working on it
and they fell asleep.
And his boss comes over,
"Are you done?"
"What? Huh?
"Uh, yeah, I just gotta put
some names in the...
"Prince Edward Island,
Nova Scotia.
So much land."
(laughter)
"New-found-land."
The boss is like,
"Are you done?"
"Uh, yeah, yeah, I'm done.
"I'm done, I'm done.
Colombia."
"That's a country already."
"Uh, British Columbia."
I've been to British Columbia.
It's not very British
or Columbian.
(laughter)
Vancouver was like a rainy
Seattle.
Spent a week in Vancouver.
Somehow it rained for two weeks.
(laughter)
Boy, you guys had fun naming
things Vancouver
out there in British Columbia.
Vancouver Island,
Vancouver City,
which is not on
Vancouver Island,
North Vancouver, West Vancouver,
South Vancouver.
Washington State, you can
have a Vancouver.
Everyone gets a Vancouver,
Everyone gets one.
It does appear you guys
struggled
with naming things a little bit.
Like Regina.
Moose Jaw.
Do you want people to
go to these places?
Then, of course, there's the
Saint John-St. John's fiasco.
(laughter, applause)
Saint John, New Brunswick,
and then right next to it...
St. John's, Newfoundland.
I'm saying this like
you don't know.
We know!
We live there! We know!
It never came up?
Nobody took a boat from
one place to the other?
"Hey, that other place has
the same name as this place."
Nobody confronted Newfoundland?
Like, "Hey, Newfoundland!
"Saint John, New Brunswick, is
the oldest city in Canada,
so don't use that name."
And Newfoundland said,
"Okay, okay.
Oh, shoot."
"What happened?"
"Nothing. (mumbles)
"Our capital is St. John's."
"That's the same name."
"No, no, it's different.
"You spell out Saint and ours
is just St.,
so it could stand for street."
"Does yours stand for street?"
"No, it stands for saint."
"But ours ends with
and apostrophe S,
"so it's possessive.
"So when St. John comes back,
he's gonna go,
'Where do I go?'"
He's gonna go to the Virgin
Islands. Who are we kidding?
I think it's fascinating
that there's a part of Canada
called the Northwest
Territories... still...
today.
I wasn't looking at a map
from the 1600s
or watching an episode
of "Deadwood."
Name your country!
(laughs) Northwest...
There are people that live
there.
What kind of civic pride...
"Well, where we're from in
the Northwest Territories,
"or as we call ourselves
the Northwest Terratorians.
Go terra."
How dismissive!
How...
Like the Northwest Territories,
"Can we be a province?"
"No!
You may not!"
"How about a territory
or a yard?
How about Northwest
Storage Area?"
The Northwest Territories
are smaller,
'cause in the '90s,
the Inuit people were like,
"We'd like our own territories."
And the Canadian government
was like,
"Oh, we didn't even know
people live there."
"Sure, sure. What do you want
your territories to be called?"
"Uh, none of it."
"Are you gonna tell them or..."
"It's a great name.
"Great name.
None of it. Love it.
"Uh, sorry for stealing
all the land.
Anyway, we got a hockey game
we're watching, so..."
I think it's strange...
Canada, it starts off...
The further east you go,
the crazier it gets.
Like, Newfoundland is like
bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa.
Newfoundland is, like,
the crazy uncle
that you don't introduce
to friends...
until you've known them
for a long time.
"I don't want them
to think I'm like them."
Everything is crazy
in Newfoundland. Everything.
It's like, "Newfoundland,
do you wanna be in the same
time zone as the Maritimes?"
"We'll go a half hour earlier."
Uh...
"Worldwide, time zones are
done by the hour."
"We'll go half hour."
"Okay. Okay. Just final
housekeeping here. Um...
Is Newfoundland three words
or two words?"
"One word."
"Thank you very much.
Thank you."
Cause it's... Canada starts
off pretty normal
on the west coast.
British Columbia, you know,
it's like,
beautiful, natural resources,
they shoot TV shows
and movies there.
That's like your California,
right?
And then there's...
There Alberta,
where it's like oil and cowboys.
That's like your Texas.
And then there's Saskatchewan,
which we have established
are all perverts.
Looks like I'm not performing
in Saskatchewan again.
And then there's...
Then there's Manitoba.
Manitoba's like that friend
you invite last to the party.
And only 'cause you forgot
they existed.
(laughter)
Canada picks on Winnipeg, right?
That was kind of a big...
I remember I was in Toronto,
and I was going to Winnipeg
and it was my first show there,
and everyone in Toronto
was like,
"Oh, bring a...
Bring a coat! Ha ha!
"Winnipeg! (laughs)
Hope you like cold weather!
(laughs)"
Uh, I'm not sleeping outside.
Then I got to Winnipeg
and I was like,
they're right, they're right.
They nailed it.
I went to Winnipeg in February.
(audience groans)
That's when you wanna go.
It was 50 below!
50! By the way, at that point,
it doesn't matter if it's
Celsius or Fahrenheit.
It's kind of like hell.
It's just bad.
And you forget how cold it is,
and then you step outside
and you're like, "Oh!"
And that's why your national
anthem starts that way.
It's like, "Oh! Canada!"
(applause)
I'm convinced half of you
don't know the rest of the words.
♪ O Canada ♪
♪ The pipes, the pipes
are calling ♪
(mumbled singing)
People were so nice in Winnipeg.
It was freezing, and they kept
apologizing for the weather.
They were like, "Sorry it's so
cold. Sorry it's so cold."
I'm like, I'm almost positive
it's not your fault.
(laughter)
But they kept apologizing.
"Sorry about the weather."
Eventually I was like,
"Did you not pay a bill
of something?"
(laughter)
"Weather work different
up here?"
I was in Winnipeg for two days.
I kept running into people
from the Philippines.
I learned later on a lot
of people from the Philippines
have immigrated to Winnipeg.
I know nothing about
the Philippines
except that it's a tropical
paradise...
which Winnipeg is not.
Which brings up the question,
how bad are things
in the Philippines?
You're moving to Winnipeg!
"You really wanna move?"
"I gotta get out of here!"
"Would you move to a place
where you can't go outside?"
"I'll go."
"All right, grab your
flip-flops, let's go."
I can say that joke 'cause
I'm from the Philippines.
(laughter)
Manitoba, then you go east,
and then there's Ontario, right?
(cheering) Ontario.
There's that province pride.
Ontario. And then there's
Quebec.
Ontario and Quebec.
Those are like the two brothers
that run the family business...
after the parents died.
But they had different mothers.
(laughter)
Right?
(applause)
Ontario's like,
"I'll handle this."
Quebec is like,
"You are so idiot."
(laughter)
Quebec is just so fascinating.
Canada's slightly different,
slightly different,
then it gets to Quebec
and it's like...
different language!
What?!
Six million French-speaking...
It's a French-speaking province!
Or a Francophone!
"Are you Francophone
or Anglophone?"
Like they're competing
cellular companies.
"Are you on the Francophone
family plan?"
"I'm thinking of switching
to the Anglophone."
That's gotta be hard
for the Quebecois, right?
You know, they're Canadian,
which, by definition,
is almost polite,
but they're also French.
(laughter)
Talk about a contradiction.
(French accent) "I want to
apologize for everything,
but I'm better than everyone."
(laughter)
"I am sorry you're so dumb."
I spent some time in Quebec.
I love Quebec.
My favorite part of
the Quebecois culture
is the curse words.
The curse words in Quebec
are just
Catholic objects in French.
(speaking mock French)
They're just saying nouns.
"You're a chair."
"Well, then you're a table."
"Fellas, fellas, there's
children present."
East of Quebec is, uh,
New Brunswick, right?
New Brunswick and the Maritimes,
that's the home of
the Acadians, right?
The Acadians. Those noble,
brave people
that the English kicked out
during the Great Expulsion.
They kicked them out of
the Maritimes,
and they sent some of them
to Louisiana,
and some of them to
the West Indies.
And a brave amount, a few,
fought their way back
to return to the coldest place
on Earth.
There's like a million French
speakers in New Brunswick.
So there's-there's...
One in five Canadians
speaks French.
So there was this great
compromise
where the English speakers
agreed to take French in school,
and the French speakers agreed
to continue speaking French.
(laughter)
Of course, there are Canadians
who speak English and French,
and they're called
flight attendants.
(laughter)
Whenever I'm on
an Air Canada flight,
I'm always like, oh, good.
Now I can ignore the same
message twice.
"Jim, you're a jerk."
I suppose the most famous
Canadian right now is Drake.
Right? I saw Drake in concert
a couple months ago.
I bet you wouldn't even think
I would be friends with Drake.
But guess what? I'm not.
(laughter)
But I did see Drake in concert.
I had two shows in Las Vegas
in the same night,
and after the second show,
the promoter came up to me
and he goes,
"Hey, Jim, Drake is doing
a special show
"here in a nightclub in
the casino.
Would you like to go
and feel uncomfortable?"
(laughter)
And I just finished
my second show.
It was like 11:30,
and I was like,
"You know what?
I wanna go. I wanna go.
"I might not be a Drake expert,
"but I have friends that
like Drake.
"Well, my six-year-old
Patrick likes Drake.
So I wanna impress Patrick."
So the promoter took Ted and I,
and he escorted is through
the casino to the nightclub
where all these Drake fans were
waiting to go in.
They all look at me like,
"Oh, my gosh.
There's Drake's accountant."
(laughter)
Brought us in the club
and set us up at a table,
and they got us drinks
and everything.
They're like, "Do you need
anything else?"
And I was like, "When does
Drake go on?"
And they're like "2:30."
And I was like, "Cool.
Can I get a wake-up call?"
(laughter)
'Cause it was probably midnight
at this point.
So I had to decide. Do I wait
two and a half hours
to see one of the biggest
musicians of today?
Who I, personally,
knew one of his songs.
Or do I go back to
my room and sleep?
And I just figured,
God's plan, right?
God's plan.
So I spent the next
two and a half hours
hanging around these
drunk Drake fans,
trying to stay awake.
After an hour, I realized
Drake is just a combination
of the words "drunk"
and "awake." Drake.
(laughter)
2:30 finally came. No Drake.
Around 2:45, I was like,
"Did Drake pick up a shift
at Tim Hortons?"
(laughter)
Drake finally went on
at 3:00 A.M.
I don't know. Maybe he slept in.
3:00 A.M.!
You know, if you're even out
at 3:00 A.M.,
you've made a couple
bad decisions.
That's when Drake starts work!
And I work at night. I like
working at night.
And generally, the later
a job starts,
the more appealing.
But 3:00 A.M.?
Drake might as well be hosting
the "Today Show."
He could fill in for
Savannah Guthrie.
Drake did an hour show.
He performed from 3:00 to 4:00.
I learned later on he was
paid $2 million
for that one hour of work.
So we make the same.
(laughter)
The show ended at 4:00,
and I started walking
back to my room.
4:00 A.M. in Vegas,
which is 7:00 A.M. here on
the East Coast,
and I live in New York,
so it's like 7:00 A.M.
in New York,
and 9:13 in Newfoundland.
(laughter)
But I was walking back,
and I was like,
it's 7:00 A.M., I should
just call home.
So I called him,
my wife answered,
and she was like, "What are
you doing awake?"
and I'm like, "It's a long
story.
"Is Patrick," our six-ear-old,
"is he awake?"
And she put Patrick on the
phone, and I'm like,
"Patrick, you're not gonna
believe
who I just saw in concert.
I saw Drake."
And Patrick said, "Who's Drake?"
(laughter)
So, it was worth it.
It was totally worth it.
(laughter, applause)
All right, that is all for me.
Thank you so much for coming.
(cheers and applause)
(music)
John: It's great to be here
in New Brunswick.
I can connect with my
Acadian roots.
My Acadian roots.
Today I had poutine rapee.
I had some putine rappee.
And, uh...
Uh, it was, uh, you know,
it tasted a little bit like
there was a flavor expulsion,
too.
Um...
Oh.
No, I have not eaten many
mashed potato baseballs.
Um...
But, uh...
That was my least favorite
of them.
Um...
But it is so fascinating.
The Acadian culture.
Such a proud, interesting
tradition.
You know, I also...
I tried some dulse.
Some dulse, which was...
That was great chewing tobacco.
And I was like, oh, this is
probably
gonna taste like seaweed.
And it was worse.
"This guy's just... He's a jerk."
Bumpton's a great city.
When I was in Saint John
yesterday,
I saw the Reversing Falls.
I was like "Wow." I mean, I...
You know, I don't know...
I mean, I wasn't expecting much.
You know what I mean?
I wasn't expecting that
movie "Avatar."
But I didn't think it would be
less impressive than
a toilet flushing.
"This guy is a jerk!"
"He's a jerk who's done
research."
I was invited to go sliding,
which was exciting.
I turned them down because
I'm an adult.
And, uh, I call it sledding.
Sliding, for me, is something
you do on accident.
Or what a drunk person
would call sledding.
"Do you wanna go sliding?
Slipping. You wanna get
injured?"
Do you wanna get injured?"
You guys call sliding...
You call sledding sliding,
but you slide on a sled.
But you sled on a skidoo.
All right. Okay. Sure.
Sure. And the Americans
are weird. Okay.
(laughs)
(rock version of "O Canada"
playing)
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org