Subtitle By: MARSH-MARIE
[male announcer over speaker]
Philippines...
are you ready?
[Jo Koy's opening song playing]
[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Jo Koy!
[Jo Koy's opening song continues to play]
[Jo] Hey.
Yes!
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Man, this is amazing, you guys.
I'm so damn excited. I don't even know
how to express how excited I am.
I'm sorry if I keep repeating myself,
but that's genuinely how I feel.
I'm so excited.
This is the highlight of my career, man.
I swear to God.
Everyone has bucket lists.
This is my bucket list moment right here.
I brought Netflix to the Philippines, man.
Are you kidding me?
It's a beautiful moment 'cause tonight
I'm going to show you my history
while we make history.
We're gonna showcase Filipino culture
to the world tonight, you guys.
That's what we're gonna do.
We're representing the Philippines
to the world.
I'm gonna show you music,
performers, food.
Every element of this show is Filipino.
Everyone... Look.
Everyone inside here is Filipino.
This casino's owned by a Filipino.
This fucking cameraman is a Filipino.
And I just found out that we're related.
That's also my uncle. He's my uncle.
I'm gonna ask the world right now,
have you ever met a Filipino?
If you've been to a hospital,
then the answer is yes.
Every nurse can sing,
every nurse can dance,
and there's always one comedian
in the emergency room.
That's what Filipinos do.
They sing, they dance, and they laugh.
[crowd cheers]
And they take your blood pressure.
And if you're sitting at home,
and you're watching this,
you're gonna love this show
because we're gonna give you
an all-expense-paid, first-class ticket
to the Philippines,
and Netflix is paying for it.
[crowd cheers]
Here's a fun fact for you.
I know a lot of people don't know this,
but the Philippines is separated
by 7,000 islands.
Seven thousand islands.
And they speak about 187 languages.
One hundred and eighty-seven languages!
-Did you get that in your head?
-[crowd] Yes!
But there's one language
you all speak fluently.
Karaoke. And that's fucking Japanese!
So I guess it's 188 languages.
Entertainment is in our blood.
My sister sang and I danced.
I know what you guys are thinking.
"You danced?"
Yes, I used to dance.
I'm an OG B-boy from the '80s, man.
[crowd cheers]
I still remember back in the day when
I used to do the moonwalk at talent shows.
And when my mom found out
I could impersonate Michael Jackson,
it was the best day
and the worst day of my life.
[crowd laughs]
Best day, because my mom was like,
[Filipino accent] "Oh! You have talent."
It was the worst day
'cause my mom was like,
[Filipino accent] "Oh! You have talent."
[crowd laughs]
And when she found out
I could dance like Michael Jackson,
she made me do it
every time someone came to the house.
Every time.
It didn't matter who was at the house.
[Filipino accent] "Your auntie is here.
Do the Michael Jackson.
[crowd laughs and cheers]
Joseph, your uncle is here.
Do the Michael Jackson.
And not just one time like that, oh.
[crowd laughs and cheers]
Joseph, my friends from work are here.
Do the Michael Jackson one time, Joseph."
She made me do Michael Jackson
my whole life
and then it just got to the point
where I was done.
I'm not gonna do the Michael Jackson
anymore.
I remember that day.
[Filipino accent] "My coworkers are here.
Do the Michael Jackson for me, Joseph."
I was like, "No, I'm not doing it.
I'm done. No more.
Stop telling people I can do that."
[Filipino accent]
"But I told all my coworkers and...
Look, they're waiting. Just...
[crowd laughs and cheers]
Come on, Joseph. Just do like-- Come on.
Just one, Joseph."
"No, Mom. Stop telling people I can do
Michael Jackson. I'm not doing it anymore.
I'm done. I'm not gonna do it."
[Filipino accent] "I told my coworkers.
That's why they're here.
They want you to do the Michael Jackson,
and you're not going to do it?
That's embarrassing me.
Why don't you want to do
the Michael Jackson?
Tell me why. Huh. Why?
Tell me why you don't want to do
the Michael Jackson, Joseph. Why?"
And I was like,"'Cause I'm 33."
And she was like, "Then move out."
I was like, "Fuck that."
[imitates
Michael Jackson's "Billy Jean"]
This is amazing, man.
This is what I love about this show,
you guys.
I get to bring some of my friends,
my Filipino friends
that are killing it in the business
back to Manila
to see where it all started.
This next dude I'm bringing up
is one of the best break-dancers
in the world, man.
He's representing the United States
in the Olympics, Paris, France,
in break-dancing.
Check this out.
[crowd cheers]
What's up, y'all?
We're here in The Tenement,
and I'm feeling really blessed
and honored to be here.
You know the locals don't have much here,
but what they do have
is the love for dance.
And this is a big part
of the Filipino culture,
and I'm gonna get the opportunity
to teach a masterclass here.
[electricity shorts]
[Ronnie] Music!
We do it one time all together.
[woman] All right. Are you ready?
Here we go.
[upbeat break dancing music playing]
I'm gonna watch this one.
Five, six, seven, eight. Go.
Wah.
Ba, ha.
Ah.
Ah. Ah.
Six, eight. And boom, boom, ba.
Four.
Eight.
Two. Nice.
-[Ronnie] All right.
-This is what it's all about. Right here.
[Jo] I've known Ronnie 20 years.
Two kids in Vegas and now look at us.
Yes. It's kind of like a clumsy run.
Instead of running this way,
you're running this way.
One more time. Let's do it.
[upbeat break dancing music
continues to play]
[Ronnie] Yeah! Ha-ha!
Let's take a little break.
[upbeat music playing]
[Ronnie] Just giving feedback,
just think about all the moves you do
as a picture.
That's how you know if you're clean.
When people rush their moves,
you don't see what they're doing.
You think you're hitting it, but,
you know, when you start getting tired,
you're not exaggerating these movements,
so when I'm saying double knee boom...
grab your head.
Grab your chest. Foot. Foot.
So pay attention to those details,
'cause that's what makes
these moments count.
I feel privileged and honored to be here.
You guys learn fast, you guys pick it up,
and you guys have that style,
which is dope.
Filipino B-boys, we're all about style,
right, and intricacy.
And having original moves.
And I can see that in every single
one of you guys. Shit's tight.
Props.
Hats off to you guys.
You guys killed it.
[Jo] About to see some real cypher.
This is a real cypher.
They're all coming out running.
This is how they claim it.
This is how you get your name
in the B-boy world,
coming after someone like Ronnie.
Watch this.
[Ronnie] Get that shit.
Killed it, bro. Killed it.
-I’m B-boy representing Paranaque
-Okay.
[man] I live here in the Philippines.
I’m a poor B-boy. I live in a jeepney.
-I also teach the kids to not use drugs.
-Yeah.
-I teach the kids to change their lives.
That's amazing, man.
-I got you, bro.
-I'm a B-boy representing Paranaque.
[upbeat break-dancing music playing]
[Ronnie] Woo-hoo! Smooth.
[Ronnie] Get it, Mouse.
This is real fucking B-boy shit
right here.
[Jo] Hey, let's go!
[Jo] Whoa. Oh, my God.
[Ronnie] Yeah!
-It's real, yo.
-That's what I'm talking about.
This is unexpected. I did not expect
that many dancers to show up.
It was crazy.
Some of them were actually from the city
where my family's from. From Iloilo.
From Pangasinan.
It's humbling to know that they came
all the way out here for this workshop.
You weren't expecting that?
-Not at all.
-They were amazing.
And they were killing it.
My favorite story from the cypher
is this one B-boy came out,
and he was like, "I live in a jeepney,
but this is what I do.
I B-boy. I teach kids to B-boy
and keep them off drugs.
And now I'm battling Ronnie."
[Jo] Like, he's seen you on YouTube
and that inspires him to try
and get other kids to stay off drugs
and dance. That's deep.
-Humbling.
-[Jo] It's what you do.
I mean...
I have family that lives in Tenement.
-And I've visited them.
-[Jo] Yeah.
And to be here, it's like...
-I know.
-This is where we're from, man.
-This is our bloodline.
-Yeah. 100%.
It's humbling.
It's a big honor to be here.
Look at this environment.
-This will humble you.
-Yep.
This goes to show you can do anything.
No matter what your situation is,
you can do it.
[crowd cheers and claps]
[same upbeat break-dancing song plays]
[Jo] Yes!
Are you kidding me?
Right there, that's Ronnie.
I want everyone to know
I've known Ronnie since he was 17.
I used to book comedy shows,
and he used to perform at my comedy shows.
So it's just fucking crazy
that two Filipinos from 20 years ago
are now doing the same thing
that they love to do
right here in the motherland,
in the Philippines, man.
How crazy is that?
This is what's even more crazy.
That we were in The Tenement
and these kids actually knew Ronnie
from the Internet.
These kids that live in The Tenement
can go on YouTube
and find another Filipino B-boy
from across the world
and, next thing you know, they're dancing
together. That shit is beautiful to me.
You couldn't do that when I was a kid.
I couldn't go online in 1989. Are you
kidding? You know how hard it was for me?
Do you know how hard it was for me
to find another Filipino comic in 1989
without the Internet?
Do you know how hard it was for me
to just find another Filipino in 1989?
It was hard.
That's why I wore the Filipino flag
on my chest when I did The Tonight Show.
People ask me, "Why did you wear that flag
on your chest on the The Tonight Show?"
Because I wanted other Filipino kids
that wanted to be a comic
to be inspired
when they saw me that night.
If they saw me that night, they would be
like, "Yo, I can do that, too."
That's the only reason
why I wore it that night.
Actually, there is one other reason
Because the night after
I taped The Tonight Show, the day after,
there was a journeyman fighter,
a Filipino journeyman fighter
by the name of Manny Pacquiao...
He was fighting Antonio Barrera.
This guy was knocking everybody out.
There was no way Manny
could have won that fight. No way.
If you had bet the house on Manny
that night,
you'd still be spending that money today.
He wasn't supposed to win.
And the whole world watched.
And I couldn't wait to watch.
I was like, "Yes, finally, there's gonna
be a Filipino at the top of his game
getting ready to represent the Filipinos."
I couldn't wait. Everyone was watching it.
Hundreds of millions of people
watched that fight.
And then he won.
He fucking won.
[crowd cheering and clapping]
He won.
And I remember just watching it,
like, "Oh, my God, he won."
It was amazing.
'Cause I knew that was the day...
that hundreds of millions of people...
were gonna hear
the thickest Filipino accent ever.
It was so fucking thick.
It was the thickest Filipino accent,
and I was so happy.
I was like,
"That's my fucking accent right there."
I remember that interview
like it was yesterday.
They were like, "So, Manny,
how did you prepare to fight Barrera?"
[Filipino accent] He was like,
"Well, you know, the...
When he was, you know...
He punched like that
and he went like that, I go like that.
And then he hit me.
I look at him, I punch him back.
He goes like that and then he...
he, uh...
he... you know, he...
he, uh... Jesus Christ.
But I will say this, man.
I was proud of Manny.
Because he spoke English.
And I'm not trying to be funny.
That was the first time
the world got to see a Filipino accent,
and I was proud of Manny that day.
And no disrespect to Antonio Barrera,
no matter how many times
he won the championship,
he always spoke Spanish.
He's supposed to 'cause he's Mexican.
But that night, Manny said,
"I'm speaking English."
I fucking applaud him for that.
That's amazing.
That was his moment,
and he knew he shocked the fucking world.
[Filipino accent] "I'm going to talk
the best I can
to let everybody know who the fuck I am."
And that's what he did.
[crowd laughs and cheers]
I remember HBO Sports
gave him an interpreter.
[crowd laughs]
That's the truth.
Look at that. Look back.
They gave him an interpreter.
I remember when Manny Pacquiao
was done talking, they went,
"Thank you so much, Manny."
Then they went to the interpreter
and went, "What did he say?"
And the interpreter was like,
"He's speaking English!
[crowd laughs]
You don't understand
what the fuck he's saying?
Everything he's saying, I'm saying it,
too. You don't understand that?
You don't understand "Jesus Christ"?
Really? This motherfucker is crazy!
Son of a shit, you. Fuck you, huh."
Nowadays,
there are a lot more opportunities
for Filipino-American comics
to get on stage and perform.
But a lot of them
haven't come back to the motherland.
Check this out.
[upbeat hip-hop beats playing]
We've been here for two hours.
I kind of just feel like
either, A, they forgot about us
or, B, we're in the wrong city.
Oh, man. My stomach's hurting.
[Andrew] Oh, is that a jeepney?
No way. Oh, shoot!
[Joey and Andrew] Oh!
[Joey] Oh, shoot!
[Andrew] Yes!
-[Joey] You picked us up in a jeepney?
-[Andrew] What?
-[Andrew] You roll up in a jeepney, dawg?
-[Joey] This is amazing.
-[Jo] This is how we pick you up.
-Stretch. Happy Philippines.
-First time?
-[Andrew] First time.
Let's get your bags. Let's go.
Leave the bags.
We've got a jeepney to catch.
Now I believe I'm in the Philippines.
[upbeat dance music playing]
I've heard about a jeepney my entire life
and now I'm in one.
Let me tell you
how resourceful Filipinos are.
A jeepney is exactly what it is. When
the Americans left, they left their jeeps.
The Filipinos were like, [Filipino accent]
"Let's turn this into some type
of transportation...
and make a business."
[Jo] And that's why it's a jeepney.
-[Jo] They're the OG Uber.
-[Joey] Yeah.
-[Jo] They started this.
-[Joey] This is it.
-[Jo] Your parents moved here when?
-My dad was born here.
-Really?
-Yeah, Dad was born here.
He left when he was young,
when he was six.
You guys never came here as kids?
-Never, no.
-That's so crazy.
[Joey] Wow, how old is this church?
-[Jo] Like 200 years, I think.
-[Joey] That's crazy.
-Beautiful.
-Wow.
Your mom and dad moved to Iowa
at what age?
My dad immigrated to Iowa
when he was sixth grade.
-Sixth grade, bro?
-Yeah.
Neither of them could speak English.
They got married in the Philippines,
and he brought my mom over
when she was 21.
When I told my parents I was coming here,
they dropped me at the airport in Iowa,
they got emotional.
It was one of those things.
They were like, "Take it all in."
Thank you for that. It was a moving moment
for them to know that I was gonna see it.
Hi.
[upbeat dance music playing]
-So fun.
-Oh, my God.
[Joey] That was dope.
We're back here.
So point, point. Garlic rice!
Itlog. Longganisa!
[Filipino accent]
Filipino breakfast at its best.
Point, point.
[Jo] Like that.
-[cat howls]
-Oh, my God, there's a cat! Jesus Christ!
-I'm so happy you guys are here.
-Thank you for taking us.
-[Jo in Tagalog] I love you.
-[Joey in Tagalog] I love you.
[crowd cheers]
Please give it up
to my friend, Andrew Lopez.
Hey.
What's up, everybody? Hey.
It's so dope to be in the Philippines
for the first time.
This is amazing for me because I'm around
people that look exactly like me.
That's amazing.
I don't think all Asians look the same,
but right when I got to the Philippines,
right when I got off the airplane,
everyone looked at me and was like,
"You look exactly like Coco Martin."
[crowd laughs and cheers]
I was like, "Who the hell is Coco Martin?"
If you don't know who Coco Martin is,
he's the Tom Cruise of the Philippines.
I looked this guy up on my phone.
I look exactly like him,
if Coco Martin was on drugs.
[crowd laughs]
But it's amazing being around people that
look like me. I never had that in my life.
I grew up in a town of 10,000 white people
and then just me.
I was one of one Asian guy in this town.
If you wanted to go
to the Chinese restaurant where I grew up,
you went to our house.
That's how white this place is.
And my name is Andrew Lopez.
Do you know how confusing that was
for all the white people?
My entire life, I had to give
presentations on what an Asian was,
because they had never seen one before.
For my third-grade show and tell,
you know what I did?
I brought my mom to school.
[crowd laughs]
I showed her off
and I told the kids I was Filipino,
and that word blew their minds
because they had never heard that word
their entire lives.
They straight up thought it was a disease
I was talking about.
Kids on the playground were like, "Yo,
bro, did you hear about the Mexican kid?
Yeah. It turns out he has Filipino."
But I got out of there.
Now I'm seeing you guys,
and I'm taking in the culture,
and I want to see the ladies,
and I want to connect with you,
and that's why I turned my Tinder on
right when I got in this bitch.
Yeah. It's on a 500 ft. radius, too,
so all the thotties in here,
let's match up, let's link up.
I have a passport.
I'll take you back to America. Let's go.
I'll hold you, bathe you, marry you,
kiss your butt and your mouth tonight.
Let's do it. I'm in. I love Tinder.
And don't pretend
like you're not on Tinder.
I watched the girls walk in, in here.
The girls with the fake eyebrows,
you're the ones on Tinder. I know.
And don't worry,
I swipe right on everyone by the way.
So all you girls, let's go tonight.
I swipe right on every single picture.
I never swipe left,
because all I'm looking for is love.
I don't even look at the pictures.
I do it in my pocket like this.
I walk around all day swiping right.
I don't even know who's gonna be
in my hotel room tonight. Let's go.
I love Tinder so much
that it changed everything about me.
I wish I was gay,
so I could suck dick and get more matches.
Do you understand?
I love Tinder so much, man. Tinder
is the most positive thing in my life.
I'm wearing a condom right now.
It's a magnum, too.
I don't fit, but it makes me feel black
and that's how I get more matches.
That's some dumb smart shit I'm saying
by the way.
I know a lot of dumb smart people.
If you don't know what a dumb smart person
is, you've got to meet a smart racist.
That's a dumb smart person.
If you don't know what a smart racist is,
some examples.
I met a guy
that was a smart racist person.
He came up to me one time,
like, "Hey, bro.
What's up with all these Asians
using chopsticks?"
I was like,
"Do you have a problem with Asians?"
He's like, "I just think
that forks and spoons are easier."
And I was like...
"You're right. I don't..."
I have parents that are very genuine.
My parents are dope.
I love them so much.
They cared about me my entire life.
My dad was in the Air Force. He did
everything for me to have a better life.
My dad is a competitive Filipino.
And if you know a competitive Filipino,
they're crazy.
Filipino dads, you know how competitive
they are by watching them sneeze.
Filipino dads, they sneeze loud as shit
and they try to sneeze louder
than the other dads. It's amazing.
You know exactly who I'm talking about.
You'll be at church, the entire church
will be completely quiet,
but if your dad needs to sneeze,
he'll just...
[sneezes forcefully]
And bless himself, like, "Bless me."
My mom was dope, too.
My mom gave me harsh love.
I remember the first time
my mom caught me drinking.
I was 16 years old,
I had a bottle of whiskey.
I walked in the room,
my mom caught me,
and she was like,
"What are you doing with that alcohol?
Do you know what that does to people?"
Do you remember when you got caught
smoking a cigarette as a kid,
and your mom was like,
"What are you doing with that cigarette?
Do you know what it does to people?"
And, as a punishment, they made you smoke
the entire pack of cigarettes?
My mom caught me
with that bottle of whiskey and was like,
"What are you doing with that whiskey?
Do you know what this does to people?"
And then she drank the whole thing.
Thank you, guys. I'm Andrew Lopez.
I appreciate and love you guys.
[Jo] Andrew Lopez!
My next guest,
make some noise for Joey Guila!
Oh, yeah! Philippines!
Yes, come on! I feel it! Keep it going!
[sensual dance music playing]
Thank you so much.
That sounded like a fart.
[makes fart sound]
Make some noise if you believe in this.
We need to see more Filipinos
on the big screen in Hollywood.
Right?
I want to see
the first Filipino cowboy movie.
Can you imagine that?
[makes clip-clop noises]
That's not his horse. That's his slippers.
Oy.
I just went
to my 30th high school reunion.
Yes. And I didn't even graduate.
I just wanted to go to the party.
Everyone was at that party though.
When the DJ played the first song,
we were like, "Oh! That's my jam."
Two songs later,
we're like, "Oh! That's my gout."
[crowd laughs]
I love going to Filipino parties,
especially my own.
My auntie always greets me with an insult.
[crowd laughs]
Does it happen to you guys, too?
That one auntie. Right?
I go, "Hi, Auntie."
[Filipino accent]
"What happened to your face?"
"What's wrong with it?"
[Filipino accent] "It's like that.
What happened to your neck?"
She has a flashlight.
"What's wrong with my neck?"
[Filipino accent] "It's like that."
[crowd laughs]
"This is my girlfriend."
[Filipino accent] "Wow.
[crowd laughs and cheers]
What happened to the skinny one?"
I say, "You're mean, Auntie."
[Filipino accent] "I'm not mean.
I'm a Catholic."
She's religious when she gambles, too.
You should see her
at the slot machines in Vegas.
She's got a long rosary.
She just puts it around there.
[Filipino accent] "Oh, God, please.
Oh, God, please.
Please, God.
Better make me win, God."
Then she pulls it.
[makes sound of slot machine]
[Filipino accent] "Shit.
What happened to you?
You don't love me?"
I was in the hospital.
I've been in remission from cancer.
I'm so happy to be here.
Yes.
[crowd claps and cheers]
And nurses-- Any nurses in the house?
Any nurses?
[crowd laughs]
You're all queens.
When I was in the hospital and--
Nurses are busy.
I'm like, "Nurse? Nurse, help."
They didn't listen. They'd walk by.
I'd go, "Nurse, wait. Wait.
I'm Filipino!"
[Filipino accent] She's like, "What?
How come you didn't tell me?
I could give you something for free."
Philippines! I'm Joey Guila.
Thank you guys so much.
I love you all.
[Jo] Joey Guila!
Andrew Lopez!
Andrew Lopez.
A very confusing name for a Filipino.
That's why we all have nicknames.
That's the truth.
Like Jo Koy is not my real name.
That's my nickname.
See, you guys are in shock.
[Filipino accent] "What?
He's an impostor?"
That's my nickname. My aunt gave me that.
My Auntie Evelyn gave me my name
"Jo Koy." That's not my real name.
I started stand-up 30 years ago in 1989.
I used to go up with my real name,
you guys. Joseph Glenn Herbert.
[crowd laughs]
Fuck you! That's why I changed my name!
[crowd laughs and cheers]
Literally.
When you first start stand-up,
you've got to do open mics,
you've got to do bars,
you've got to do restaurants.
You only get three minutes,
and I would go up with my real name,
and then people would laugh.
"Joseph Glenn Herbert." Fucking people
would laugh. I'm like, "God damn it."
All my sets were about my fucking name.
Then I went to my aunt's house
after one of the shows.
My cousin Mona lives there,
and I was talking to Mona.
I was just like, "Mona, I've got to change
my name. Every time I go up on stage,
they say my name, they laugh."
And then my cousin was like,
"Yeah, 'cause your name sucks."
[crowd laughs]
I go, "Okay, I know that." She's like,
"We've got to change your name."
She goes, "All right.
Why don't you drop your last name
and just go with your middle name
as your last name?"
I go, "Joseph Glenn?"
She goes, "Yeah, that sucks, too. Listen."
She goes, "Get rid of your middle name,
and then take your last name,
and then move it to your first name."
I go, "Bitch, that's still Herbert."
[crowd laughs]
And right when I said that,
my Auntie Evelyn was in the kitchen.
She goes,
[Filipino accent] "Jo Koy, eat.
Jo Koy, eat. Jo Koy, eat."
I swear to God, I was like...
"That's my name."
She had been calling me that my whole
life, but it wasn't until that moment
when I knew I had to change my name,
I was like, "That's my name.
I'm going to go by Jo Koy."
1989. That's when I was like,
"I'm gonna use Jo Koy."
Since then, for 30 years,
I've been going up as Jo Koy.
Then when this last special came out...
I had to do press,
and they kept interviewing me.
And every reporter
kept landing on the same question.
"Why do you go by Jo Koy?"
I was like, "I don't have an answer."
[crowd laughs]
I go, "That's just what Filipinos do.
They name you one thing
and then fucking call you something else."
And this is a very true story,
'cause I just found this out, you guys.
This happened about four months ago.
I went to Vegas
and I took my Auntie Evelyn out to eat.
And I just looked at her and I go,
"Look, Auntie,
a lot of reporters are asking me
where I got my nickname,
and I don't have a story,
so can you just tell me a story,
why you came up with the nickname Jo Koy?"
She's really old.
You've got to understand.
She looked at me and she went like this,
she goes...
[Filipino accent]
"I don't call you Jo Koy."
[crowd laughs]
And then I was like,
"Oh my God, she's old.
She's losing it.
She's losing it."
So I felt bad. I went like this.
I go, "Auntie, no, it's me.
It's me. I'm Jo Koy.
I'm Jo Koy.
I'm Jo Koy, your favorite...
your favorite... nephew. I'm...
I'm Jo Koy."
And then she goes,
[Filipino accent] "I know who you are.
I'm not stupid.
I'm just telling you
I don't call you Jo Koy."
I go, "What are you talking about,
you don't call me Jo Koy? You were--
Are you fucking with me right now? Like...
Are you being serious?
Thirty years, I've been going by Jo Koy.
You've never said anything."
She's like, [Filipino accent] "Yeah,
I never said anything,
because you keep saying Jo Koy,
so I just let you say it."
"So for 30 years, you let me
say Jo Koy, but you don't call me Jo Koy?
I could have sworn,
that day when I was at the house,
you said, 'Jo Koy, eat,' and I was like,
'Jo Koy, that's my nickname.'
Are you serious right now?"
[Filipino accent]
"I don't call you Jo Koy."
"Then what do you--
Then what do you call me?"
It's a true story, you guys.
Are you ready for this shit?
It's gonna fucking make you cry.
I swear I just found this shit out.
"What do you call me?"
She goes,
[Filipino accent] "I call you Jo Ko.
That is your nickname. Jo Ko."
And for all of you at home
that don't know what that means,
in Tagalog, "ko" means "my."
My nickname is My Jo. Jo Ko.
How fucking sweet is that?
That's so sweet.
I had no idea.
I go, "That is the sweetest nickname."
[Filipino accent] "You're the one
that keeps saying fucking Jo Koy.
I don't know who the fuck that is.
Every Netflix special,
'Coming to the stage, Jo Koy.'
I'm like,
'Who the fuck is that? It's Jo Ko!
That's Jo Ko.'"
Why didn't she tell me this 30 years ago?
All my merchandise, misspelled.
My next friend right here, Ramon Ibanga,
doesn't go by his real name either.
But you know who he's worked with? Drake.
[crowd cheers]
J. Cole. Jay-Z and Beyoncé.
And guess what? Those are nicknames too.
Those are nicknames too.
Well, not Beyoncé.
This whole time, I thought
that was a nickname. Anyways...
He's better known as Grammy award-winning
producer !llmind, everybody.
And we brought him home to make some
music magic right here in the Philippines.
Check this out.
[traditional Filipino instruments playing]
Yo, yo.
-That's good, bro.
-The legendary !llmind.
How are you, man? Thank you so much.
What's up, man?
-I'm a fan.
-Good to meet you. Thanks. Likewise.
-This is wild.
-It's crazy. I can't believe I'm here.
We gotta make this intro song for Jo.
We should use some authentic loops
and sounds that are kind of original.
I'm there. I'm in that zone.
This is an opportunity to introduce
Filipino culture to America.
Just bringing those two cultures together.
Let's get to work. Come on.
[different beats playing]
I love this loop.
What's the BPM?
Eighty-five.
Can you go to 90?
[same loop continues to play]
All right, um...
What record did you get the guitar from?
Do you have that record on you?
-I made that.
-You made it?
-Did you bring the records?
-Yeah.
[drums playing]
-This is crazy right here.
-Yeah.
We can serve that drum pattern
in the background.
You can watch. The type of drum pattern
we're gonna put on this is gonna be crazy.
-All right, we've got enough. Okay.
-How about some native strings?
-[!llmind] Yeah, let's hear that.
-[DJ] Right?
[people singing traditional song]
Whoo!
[people continue to sing traditional song]
Can we actually...
Can you actually plug that in
and then let's import those samples?
So what I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna take that first piece,
I'm just gonna line it up.
[drums playing]
[!llmind]  If you put in some deep bass,
you know...
Trust me. You got it.
-[!llmind] I want to import that vocal.
-Okay.
And then see
if I can fit those two pieces together,
-the vocal and then this percussion.
-Okay.
And then I want to have you add,
-like, boom bap drums on top of it.
-Okay.
[drums playing]
I like those drums.
I was thinking that the part
when it comes in, "Boom..."
just for the intro and then
somebody will be screaming, like, uh...
-"Another fucking crazy-ass pinoy."
-Yeah.
"Another fucking crazy-ass pinoy,"
-before a rapper will come in.
-Right.
[drums playing]
[beats dropping]
♪ Everybody getting down with the brown
Boom ♪
-That's fire.
-All right.
♪ Everybody getting down with the brown ♪
I love that.
[vocals continue]
[DJ] All right, you guys come in
after eight bars.
-Eight bars.
-[DJ] All right, let's do it.
!Ilmind, you're my "LODI."
[men laugh]
-[DJ] Do you know what "LODI" is?
-[!llmind] No.
-It's "Idol."
-Oh, man.
-[drum and vocals playing]
-[woman rapping]
[rapping]
-I love his delivery.
-Yeah.
"Introducing...
Jo...
Koy!
Make some motherfucking noise!"
Crazy.
♪ Everybody getting down with the brown
Boom ♪
-Jo.
-Jo Koy in the building.
The man, the myth, the legend.
-What's up, man?
-Dude, man.
-!ll! I love you, man.
-Oh, man.
-Amazing. I'm so happy you're here.
-Can't believe I'm here.
This shit is crazy. Jo Koy in the flesh.
-You bet.
-I'm so happy. This is amazing, dude.
-Are you loving it?
-I love this track.
-You like it, man?
-Yeah.
The world's are all coming together, man.
This is what we wanted.
Your story is such an amazing story
to get inspired by.
Know what I mean? Now we live
in a generation where we can reach
-and let these people know who you are.
-Right.
And now we've got these three kids
that are inspired by that.
We give our people the chance
to realize that it's possible.
You can look like us
and be from where we're from--
-Exactly.
-And actually do something.
For a long time,
we didn't really have that--
-[Jo] No!
-That vision.
Like, "Yo, I can get in the booth,
because !llmind did it."
Or, "I can get on stage and tell jokes,
'cause Jo Koy did it."
"I can do it."
-[!llmind] Exactly.
-"I don't have to be a nurse."
That's real. No, that's real.
That's real shit.
Damn, you're the shit. Love you.
I can't wait to see you walk out
with this shit, bro.
-Right? It's gonna be so sick.
-I need to hear it. It's gonna be sick.
[Jo Koy's opening song playing]
Give it up for !llmind.
[crowd cheers]
[Jo] That was sick.
You hear that track right there?
That's original right there.
That is authentic Filipino.
[song continues to play]
And that's a real collaboration
with my dude DJ Medmessiah right here.
-Give it up right here, everybody.
-[!llmind] Med in the house.
I absolutely love
everything that we're doing tonight.
Nothing better than authenticity.
Thank you, !llmind.
-Thank you, DJ Medmessiah.
-Thank you, guys.
I also brought my friend Andrew Orolfo,
right here to taste
some real Filipino food
cooked by my family
at an authentic Filipino farmers market.
[upbeat dance music playing]
Andrew!
What's happening, baby?
Let's go.
You wanted breakfast.
I'm bringing you breakfast.
[Jo] This is the farmers market, man.
-[Gemma] Hi.
-This is my sister, Gemma.
-How are you?
-This beautiful woman is my aunt.
-[Jo] My Auntie Ofie.
-Come here.
-[Ofie] Welcome to the Philippines.
-Thank you so much.
I want nothing but the best Filipino food
made for you
for your homecoming since you were a kid.
-Let's walk around. Let's pick the stuff.
-Yeah.
[upbeat dance music]
-Which do we put in the--
-Yeah, this one only.
-[Jo] This one?
-[Andrew] Okay.
One kilo, please.
[Jo] Welcome to the chicken department.
This is where we can get everything, man.
Wings, thighs, breasts.
We'll just get a bag of chicken.
What's your name?
Call me Lodi.
Lodi? Idol!
Here in the Philippines,
that's backwards for "idol."
Well, brother, actually her name is Ludi.
Damn it. Her name is actually really Ludi.
-My bad.
-It's Ludi.
But you're my idol. High five.
-[in Tagalog] Thank you.
-Let's go eat.
-Thank you.
[upbeat instrumental music playing]
How much fun are you having?
This is honestly
one of the greatest experiences.
Right? I can't wait.
My sister's cooking for us right now, man.
They're letting us cook
in that restaurant.
You can't go to any restaurant in America
and go, "Hey, can we use your kitchen?"
Like, "What?"
-My favorite dish is chicken adobo.
-Yeah.
Ever taste something
that takes you back to childhood?
Yeah. My mom used to cook it
all the time when we were young.
To this day, I still remember the pot
that it was cooked in.
-Yes.
-I think my mom still has that pot.
When you had friends come over
and try chicken adobo,
did they not go, "What?"
-They loved it.
-They would go apeshit.
How often do you go to a pot luck
and bring lumpia
-and everybody's just hyped?
-Kills it.
So why do we keep telling the world
about balut?
-Enough!
-[Andrew chuckles]
When did you leave here?
How old were you?
I visited when I was a kid,
probably before I was ten.
-Really?
-We were only here for, like, a week.
When you started doing stand-up,
did you think,
ever, that you would be performing
in the motherland?
-Never.
-Never, right?
I never thought
I'd be out here doing this.
I'm Filipino, but I grew up in America.
I was honestly scared when I was like,
"You're gonna perform in the Philippines."
-Really? Yeah.
-Oh, man.
I always had that weird thing
in my head of, like,
"I don't think
they're gonna get my stuff."
Who's not gonna get it?
-Anybody?
-Just anybody in the Philippines.
Just Filipinos in general.
First of all, comedy is comedy.
-Yeah.
-Funny is funny.
The only time they're not gonna laugh
is if you're not funny.
-Right?
-It's true.
I've realized, "I'm not the only Filipino
who thinks like me, who looks like me."
We have so much more in common
than I ever would have thought.
Yeah, man.
I'm so glad I'm here
and I'm excited to be performing.
-That's cool. Now we've got to eat.
-Let's eat.
[Gemma] All done.
-My auntie!
-Thank you.
Chicken adobo.
[Jo] Upo, chicken adobo,
garlic fried rice.
-This is the food I made.
-Yum.
This is my favorite. Chicken adobo.
It's the best.
Best Filipino dish.
In the Philippines,
they eat with their hands, so...
-Can I just get a fork?
-Joseph!
Just eat it! Eat it.
Eat it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my friend, Andrew Orolfo.
[upbeat hip-hop beats playing]
Yo, what's going on?
Are you enjoying the show?
Has this been good?
I feel good.
Been hanging out a lot with my dad.
He just bought those things
called the transition glasses.
Know what I'm talking about?
If you don't know, those are the glasses
where the lenses will actually change
so people don't have sex with you and...
And those glasses are ridiculous to me.
I don't know if anybody in this room
has them.
If you do, don't tell me.
I don't respect you.
You know what I'm saying?
Are those them, my man? Are those them?
Look into this light right now. Look--
No, I'm just kidding.
I take that back.
If you do have those glasses,
I actually would like you to let me know
that you're wearing them
before you start talking to me.
That's only because,
when I was talking to my dad,
they changed mid-conversation.
And I had never felt so disrespected
in my life, you know?
And that's because when we were talking,
we were going from inside to outside
and then they start to get dark.
So I sped up my sentence, 'cause I felt
like I was running out of time.
But that's my dad.
He's just like a real goofy-ass dad.
You know, like he's so goofy
that he voted for Trump. That's who he is.
And it was so crazy to me, you know,
only because I had no idea
that he was even a citizen
of the country, so...
I've been hanging out with my dad a lot
and I think it's 'cause we're trying
to make up for lost time or whatever.
My parents aren't together.
Anybody else grow up
in a single-parent household?
It was your fault. And...
Just kidding.
My parents aren't together.
My parents split up when I was, like, 12.
And then, when I was 15,
I found out. Yeah.
For a good while, I had no idea. Just...
Just one day I went up to my mom,
like, "Where's Dad been at?"
She looked at me like,
"I knew I forgot something. Oh, man."
Growing up--
I have a sister,
and neither of us knew he was gone.
That's because, when he lived with us,
he didn't hang out with us at all.
He was gone all the time already.
So there was no real, like,
emotional attachment to him.
It was kind of like this.
You know when you're at a party and you're
in a conversation with two other people,
and those two people
are really engaged in the conversation,
and you're not really contributing,
so you kind of just slowly
just walk out of the conversation?
And then start a new family.
You ever do that? That's wild.
Yeah.
We still talk all the time.
He just got a new job.
He's currently a grade-school bus driver,
which is so silly to me, you know.
'Cause it's like, "Okay,
you wouldn't drive this kid to school,
but now you want to drive
everybody's kids to school. Right?
Fine. Fine."
I live in California, uh...
And we get a lot of earthquakes.
Before I do this,
do we all know what the Richter scale is?
Okay, good,
'cause I've been thinking about it
and I think it's crazy that the way
we measure earthquake magnitude
can also be applied to dick size.
Uh...
Yeah, some of you get it already.
Really think about it.
Say you're working with, like, a 3.5,
you're like, "Did you feel that shit?"
No, nobody did. Nobody felt that.
What? Wild.
5.5 to 6, you can handle that, you know.
That comes around the most often
and, to be honest, might be the best one.
Shut up.
6.5 to, like, 7, now you're like,
"Whoa, that was wild.
We could probably go through that again,
but maybe we should be more prepared
next time." You hear what I'm saying?
And then anything above an eight,
you're like,
"Oh, my God. Everything is ruined.
Everything is ruined.
And my dog's dead." What? Why?
That's been my favorite joke to tell
as of late, only because I can see
where the dudes are at in the joke
when I look at you and tell it.
'Cause a lot of you
look real sad at three, but...
But at eight, this dude elbowed his girl
like, "That's me, baby. That's me."
She's not disagreeing. All right.
All right, that's my time.
Thank you so much. Bye.
Andrew Orolfo!
Tonight, we've seen Filipino-Americans
perform in the Philippines
for the first time.
But my next friend was born
right here in Manila.
That's right, right here in Manila.
And now he's touring the world over.
Give it up for Iñigo Pascual!
[Iñigo Pascual's "Catching Feelings"
playing]
Thank you so much, Jo!
Yeah! This one's called
"Catching Feelings." Let's go.
♪ Just came from another mistake
Just another heartbreak ♪
♪ Repeating it over and over
'Til our hearts break ♪
♪ Losing my mind every time with ya ♪
♪ Back to the wringer
And we always hit rewind, baby ♪
♪ Say something stupid
And you start to see red ♪
♪ I'm tryna please you
But I'm losing my head ♪
♪ Think I needa bounce, let me out
Hit the ground, running 'til I drop dead ♪
♪ But every time you tell me
That you love me ♪
♪ Every time you tell me
That you want me ♪
♪ Making me feel and think
It's the same inside ♪
♪ I would keep it to myself
But I gotta let you know that ♪
♪ I'm catchin' feelings for ya ♪
♪ Gotta let you know
That I'm catchin' feelings for ya ♪
♪Yeah, I'm catchin' feelings, feelings
Yeah ♪
♪ Tell me why even if I gave you my life
You still mad at me ♪
♪Tell me what the hell would suffice
I got a better me ♪
♪You calling me out
For all these dumb reasons ♪
♪ Gotta air it all out
You gotta run with me ♪
♪You stay on my mind
And I can't get you out ♪
♪You a real dime, baby
There is no doubt ♪
♪ I'm on the brink, 'bout to sink
But I think I got you figured out ♪
♪ But every time you tell me
That you love me ♪
♪ Every time you tell me
That you want me ♪
♪ Making me feel and think
It's the same inside ♪
♪ I would keep it to myself
But I gotta let you know that ♪
♪ I'm catchin' feelings for ya ♪
♪ I'm catchin' feelings ♪
[crowd cheers]
Iñigo Pascual, everyone!
Yes! That's how we close the show!
That's how we close the show.
Make some noise, you guys!
[crowd erupts]
That's what I'm talking about.
This was a dream come true, you guys.
This really was.
This was a dream come true, man,
and I'm so happy
that I got to come back to the motherland
and celebrate my culture, our culture,
with everyone out there
watching right now.
I hope we entertained you
and I hope we inspired you
to go celebrate your own culture,
whatever that may be, you guys.
Just do it. Embrace it.
But most importantly,
I got to share this moment with my son,
ladies and gentlemen.
I got to bring him to the Philippines
with me for the first time!
There he is, everybody! My boy!
Yes!
I love you guys. Goodnight!
[Jo Koy's opening song plays]
Subtitle By: MARSH-MARIE
[recording] Hey, this is Jo Koy,
and you are now listening to Moro Beats.