I think being an American
is a preexisting condition.
My hair used to be black.
Now every year white hairs show up.
Next year more white hairs moving in.
It makes me mad, makes me sad
'cause it means
my head is getting gentrified.
And...
there is nothing I can do to stop it.
Pretty soon I won't be able to afford it.
But I keep moving forward
because I'm an American.
I just wrote a movie about a piñata
that comes back to life
and murders all the children
that beat her with a stick.
That's right, I said her.
It's piñata, not piñato. Okay?
Piñatas are females
who have been getting abused by children
at the encouragement of parents
for centuries.
I like trilogies.
That's why I'm so excited
about World War III.
The original was a landmark.
Everyone loved that one.
A lot of critics and fans
think the second one
was better than the first, and...
We've all been waiting over 70 years
for the final chapter in the trilogy.
I wish they would just
give it to us already. I...
I think the next one
could be the highest-grossing.
I just hope they don't ruin it
with too much merchandising.
I do a lot of charity work. Anyone else?
You seem like great people.
I just donated to this organization,
Doctors Without Passports.
It's a group of doctors who wanna help
sick people in foreign countries
but they're not motivated enough
to get a passport.
Try to chip in and make a difference.
I wrote a self-help book for trees.
It's called How Not to Become a Book.
I'm hoping to sell 10 million copies.
I just made a documentary
about the horrors of human trafficking
during rush hour.
I'm always trying to help people.
Anyone from far away? Or, uh...?
- Where are you from?
- Guatemala.
Yeah.
- Guatemala's not that far.
I was actually there this morning.
I, uh...
I was gonna fly in for the show,
but it was nice out
so I parkoured my way over here, and so...
I care about the planet,
I don't use up carbon footprints,
just real footprints.
- What else? Who else?
- Mexico.
It's pronounced Mexico, okay.
Mexico.
- Where in Mexico?
- Monterrey.
Mm-hm. It's Monterrey. Monterrey.
I used to live
in downtown Monterrey, Mexico.
What part? I lived on First Street.
Sorry, it was Uno Street.
It was Uno Street.
The number one street
in Monterrey, Mexico.
That's why it's called Uno Street.
Welcome, great to have you here.
- Where you from?
- England.
England, at one point,
you used to own the whole world.
What happened?
I don't think you are an evil,
imperialistic nation.
I think you were simply a country that was
in search of better-tasting cuisine.
I, uh... I think one day your troops
wandered over to India,
took a lunch break, and were like,
"Wow. This curry is just dandy.
Let's take this recipe back to the queen."
Your general said,
"No, this is too good.
We should surround this nation
with our troops
and protect
this chicken tikka masala recipe.
Make sure it stays authentic."
And, England, you used to own us.
Yeah, you did. You used to own us.
And then we defeated you.
Took your language and perfected it.
You got nothing left.
Your last piece of dignity,
David Beckham, lives here.
He named his son Brooklyn, it's over.
That's the second
American Revolutionary War,
Beckham naming his son Brooklyn.
The tie is up at seven.
- What do you do, England?
- I organize events.
You organize events.
It sounds like you're a terrorist.
I'm gonna kick your ass
after the show.
- Any other countries?
- Germany.
Where in Germany?
West Germany.
Have you learned the name of the town yet
or...?
Or you know it's in the western part
of your country?
As a German I expect
more precision with your answer.
- Lithuania.
Got a zero from the crowd, sir, but I...
I think it's one of the top, uh, ten
ex-Soviet countries.
I, uh...
Welcome.
What do you do for a living?
- Student.
- Student?
You get paid to go to school?
Okay. What do you study?
- Physical education.
You study physical education.
So, when kids are in gym class,
you're looking through the window
and taking notes?
That's a crime in this country.
Well, all of you, uh,
Mexico, Venezuela, Argentina,
Germany, Ireland, Australia,
Netherlands, Switzerland,
all of you,
welcome to the number one country.
Welcome.
Thank you for coming all the way
from your little amateur,
junior varsity country
to an actual real, professional
and number one country.
Netherlands, beautiful country.
Most indecisive country in the world.
You're the Netherlands,
you're also Holland.
And when you meet someone
you tell them to call you Dutch.
You've been a country a long time now,
pick a fucking name.
Healthiest country in the world.
Everyone bicycles every day
in the Netherlands.
Yet they've never won the Tour de France.
Sad, dude.
Twice.
Switzer... No. That's a Dutch myth.
Yeah, that actually never happened.
Netherlands, what's your rank worldwide?
What do you guys rank?
We're number one,
but what do you guys rank?
Last time I checked the charts,
I didn't see you guys on it.
I know you're one of
the top 30 countries in Europe,
but, you know, like worldwide,
what's the rank?
You don't know? Let's go to the stats.
All right, Netherlands, uh,
how many, uh...?
How many gun murders a year do you have?
Like three? Four?
We have 30,000.
And you know why?
'Cause we're number one.
And think about it, why does America
have so many more gun murders
than the Netherlands?
It's because our country has superior aim.
We're...
We're better marksmen.
You all have no hand-eye coordination.
That's...
That's why you're playing soccer.
That's why you never won the World Series.
Netherlands, another question. Um...
When a woman in Netherlands
gives birth to a baby,
how much time is she given off of work
and maybe even paid
for that time off of work?
One year.
Women in Netherlands are given
a year of paid leave after giving birth.
Know how much time
women in America are given off of work
after they give birth to a baby?
Zero.
And you know why?
It's because our women
care about the economy.
That's why the euro is going down.
Number one.
Netherlands, another question. Um...
How many people imprisoned
in the Netherlands?
I don't mean emotionally, but literally,
how many people imprisoned
in the Netherlands?
- We close down prisons.
- You close down your prisons? No.
No one has the courage to steal?
Just sad, dude.
You probably have about 350 people
in prison.
We have 2.6 million people in prison
in this country.
That means we have a government
that cares so much about its citizens
it awards 2.6 million of them
free meals and housing.
And some of them are given
a lifetime supply.
And they cannot say no.
It's a mandatory gesture
of unconditional love.
I'm sorry your government hates you.
We have 2.6 million people in prison
in this country.
Kim Kardashian has 50.7 million followers
on Twitter.
We are incarcerating the wrong people.
That's the way I see it.
I was just in Italy.
Have you been there?
- Did you like it?
- Yes.
Really? I was not impressed.
I traveled all over Italy,
not one Olive Garden
in the entire country.
All these tiny Italian restaurants
that nobody's ever even heard of before,
not one good enough
to warrant opening a second one
and starting a chain.
Just failing across the entire country.
Sad, but...
We even have the greatest Irish restaurant
in the world, McDonald's.
That's why the Irish have been moving here
for decades.
Now, where do you guys stand
on professional sports teams
using racist mascots?
I'm against it.
But what about McDonald's
and their mascot?
Now, like I said, McDonald's,
greatest Irish restaurant,
and the Irish are known for often having
fair skin and reddish hair.
And you look at the McDonald's mascot,
it's literally a fucking clown.
A painted white face,
blood-red hair and nose.
How is that not offensive to our friends
in the Irish community?
Why are they not marching and protest...?
I think they must be too drunk to notice.
I can't think of one reason
they're not sticking up for themselves.
Question for the Europeans in the crowd.
How come when you go to Europe
nobody ever really tips the, uh, waiters
and the waitresses at a restaurant?
- They have better minimum wage.
- No, sir.
It's because they have inferior
waiters and waitresses.
America has the most elite waitstaff
on the planet.
Plus we're just a more generous country.
We're givers.
That's why we have military bases
in over 80 different countries.
We care.
America has military bases in Europe,
Europe has zero military bases in America.
Why? Because they're fucking selfish.
And we have the best drones in the world.
Drones are designed
to do a surgical strike,
to take out one person at a time.
Ours often kill up to 20 or 25 people
at a time.
That's an overachieving victory drone.
Now, I'm against the military
using drone strikes
because it takes away American jobs.
And...
Now, outside the military,
drones are starting to deliver packages.
That takes jobs away from birds.
This country used to have carrier pigeons,
and now they are all out of work.
That's the real reason
we have Angry Birds.
We're the fattest country
in the world.
Another reason we're number one,
and we keep getting fatter.
Why? Because the galaxy is expanding.
We're the only country adapting to it.
European countries, you're too healthy.
Pretty soon you're gonna lose your gravity
and float in outer space,
and then we will wobble over
and take your land.
That's why California gets
those earthquakes.
Too many skinny people,
not heavy enough to hold that earth down.
The Midwest, no earthquakes
because people are fucking solid.
I teach science part-time online
at Dunkin' Donuts Academy.
You guys should definitely take
one of my courses.
We're number one in type 2 diabetes.
- Any other countries?
- Canada.
- Where?
Why did you say that? We were
having a good time without...
We're all here having fun
and you had to say Canada.
Canada, do you realize we could've
invaded you at any point in history?
We were just never interested.
We actually marched
all the way through your country,
skipped it, then took Alaska.
Like, "You want this?" "No."
"What about this here?"
"Not feeling it."
"Oh, look, Alaska. We'll take that."
Canada, in the War of 1812,
you burned down the White House
and we still did not invade you.
Because we came to the realization
that living in Canada
was punishment enough.
So polite, Canada, so polite.
I was just on Canadian Tinder.
It was, uh...
There was no swipe left,
only swipe rights. Just...
Too polite to say no to anybody.
Said, "Well, not my type, but who knows,
it could work out. It could work out."
- A lot of Canadians hate America.
- No.
No, you do, but you don't admit it
because you're too polite and nice.
- That's true!
- And you hate us
because you think we hate you.
But we don't hate you,
we just don't notice you.
Canada is like,
"America, show us some love.
We're Canada, we have free healthcare,
no violence." We're like, "We're busy."
You see, America, we're the
cheerleaders and the quarterbacks.
And Canada is like the nerdy kid
who just moved here
even though he's been here
the whole fucking time.
Understand what I'm saying?
Canada gets American news.
America does not get Canadian news
unless it's a story
about a crackhead mayor
acting like a stupid American.
See, Canada,
when you're better than us, we ignore you.
When you dumb it down,
we wanna hang out.
This will sum up the entire
Canadian-American dynamic.
As an American, you go to Canada,
you don't have to switch
American money
over to Canadian money.
That's how friendly and polite they are.
They save you that hassle
of going to the exchange place
just so that you,
a foreigner in their land,
can have more free time.
Very nice.
If a Canadian comes to America
and tries to put one little shiny,
sparkly Canadian quarter
into some dirty slot
in an American parking meter,
we're like,
"Get that fucking shit out of here."
That's the relationship.
And as a result,
Canada has low self-esteem.
And there is proof in your money.
Who is printed on American money?
American presidents for the most part.
And who is printed
on a lot of Canadian money?
The Queen of England.
How do you think that makes
the Queen of Canada feel?
Dear Canada,
before you want America to love you,
learn to love yourself.
We're just a better country, Canada.
You have red and white in your flag.
We have red, white, and blue on our flag.
That's why we're number one.
We've got red, white, and blue in our flag
just like Cuba and North Korea.
We're a flawless nation.
America is the greatest country
in the United States.
You cannot argue that.
How does it feel being in Canada,
living so close to greatness?
Yet so far away at the same time.
It feels awesome.
Way too much energy for Canada.
Way too much energy.
Israel.
- Where?
- Israel.
Cool. Where in Palestine are you from?
- Any other countries?
- Israel.
- Where?
- Here, Israel.
- Where in Israel?
- Right here.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah... I ju...
This is not Israel here, so...
I'm from right here in Israel.
Wow, no wonder why there's
so much conflict with Palestine.
Like everywhere we go is Israel.
Doesn't matter. If, uh...
we built settlements down here,
yeah, that's Israel.
We take a plane to New York,
that's Israel, too.
Okay? Wherever we go,
it's fucking Israel, okay?
So, you're from Israel? Cool.
You're Asian.
Yes, you are. You're Asian.
Israel is in Asia.
It's not in Africa.
It's not in Europe.
The Mideast is not a continent.
You're Asian.
Jesus was Asian.
Santa Claus is Asian.
That's why all the toys say
"made in China."
I was just in China, met a 5-year-old boy.
His toy said, "I made this."
I like China.
China has my favorite air quality.
I don't trust the air in America.
I don't trust what I can't see.
In China, you can see it. I trust that.
It's honest air.
Without transparency,
they achieve transparency.
You're from Israel,
what should happen?
Should Israel have a two-state solution?
A one-state solution?
Or just a free-for-all?
What should happen?
- I'm gunning for the two states.
- The two-state? Okay.
So, you're thinking maybe you should do
what we did in our country with Carolina?
For centuries it was just Carolina, and...
they were always at war with each other.
North...
The north part of Carolina was building
settlements in the southern parts
and making life
very, very difficult for them.
They would sometimes throw rocks
back at them, and...
And then we split them up
into two completely separate states.
North and South Carolina.
And now they are the two
most shining examples
of perfect states in our country.
North Carolina and South Carolina
have had zero problems
and are the best states in the nation
since we did that, so...
I don't know, maybe you're right,
or maybe not.
Uh...
How about you? What do you do?
You look like you teach chess to cops.
Smart but solid.
Sounds good to me.
- Yeah? Where is home? Australia?
- Yeah.
- What part?
- Melbourne.
It's pronounced Melbourne.
Yeah, it's Melbourne.
You almost got it. You almost got it.
Melbourne.
M-E-L-B-O-U-R-N-E. Melbourne.
Australians are always mispronouncing
their own names.
They don't say Melbourne,
they say Melbourne.
They don't say Perth, they say Perth.
And it has nothing to do with your accent.
I mean, as a country,
you're acist against the letter R.
I think the actual name of your country
is Raustralia.
But you efused to say R
more than one time in a word.
Australia, you're a lot like America.
But you're a lot behind us.
You're a lot younger than us.
You're a big country like us,
but you've only got cities
along the coast.
You've got nothing in the middle.
Here in America,
we've got cities along the coast
and throughout the middle.
Except nobody wants to visit
the cities in the middle.
So, even though you're behind,
you're actually ahead.
Well done, Raustralia.
Now, ahem... Australia, why are you
so far away from the rest of the world?
What's up with that?
I think it's because you're scared.
Of every country.
Except New Zealand,
the Canada of Australia.
- Okay, where you from?
- Denmark.
Denmark, very nice, too.
That's Scandinavia.
Beautiful part of the world.
Interesting part of the world,
Scandinavia.
Almost all white people...
yet still segregated.
The popular people are in Sweden,
the rich people in Norway,
artsy people in Denmark,
and the depressed nerds
with zero self-esteem
waiting to kill themselves
are in Finland.
And...
the people you do not even acknowledge
are in Iceland.
So, it's interesting
how you work out these things.
Is anyone from another, uh, state?
Anyone from another state?
- Where are you from?
- Chicago.
Chicago.
Correct answer would've been Illinois.
See? That's Americans right there.
We're dumb, but we're confident.
One of the many reasons we're number one.
- Where did you grow up?
- Spain.
- Where?
- From Spain.
It's pronounced España.
España.
Why do you change the name of your country
when you go to other countries?
- You call it España?
- Sure.
Sure? You're just agreeing with me now?
Or like is that the answer?
- Seriously.
- Okay.
Then you should call it that in...
Wherever you go.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
When someone from the United States
goes to Spain
they don't say
they're from Estados Unidos.
They get it wrong in a different way.
They say they're from the States.
But no one ever here,
if someone asked if they're from here,
say they're from the States.
If you're already here
and you say you're from the States,
they will think
you're not fucking from here.
I met some people a few weeks ago
and I asked them where they were from
and they said South Korea.
I'm like, "No, just say Korea."
'Cause when you say South Korea
it sounds like you're North Korean
pretending to be South Korean.
If you're here
and you're from one of the Koreas,
we know it's South Korea.
What's the lamest state in the country?
What's the lamest state?
- Utah.
- No, no, no.
- Delaware.
- No.
- New Jersey.
- All inferior states, yes,
but not the lamest.
The lamest? Washington state.
It's the only state that has to specify
that they're a state.
Because if you just say Washington,
you think Washington, D.C.
Which is not even a state.
You don't say, "Where you from?"
"Virginia state."
Yeah... No.
But Washington state you say.
How about this table,
where are you from?
- New York.
- New York, that's here, sir.
Sir, let me explain something.
You ask someone where they're from
and they say the name of the city
you're currently at,
it implies you don't know
where the fuck you are, okay?
- Where in New York do you live?
- Tribeca.
Tribeca.
It's a very dangerous neighborhood.
Look at someone the wrong way
on the streets of Tribeca,
they might unfollow you on Instagram.
Tribeca is one of
the most diverse neighborhoods
in New York City.
Where else can you find hedge fund CEOs
living right next door
to venture capitalists?
Both upstairs from a CVS
that's inside of a Walgreens.
Which are both inside a Citibank.
Where else can you find that
but the melting pot that is New York City?
Our slogan is "Welcome to New York."
We are the only city whose slogan
is sarcastic.
Like, "What is this shit?
The ATM just took an additional $60
out of my account.
Holy fuck, where's my phone?"
Welcome to New York.
Our slogan is "go fuck yourself."
A lot of the new kids moving here
do not know that.
They listen to Taylor Swift sing a song
called "Welcome to New York."
And when she sings it, she means it.
That's not right.
I'm trying to tell you
if you're walking around the city,
and you happen to see Taylor Swift,
rob her.
So that she can learn
what her own song means.
'Cause she doesn't fucking know.
The new regime wants to bring back
the policing tactic of stop-and-frisk.
What do you guys think about that?
I'm against it.
Stop-and-frisk was proven
to be unconstitutional and ineffective.
Studies show that 90 percent of the people
who were stopped and frisked by police
were black and Latino men.
And 95 percent of the time they were
stopped and frisked, they were innocent.
There was no reason for them
to be stopped and frisked,
yet they were stopped and frisked.
So, what does that mean?
Cops are gay.
And they prefer black and Latino men
90 percent over all other men.
And I think that is discriminatory
towards other men
who want to be molested and squeezed
by sweaty cops.
That's my stance.
A friend of mine just went
to a pro-police brutality rally,
and the cops
beat the shit out of him, they...
Be very careful what protests you go to.
Protesting, one of the most
important things you can do,
just double-check which one of these
you're going to.
If you're transgender
you should be able to go to whatever
bathroom you think you should go to.
I don't know what the deal
about that is.
I think we all grew up in households
with unsegregated bathrooms.
It's not until we ventured out
in the public
they started segregating bathrooms.
And I think even more importantly,
as a nation,
we need to start shitting outside
again and marking our territory
and taking this country back
from the other animals.
- Yeah.
- Other animals try to infiltrate us.
Look at dogs, they're wearing clothes now
trying to be like us.
We've gotta stamp this out
before it's too big of a problem.
I think God is fake news.
No, not your God.
I'm talking about that other God.
People are freaking out about fake news
like it's something new.
What about the horoscope section
in the newspaper?
That's been fake news for at least
a couple of months at this point, right?
Kale is delicious.
Fake news. That's fake news.
It's fake news.
I think O.J. Simpson... is innocent.
I saw the trial, he was in court.
They put a glove recovered
from the murder scene,
tried to put it on his hand,
his hand was too big.
The glove did not fit.
Donald Trump has very small hands.
Donald Trump framed O.J. Simpson
for the murder of Nicole Brown Simpson
and Ron Goldman.
Trump is a career racist.
At the time, O.J.,
one of the most popular black men
in America.
It's a closed case.
And if you disagree with me,
you're fucking racist.
Well, they say love wins.
I think hate
has a pretty strong track record.
- Do you think love wins?
- No.
No, it doesn't.
Because love is not a competition.
If you view love as something
about winning or losing,
you don't know what love is about.
Sometimes I get deep.
You gotta be fucking ready for it.
I think Trump
was an excellent candidate for hate.
I think Bernie
was a good candidate for love.
I think Hillary was neither.
So, love never even got to the finals.
Well, who is ready to join the rebellion
and fight for democracy?
That'll do it. Yeah.
That was just the energy level
necessary to overthrow a dictatorship.
I...
I think some of that energy
and a couple of new apps,
and, uh, we'll be just fine.
Apps make the world go around.
Always remember
it was the, uh, Voting Rights app of 1965
that got black Americans
the voter protection they needed.
And it was not until the great
ice bucket challenge of 1920
that women got the right to vote.
Once that went viral,
things worked out perfectly
for women forever without a glitch.
Think we should have had a recount?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
I don't think
we should have had a recount.
Because I think as a nation
one of our strong points is not math.
Well, it's official,
Donald Trump is the 45th
greatest president of the United States.
I...
I just can't believe that Donald Trump
is now living in government housing.
You know, he has fallen off so hard.
He used to be at the top,
now he is in the projects.
He is in the White House.
Fifty bucks says in six months
he tries to flip it, sell it for a profit.
If Trump had any balls
he'd do his next press conference in
fluent Russian just to fuck with people.
I did not vote for Donald Trump.
I wrote in Eric Trump.
I just think he's so cool.
Eric Trump always looks like
he just realized he lost his keys.
He always looks like he just found out
someone else is sleeping with his wife,
and it's his dad.
He can't do anything about it
'cause it's also his boss.
We live in an oligarchy,
but with, uh, humidity
it feels like a dictatorship.
I don't think the mother of all bombs
did a good job raising her kids.
I think Mike Pence thinks
being gay is a choice
because he made a choice to be straight.
Mike Pence was just in Korea,
near the DMZ.
He made a speech
and he said
the era of strategic patience is over.
So, I guess he's coming out of the closet
any second now.
I'm against North Korea
using nuclear weapons.
Because that is cultural appropriation
of the United States,
and that is not okay.
I think I'm gonna have to be
the next president.
Yup, 2017, that's my year.
Not waiting until 2020. 2017.
I'm challenging Trump tomorrow,
three o'clock, White House parking lot.
I'll be like, "Let's go, Trump.
One-on-one for the presidency.
Oh. You wanna wait three years?
Are you scared?
Let's fucking go now."
I'll take him down in the first debate.
I'll be like,
"Yeah, Trump, I've got a question.
How can you look at your two sons,
Donald and Eric, and still be pro-life?
How can you do that?
You have two minutes
to answer the question.
One minute for each son. Done."
He does have a big following,
but I will defeat him.
He's got some of the Republican vote,
some of the Democrat vote,
some of the antiestablishment vote,
he's got the racism vote,
he's got the sexism vote,
and now with the support
of Chris Christie and Ben Carson,
he has the sleep apnea vote as well.
But I will defeat him.
Any questions about my
presidential platform for 2017?
Any issues close to your heart
you would like me to address?
Nothing? You lead privileged lives.
There's not one issue
you're concerned about?
Global warming.
Everybody's gotta start
taking off their clothes.
It's getting hot,
it's time everybody starts appreciating
each other's bodies.
Solid question.
- Yes. Over here.
- Healthcare.
Healthcare? We don't need it.
We're Americans, we're strong.
Europeans need it because they're
inferior and they have no confidence.
When I'm president
I say everyone gets healthcare.
Except the insurance companies.
Fuck them.
We kill them off first
then we can really change lives.
A lot of European countries
look down on America
'cause they have healthcare, and we don't.
But at least we have air conditioning.
Air conditioning is illegal in Europe.
At least in America,
we can get a fatal disease
and have the dignity of rotting
in a cooled-down apartment.
Instead of being stuck
all healthy and sweaty in Belgium,
or as I call it, the Delaware of Europe.
No one has been to Delaware.
See? No one has been to Delaware.
Maybe you drove through it
accidentally
and you were like,
"What the fuck is this?"
Then you said,
"Oh, it's the first state?
I guess we've made a lot of
improvements since then.
Let's try to forget this shit
ever happened."
When I'm president
I'm gonna make Puerto Rico the 50th state.
I'm demoting Delaware.
It's our first state,
we've yet to be impressed.
Puerto Rico is getting a shot.
International policies.
Foreign policy step one,
invade North Dakota.
Send North Korea a message.
Strategy, strategy.
Foreign policy step two,
invade Switzerland.
That's what they get
for being neutral all these years.
When you are silent,
you side with the oppressors.
How will we defeat them?
By using their own Swiss army knives
against them.
We'll poke them with that,
cut them up with those little scissors.
We will defeat them physically
and psychologically.
And it will not cost us a dime
because we will use
their Swiss army knives.
Foreign policy step three,
unblur Japanese porn.
Hear me out.
It's more complicated than you think.
It goes back all the way to World War II
where there were a lot of atrocities.
One of them,
we dropped two nuclear bombs on Japan
killing thousands and thousands,
devastating their country for decades.
Thirty-five years later,
Japan blurred the genitals in their porn.
Victory: Japan.
It's time for a truce.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you like Hawaii?
- Never been.
- Okay.
Well, as president I'm gonna move it
to Lake Michigan.
Hawaii is beautiful, it is too far away.
Move it to Lake Michigan,
it's a five-minute canoe ride
from downtown Chicago.
Easier for the entire country to visit.
Do you all like California?
Yeah!
Do you like New York?
Both cool, again too far away.
I have a solution.
California here, New York here.
We take the bulk of the Midwest
and we move it above Canada.
New York and California
come closer together.
You can now take the E train
from the Empire State Building
to In-N-Out Burger in 23 minutes.
By moving all of that land around,
that's gonna create jobs.
Yeah!
Economy thing.
I'll solve the homeless crisis
in this country.
A lot of homeless in this country.
And what else do we have a lot of
in this country? Cars.
Right? Young man, what do cars run on?
Gas.
No, roads actually, sir. Roads.
Cars run on roads.
And what do some roads have? Tollbooths.
Little houses.
We make the homeless full-time,
live-in tollbooth operators.
They're already good at asking for change.
It's a perfect fit.
I just solved the homeless crisis
in America.
I think the term homeless
can be derogatory.
At the beginning of time,
everyone was homeless.
So, I prefer the term old-fashioned.
- Any other issues?
- Abortion.
Mandatory. Mandatory.
I'm a feminist,
I'm for women's rights 100 percent.
You want your rights, you got them.
As a nation we are overpopulated.
Ladies, this is your chance to shine.
I'm for women's rights 100 percent.
When I'm president,
I'm not gonna have a first lady.
Because I think ranking women is sexist.
A lot of women in this country get paid
less than men to do the same job.
It's a disgrace to the nation.
So, I'm gonna make pay equality a reality
by lowering men's wages.
We will now have the equality
we've always dreamed of.
Parenthood is usually better
when it's planned,
so, uh, we'll keep Planned Parenthood.
I, uh...
I actually became a father when I was 15.
And at the time I realized I wasn't
mature enough to raise a child of my own,
so I adopted.
I think I did the right thing.
- Any other issues?
- Same-sex marriage.
You're talking about gay marriage?
Okay, also mandatory. Also mandatory.
If you're a guy and you wanna marry
a girl, you've gotta fuck a dude first.
If you make that work,
your relationship with a woman
will be pretty simple someday.
Plus, some gay guys like hooking up
with a straight guy,
and all women love putting men
through tests.
So, it's a win-win-win situation.
Gay marriage was legalized
about a year ago.
There were a lot of celebrations in
New York City. It's a very exciting time.
It was a conflicting time for me
because I love gay people,
but I hate rainbows.
I, uh...
I think rainbows are offensive
to the blind.
I used to be blind.
But then I went gluten-free
and cleared that shit right up.
- Oh, my God.
- Now I have better than perfect vision.
These glasses make my eyes weaker.
If I took these glasses off,
your vision would get blurry.
You're welcome.
Any other issues?
- Immigration.
- What?
Immigration.
You can stay, you can stay.
Sometimes you've gotta do the right thing.
But I'm deporting your friend
at 8:30 tomorrow.
I don't like his attitude.
When it comes to immigration,
let everyone in, have a big party.
Unless we have proof someone's a violent
criminal, we need border security.
And I have a plan.
To seal the borders
I'm going to hire the company
that makes DVD wrappers.
If it takes an hour and a half
to open up a DVD package,
imagine what they can do with the borders.
And if a criminal does sneak through,
he gets a free DVD.
He gets a free DVD,
takes him an hour to open it,
and you fucking nail him there.
Immigration is a very tricky subject.
Just last year, 10,000 children came up
through Central American countries,
through Mexico, across the U.S. border,
and then got busted in Texas.
Our government was trying to decide:
"What do we do
with these 10,000 desperate children?"
I think we should have
let them stick to their plan,
which was get to Canada.
I think it's presumptuous of us to think
we were their final destination.
We have no healthcare,
we're overcrowded.
Canada has free healthcare
and could use a few fucking people.
Woo!
I'm also gonna build a wall
through the middle of Mexico.
That way they'll get confused
and sneak into Mexico.
Strategy. Strategy.
Any other issues?
We're getting a lot done.
- Legalized pot.
- No.
What are you, afraid to break the law?
You're sitting at home all day going,
"I wanna smoke pot,
but I don't wanna get caught
and get in trouble"?
Toughen the fuck up, break the law.
Be a rebel, break the law.
Now, I'm a drug war reenactor, and, uh...
If you get busted for doing drugs,
tell the cops you're a drug war reenactor,
they get confused,
it sounds pro-military,
sometimes they let you off.
I don't do drugs.
I'm a role model to children.
But I believe doing drugs
is a personal choice,
not the government's business.
So, yeah, when I'm president
I'm gonna legalize drugs.
But I'm not gonna start with marijuana.
I'm gonna start with heroin.
If we legalize heroin first,
it will be very easy to legalize marijuana
after that.
Strategy, strategy.
You've gotta know how to work Congress.
Fuck it,
I'll start by legalizing crystal meth.
I'll sidestep Congress.
I'll take it to the people.
I'll mail everyone in the country
an envelope.
You mail back teeth, that's a yes.
Power to the people.
Climate change.
I am for climate change.
I don't want the same weather every day.
That's fascism.
Who thinks climate change is real?
Who thinks it's man-made?
- Yeah.
That's where you're wrong.
Think about it.
Temperatures are going up,
glaciers are melting,
sea levels are rising.
Why?
Fish are trying to take over the planet.
Earth has always been 71 percent water.
Now fish want the whole fucking thing.
Eat as much sushi as you can.
Japan has been leading the way on this
for years,
it's time for the rest of the world
to step it the fuck up.
I teach science part-time online
at ChristianMingle.com.
You guys should definitely take
one of my courses.
So, you think climate change is real?
You think it's bad?
You'd like to curb it?
- And where is home for you?
- Uh, Baltimore.
- Baltimore? Okay.
- Yeah!
And do you live in a...?
Do you live in a house or an apartment?
I live in... Well, I live in
New Jersey now, but I'm from Baltimore.
Okay, first of all, you're a liar.
You're a liar.
In New Jersey,
do you live in a house or an apartment?
- Apartment.
- In an apartment.
- And is it a new or old building?
- From the '80s, so it depends on...
- Uh, what floor are you on?
- Third.
- You have an air conditioner?
- Yeah, thank God.
Then you are for climate change.
Air conditioning literally
is climate change.
Unless you have your air conditioner on,
build a fire in your living room,
and let them battle it out,
then you are fighting climate change.
Otherwise,
you're part of the fucking problem.
We've gotta save water, people.
We've gotta save water.
That's why I don't shower.
I just smear hand sanitizer
all over my body.
I'm sticky, but I'm clean.
And I'm saving the planet.
Any other questions about my presidency?
- Any other issues?
- Russia.
Russia. We show them Rocky IV.
Russia has never seen
the entire film Rocky IV.
Rocky IV was released in Russia,
but it was a heavily edited version.
They cut it down to 17 minutes.
It ended when Apollo Creed
died in the ring
and they freeze-framed
on Rocky's crying face.
So, they showed it
80 times a day in the theaters.
The highest grossing film ever in Russia.
They never saw the ending,
so we have to show them the real movie
and that will clear it up.
The point is
I think we should build a wall.
Around Donald Trump.
- Yeah!
- I, uh...
Put, uh...
Put mirrors on the inside,
that way he's happy,
and... I think when Mexico
hears about this they'll be like,
"You know what? We'd like to pay for this.
We think this is a bueno investment."
- Coal.
- The economy.
We don't need to bring back coal, but I'll
bring back the VCR repairman jobs.
This country was built on VHS tapes.
VHS repair jobs
used to be the biggest industry
in the nation.
It was the heart of our economy,
and now it's gone to shit.
VHS is the premier way
to watch a movie at home.
Sure,
those critics out there will tell you
that Blu-ray has a sharper image,
but VHS is sharper emotionally.
And...
When I'm president
I'm gonna make college free.
You gotta pay for high school.
You're gonna pay for it one way
or the other. Might as well be cash.
And I'm going to raise the minimum wage
to 15 bucks an hour.
And I'm going to lower the maximum wage
to 14.50.
Put those CEOs in their place.
Who here recycles?
I'm gonna ban recycling.
Because I think segregating garbage
is racist.
Brown v. Board of Education, 1954,
separate is not equal.
All the trash
gets put in this disgusting dirty bag
while the recyclables
get a cute little shower
and then put in this privileged
sky blue clear bag. It's not right.
And I'm gonna ban brunch.
Because I am against corporate mergers.
Breakfast and lunch coming together.
It's too much power.
I'm gonna break it up.
And I'm gonna ban the Winter Olympics.
It's wrong that whatever country wins
the most medals at the Winter Olympics
gets to invade Ukraine.
I don't know why that is part
of the official Olympic platform,
but I'm against it.
And I'm gonna add three moons.
This is America, we shouldn't have to
share our moon with any other country.
If we add three,
we've got a total of four,
now werewolves can go out
and party once a week.
They're restricted to once a month.
That's why they get violent.
They've been in solitary
for 30 days straight.
Mermaids have been protecting
our ocean borders for over 200 years
and still do not have the right to vote.
It's wrong.
The key to surviving the zombie apocalypse
is... dentistry.
Before they turn into zombies,
the dentists extract their teeth,
and then they gnaw on you
with their gums
and just give you a nice massage.
Just relax the whole planet.
Zombies plus dentistry equals world peace.
- Has anyone here ever seen a UFO?
- Yeah.
Really? I have never seen a UFO.
Because I've always been able
to correctly identify the alien spacecraft
that I have come across.
You see, that's the difference
between you and me.
Do you think dinosaurs went extinct?
I do not.
I think dinosaurs are bone creatures
who live underground.
And archaeologists dig them up,
ripping them out of their homes
and murdering them.
And then they sell their body parts
to museums
where they are put on display
to scare children.
It's a big problem.
Other questions
about my presidential platform?
Gun control.
I think if Jesus had been American,
and had a gun,
he'd still be alive today.
They try to nail him to the cross, he'd be
like, "Not so fast, you pieces of shit."
Jesus, America, victory.
In a perfect world people would
be good enough at karate
so they wouldn't need a gun,
but I realize not everyone
can be a karate hero like myself.
Now, it's not my style,
but if you have a gun and you go hunting
and eat what you hunted,
that should be okay. But if you have a gun
and kill a person, right to jail.
Unless you eat the person,
then I think it should be okay.
Let's get a friendly poll here,
nobody's opinions are wrong,
nobody boo,
let's get a friendly poll.
Who here, by round of applause,
wants less guns?
Okay.
Who wants more guns?
Okay, you're both wrong.
Karate is the answer to gun control.
Fists don't run out of knuckles,
feet don't have to reload,
elbows don't get jammed.
I live in New York City.
A guy tried to mug me last year
and he had a gun,
but I had a bucket of diarrhea.
I dumped it over his head,
he shot himself.
That's karate strategy.
New York City has a program
to get illegal guns off the street.
Guns for cash.
Where if you have an illegal gun,
you can turn it in,
the government won't ask
any questions,
they give you $200,
that illegal gun is off the street.
When I'm president,
I'm doing the exact same thing nationwide,
except with Ashton Kutcher movies.
If you own a movie
starring Ashton Kutcher,
you can turn it in, no questions asked...
and we will give you $500,000...
and a gun.
Just trying to make America better.
How do you feel about parents
who don't vaccinate their kids?
I don't think anti-vaxers
are anti-science.
I think they are just
pro-diseases' rights.
And it's about time
somebody stands up for bacteria.
Fracking, where do you stand?
For or against it?
I'm for it. I think they're just trying
to kill the devil.
If they drill deep enough one day
they'll hit the devil right in the skull.
I guess you guys are pro-devil.
- Are you all religious? Yes? No?
- No.
It's okay.
How religious are you?
If you see a big building,
do you call it a skyscraper
or heaven tickler, what do you say?
I'm just trying to gauge.
The Bible says
love thy neighbor as thyself.
What if you hate yourself? That's caused
some problems over the years.
I used to think I was Jewish.
And then some Jewish people told me
I wasn't Jewish.
According to a lot of Jewish people,
unless your mom's Jewish,
you're not Jewish. No fucking exceptions.
My name's very Jewish.
My dad's Jewish, but my mom's Catholic.
A lot of Jewish people, when they meet me
think I'm Jewish by their definition,
and when they find out my mom's Catholic
they think I tried to trick them
into thinking I was Jewish
and I'm some kind of evil fake Jew.
According to Hitler,
if one grandparent was Jewish,
he considered you Jewish
and had you sent for extermination.
So, in a way, Hitler was actually
more inclusive of the Jews
than many Jews today.
Racism, where do you stand?
For it or against it?
A lot of undecided.
Racism, big problem,
but we're still number one at it.
Racism is everywhere you look,
it's part of the country's
founding structure,
it's still there
and it's never gonna get better
unless people at least start talking
about it.
It's everywhere you look.
Hollywood's racist.
Anyone know what the first
Hollywood blockbuster ever made was?
- Birth of a Nation.
- Birth of a Nation, 1915,
based on a book called The Clansman.
And in the movie,
the KKK are the good guys.
Hollywood should be like,
"Yeah, we fucked up
on that one, sorry." Start a dialogue.
Then there's a chance
things can get better.
A lot of black people in the movie
are white people in blackface.
Hollywood should be like,
"Yeah, we fucked up there. Sorry."
Hollywood will take a white show
and make it whiter.
Anyone remember the show
Everybody Loves Raymond?
The lead actor, Italian-American,
dark brown hair.
His wife on the show, dark brown hair.
Their three little kids on the show?
All blond.
That's Hollywood taking a white show
and making it whiter.
If they're whitewashing a white show,
imagine what they're doing to any
other show if that show gets a chance.
But that's what Hollywood's about.
It's about thin, blond and white.
So, how do we solve this problem?
We invade Sweden.
We invade Sweden, the blondest,
whitest country in the world,
and everyone will be like,
"Why did America bomb Sweden?"
And we're like,
"Because Hollywood's racist."
That's the American way.
When we have a problem,
we invade the wrong country
and everything is perfect.
Hollywood has made some progress, though.
Uh...
The TV show How to Get Away with Murder
changed its name to Become a Cop.
I was like,
"That's a pretty bold move
coming from a corporate network
like that."
What's your favorite Asian film
Hollywood made?
Mine's The Last Samurai,
starring Tom Cruise.
Good job, Hollywood. Good job there, too.
Racism is everywhere you look.
I think astronauts are racists.
Yeah, I said it, buddy.
- What year did we land on the moon?
- '69.
1969, right at the tail end
of the civil rights era.
Right when black Americans
had been marching and protesting
and getting some legislation passed
so they could get
a bit of human rights.
And a bunch of white guys
got on a rocket and left the planet.
To start an all-white race on the moon.
I'm not even gonna guess
what the N in NASA stands for.
I'm not gonna do it.
And they didn't bring any women
because they were sexist.
They were afraid of being
defeated by a woman
in a no-gravity zone.
So, they made their new home the moon,
or as they called it, "White Junior."
I think the New York City Marathon
is racist.
Ten thousand white people
chasing five Africans.
The most racist sporting display
I have ever seen.
I'm like, "Stop chasing them,
they've done nothing wrong.
And you're not gonna catch them...
you fucking slow racists."
And if you didn't laugh at that,
you might be a fucking slow racist.
I wanna talk terminology for a second.
A question for black people
in the audience,
just to make everyone uncomfortable,
the term black, is it preferred?
Or African-American?
- Hello? Hello?
- Oh, my God.
- Anyone wanna answer the question or...?
- Black is fine.
You like black? Okay.
What about this?
You hear this on the news.
Sometimes the news will refer
to a black person as a person of color.
You don't like that? Okay.
If the news refers
to a black person as a person of color,
they should start referring
to white people as a person without color.
Sad.
Just fearing the sun every day,
praying for the night.
White people are so oppressed,
living on a planet that circles
the very thing they fear every day.
Since the beginning of time.
All right, let's lighten up
the mood a little bit.
Uh... Reparations. Reparations.
Should black Americans
receive reparations?
One person says yes,
the rest of you, fucking racist.
Fucking racist, remember their faces.
I think black Americans
should receive reparations.
How do you think it should be given out?
No ideas?
Nothing?
- Economic allowances.
- Trump Tower!
Economic allowances. Okay.
I was thinking white slavery.
White slavery.
If you're black American,
you can own Donald Trump.
Please!
Or his creepy kid Eric,
he could be a house slave.
Donald, way out in the field.
Far, far, far from the home.
- Whoa, what did you drop?
- A candle.
A candle? Okay.
Sorry, can't relate. I've, uh...
I've never dropped anything before.
I have perfect grip, so just...
I'd like to relate to what
you're going through, but I can't.
I hope you can power through.
- ISIS.
- Are you afraid of ISIS?
- You tell me.
- Yeah, I think you are.
I think that's the reason
you asked the question.
Have you ever had a close call with ISIS?
You ever get home late at night...
honey's like, "How was your day?"
You're like, "Pretty good,
almost got fucked up by ISIS.
Fortunately it worked out."
Nothing to worry about.
That's the news trying to scare you.
The news is talking about something
from another country,
and it's coming here,
so you better be scared.
They do the same thing with diseases.
Like the Zika virus.
It's a disease from another country
and it's coming, so be scared.
Nothing to worry about. Look at me.
I've had Ebola for six weeks.
I'm fucking perfect.
A few years ago it was the swine flu.
When that happened,
I gave a pig the human flu.
Fight back. Fight back.
This country needs to toughen the fuck up.
- Any other issues?
- Citizens United.
I think we should...
Citizens should unite
against Citizens United.
I think...
You just earned yourself
a cabinet position, well done.
I think eventually
everyone gets the death penalty.
It should really be called
the murder penalty.
If you were on death row,
what would you request for your last meal?
Taco Bell.
Okay.
I'd request the finger of the guy
flipping the electric switch.
Buy myself a few extra minutes.
For a beverage I'd request
the blood from the warden's body.
And then my dessert would be freedom.
You see? Strategy, strategy.
You gotta look at the big picture,
not just the short satisfaction.
Europeans and Canadians live longer
than Americans.
Americans die sooner
than Europeans and Canadians.
- And why is that?
- Healthcare.
No, it's because we're efficient.
We get shit done faster.
You Europeans and Canadians are slow,
you're lazy,
you don't know what the fuck you're doing,
and you're greedy.
You're taking all this time to get
shit done, you never accomplish anything.
We get shit done and let it go,
we let the next generation take over.
We're progressive that way, we share,
you know.
Uh, you guys are clock hoggers.
You know, just...
Sexual education?
I don't think it should be part of school.
I, uh...
It should be something you learn
on your own.
It might not work out well,
but you'll remember it better.
Comprehension, very important, everybody.
Very important.
It's not what you learn,
it's how well you learn it.
How do you approach income inequality?
How much you need?
National drinking age.
How old are you?
- How old are you?
- Old enough.
- Twenty-eight.
I'm raising it to 29.
What about North Korea?
Okay, this guy's a spy.
This guy's a spy.
Nobody talk to this guy after the show.
Don't give him a hug,
he'll plant something on you.
He'll plant a tracker or something.
Second row, what's your name?
What do you do?
- Yeah.
- I work in social media.
Social media. What is that?
I help...
I help brands be good at social media.
You help brands be good at social media.
So, what's an example of a brand
being good at social media?
I don't understand.
- It's complicated.
- It's complicated?
So, what are some of these brands?
Bud Light is one.
- Bud Light?
- Yeah.
Does anyone follow Bud Light on Twitter?
Because, you know,
there's lots of stuff
happening in the world these days...
and when I see some breaking news,
I wanna be like,
"What does Bud Light think about this?"
What would your presidential slogan be?
Worst question of the night, sir.
No slogan. It's a movement, buddy.
It's beyond that.
I expected better from you, dude.
- Your running mate.
- What?
- Your running mate?
- I won't have a running mate.
First, I'm not running for president.
I'm standing for president.
Running means you're scared.
And I will not have a VP
because I view having an assistant
as a sign of weakness.
Heroes stand alone and get shit done.
If I had a vice president,
the first thing I'd do in office,
I'd karate kick him in the face.
Let him know
who runs this fucking country.
- Any other issues?
- Term limits.
I think we should have term limits
for citizens.
Everyone gets four years,
and if you do a good job
and your neighbors don't think
you're an asshole
you can stay for another four.
Maybe people would be a little nicer
to each other that way.
We have a lot of weird holidays
in America.
Christopher Columbus Day,
that's a weird one.
It's about the guy, Christopher Columbus,
who discovered America.
Germany, do you have a holiday
about the person who discovered Germany?
No? Then I guess it's not
a country worth celebrating.
It's a weird holiday,
Christopher Columbus Day.
He's the guy, Christopher Columbus,
who discovered America.
Even though there was
millions of people living here
for thousands of years.
He called them Indians.
He thought he landed in India,
but he landed in America.
But he just kept calling them Indians.
They pretty much slaughtered all Indians,
and we have a holiday
celebrating that guy.
That's kind of weird.
How should we celebrate
Christopher Columbus Day?
Here's a thought. You know when you're
in a big building on a high floor
and go down to the lobby,
but the elevator's crowded
and someone else has pressed floor three,
but you weren't paying attention,
so when the elevator stops on floor three
you get off
because you think it's the lobby,
and instead of realizing that
and turning back around
into the crowded elevator
and admitting you're a moron, you're like,
"Hey, sorry, I'm a fucking idiot.
I wasn't paying attention.
I thought it was the lobby."
No, you don't admit it,
you just stay on floor three
and you pretend it's the lobby.
And then you murder everyone
on floor three.
That's how we should celebrate
Christopher Columbus Day.
Just a thought, just a thought.
Thanksgiving, that's an American holiday.
Canada, you celebrate Thanksgiving.
On the wrong day, but you celebrate it.
And, Canada, what are you thankful for?
That you border America.
That's it, that's all you got.
Germany, you don't celebrate Thanksgiving.
It's because you got nothing
to be thankful for.
Always try to remember that.
We celebrate it
because we're such a narcissistic country
we need a holiday to force us
to say thank you once a year.
Because normally we do not say thank you.
We say "you're welcome" a lot.
Often after a country
did not say "thank you."
They usually said,
"Ouch. Cut it out, stop."
And we're like, "You're welcome."
Why do we have turkey on Thanksgiving?
Does anyone know?
Are you completely uneducated?
Nobody knows? It's okay if you don't.
The government doesn't want you
to know the truth.
The real reason we have turkey
on Thanksgiving
is because just 80 years ago
this entire country
was enslaved by turkeys.
And it was not till we invented the baster
we were able to rise up
and conquer the evil turkey.
That's why today on Thanksgiving
not only do we kill and eat a turkey,
we stuff shit up its ass
to humiliate the turkey
and send the message
that it never happens again.
I teach American history part-time online
at Axe Body Spray University.
You guys should definitely
take one of my courses.
What's Christmas about?
- Presents.
- Presents? No.
Jesus.
Wrong again.
- America.
- Nope, it's about killing trees.
Because just 90 years ago,
this entire country was ruled by trees.
And it was not until we invented the ax
that we conquered the tree.
That's why on Christmas,
not only do we kill a tree,
we put it up in our living room by the
window so other trees can see it,
and let them know
we're not fucking around.
Sometimes we put up a fake tree
to let them know
they can be replaced at any time.
And then we give each other presents
to show our human superiority,
and presents are wrapped in paper,
which is made out of trees.
Know your fucking history, people.
Can you believe
that we're the only country
that celebrates the Fourth of July?
America's birthday,
most important holiday on the planet,
and we're the only ones celebrating it.
It's fucked up.
A lot of countries hate America.
Why do some countries hate America?
Let's hear it, foreigners.
We're all friends.
Why do some countries hate America?
They're trying to police the world.
We try to police the world.
Because we bomb countries
that never attack us.
That's what the government refers to
as a nonissue.
Way off, buddy.
The real reason
other countries hate America
is because America
has the greatest cheese in the world.
American cheese is the greatest cheese
on Earth.
That's why each slice
comes in its own protective wrapping.
To preserve and protect
the subtle nuances
and amazing super glory of justice
that is American cheese.
Other countries don't have
the technology to replicate it,
so they're jealous and they hate us.
In France, you get a wedge of Brie,
it's unwrapped,
broken cracker bits,
bloody fingernails.
It's fucking disgusting.
I teach international politics part-time
online at Kambridge, with a K.
You guys should definitely take
one of my courses.
Do you like the zoo?
- No.
- Yeah.
- Why not?
- Because they're slaves.
It's true, they're segregated.
In theory the zoo is nice,
but you go, it's segregated.
You have gazelles fenced in here...
lemurs caged in over here.
That's why one day
I'll open up my own zoo.
One room, every animal out for themselves.
With a naked guy in the middle
trying to get out alive.
That's a zoo.
I'll have some gorillas
playing tug-of-war with an anaconda,
100 chickens attacking a giraffe.
That's a zoo. That's right,
I'm having chickens in my zoo.
They're the underclass
of the animal world.
I'm also gonna have pigeons,
or as you might call them, homeless birds.
What animal don't you see at the zoo?
The cow.
But what do you see at the zoo?
A snack bar,
where you get a cheeseburger.
So, cows are at the zoo,
just in a different presentation.
We have a lot of problems in this country,
but we gotta appreciate the progress
that we have made in certain areas.
Twins, for example,
today have full rights.
Forty years ago,
twins had no rights in this country.
Forty years ago, you could kill a twin,
it wouldn't matter.
On trial for murder,
judge would be like, "You killed a man."
You go, "Yeah, Your Honor, but there's
a fucking other one right there."
And he'd be like, "Oh, my bad."
Then they'd just let you off.
But today, twins are safe.
It's still legal to kill a triplet
in this country, but twins are safe.
- What are you doing later tonight, buddy?
- Tonight?
Catch up with some mates,
smoke some weed. Pretty nice.
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I got a copy of Planet of the Apes,
and tonight I'm gonna break into the zoo
and screen it for the apes.
Start a revolution.
Humans made a film about the apes
but never showed it to the apes.
That's not right.
Tonight, that's gonna change.
Do you wanna go?
Sorry, apes only.
This is their time.
I'm actually going on vacation tomorrow.
I'm excited, going away for three weeks.
- It's gonna be great.
- Where you going?
Coney Island. Coney Island.
For three weeks, gonna away from it all.
Just relax, get some culture.
Who knows? Maybe hook up with
some island girls. See how it goes.
You gotta see the world, people.
Well, I expect all of your votes tomorrow.
Yep.
You guys have done a great job tonight.
Sir, you started out
as the worst audience member...
and you worked your way
up to the bottom 20 percent.
I always knew
you had that kind of potential.
Sir, I did not talk to you...
because I don't like you.
I think you have a serious
attitude problem.
As a matter of fact, nobody make
eye contact with him after the show.
Well...
I recommend that you guys, uh,
stick around after the show
and watch the credits.
I heard they're really cool.
Other questions before I go?
Any other questions?
Any other issues?
- Trade.
- Trade?
I'm gonna trade you
for another audience member.
Any other issues before I go?
- Marijuana.
- Immigration.
Marijuana, immigration,
good combination question.
Only immigrants get to smoke pot.
Yeah!
Any other issues?
The environment.
You for it or against it?
I don't understand the question.
As president I will keep the environment.
I will not deport the environment
or put a roof up over the country
or a sky wall
as some people are asking for.
I think climate change won the Cold War.
When I'm president
I'm gonna move the border every day.
Keep this country on its toes.
I might have it go
through Cincinnati one morning.
They'll be like, "What is going on?"
I'll be like, "Should've checked
the border app on your phone."
Any other questions? Other questions?
- Prison system.
- What about the prison system?
We have one of the most diverse
prison systems in the world.
Outsourcing in automation.
Are you a robot or a human?
Describe your perfect day.
Anything where that doesn't happen.