[host] The Hangover...
[cheering]
Community...
Dr. Ken...
Crazy Rich Asians...
Give it up for Ken Jeong!
[crowd cheering]
[rock song playing in the background]
♪ I said the joker is a wanted man ♪
-[mouthing along]
-♪ He makes his way all across the land ♪
♪ See him sifting through the sand ♪
♪ So I'll tell you all the story ♪
♪ About the joker
and the thief of the night ♪
[music stops]
Oooooh!
Goddamn!
Thank you so much!
[crowd screaming]
Fuck!
Oh, my God, I don't even know what to say.
-This is--
-[woman] I love you, Ken!
I love you too, bitch.
I do.
This is my first...
This is my first stand-up special ever.
So, thank you, guys.
-[crowd cheering]
-Ever!
This is the club
where I got my start, man!
It's... The Ice House is like, amazing.
We're like family.
I wanted to do my first Netflix special
in a club
because every Netflix special
you fucking see is in an auditorium.
It's in a big theater.
And, I tell you, live comedy
begins in the motherfucking clubs.
We want to keep that shit real!
Club folk.
And it's an honor for me to entertain
the lowers.
Now...
[crowd laughing]
[Ken imitates laugh]
Anyway, some people may know this,
some people not...
I used to be a doctor...
...at Kaiser-fucking-Permanente.
[crowd cheers]
And then I said, "Fuck that shit!
I'll be naked and famous in a movie,
make some moolah."
And that is what makes America great.
Am I right, guys?
My God! My God!
I was a general practitioner, all right?
We are the dumbest of all doctors,
all right?
Like, in general, we knew nothing.
We're stupid, okay?
Like, if a patient came up to me and said,
"What do I have?"
"Well, in general, you're sick,
so I'll refer you to a specificist."
Do you know what I mean?
"I don't know. See someone else.
I'm a day drunk, all right?
Welcome to Kaiser."
Anyway...
I'm kidding.
Dude, Dr. Ken, that show I was on...
I modeled that HMO after Kaiser.
Dude, everything about Kaiser...
I owe my livelihood to Kaiser Permanente.
Actually, I met my wife at work,
all right?
She's a doctor.
She's Vietnamese.
Doctor... Last name, "Ho."
I'm not fucking making that shit up.
I married a "Ho," okay?
[crowd cheers]
Dude, that's like a wet dream to a comic.
I can say anything the fuck I want,
and it's street-legal,
you know what I mean?
"Get in the car, Ho!" I can say that.
"Make me some rice, Ho!"
[crowd laughs]
"You complete me, Ho." You know?
I can say that because I'm sensitive,
by the way.
And Koreans, we're the most sensitive
people on the fucking planet.
Where are the Koreans in the house?
Koreans in the house?
[scattered cheering]
Yeah, we are
the hottest-tempered of all Asians.
We are the angriest of all the...
[Ken speaks in Korean]
That means "Hello" in Korean.
All right, so...
You're Vietnamese?
Just out of curiosity,
what's your last name?
-Ho.
[crowd laughs]
Don't you ever upstage me again, Ho.
Don't you ever be funnier than me, Ho.
How dare you?
This is my Netflix special, Ho!
[crowd laughs]
What's your first name?
-What's your first name?
-Tran.
Is your real name--
Is your first name "Tran"?
My wife's fucking first name is Tran!
-Really?
-Yeah, my wife's fucking first name
is Tran-fucking-Ho!
[crowd laughs]
What do you do for a living?
And if you say "doctor,"
I'm going to fuck myself, all right?
You're not a doctor, right?
Fuck me.
[crowd cheering]
-What the fuck? Is your last--
-Ho.
Your last-- Are you fucking kidding me?
Your last name is fucking "Ho"?
Fuck you Hos, all right?
Fuck the Hos!
Someone in the back
is fucking with me right now.
Because there's Hos to the left of me,
Hos to the right of me.
And my real-life wife, Ho,
is in the fucking back!
This is like...
[crowd claps]
Are you fucking kidding me?
This is a Bizarro Ho universe.
I don't know what's going on.
Your last name is also "Ho"?
Are you Vietnamese?
-No.
-Oh, good.
Thank God, okay. All right.
It wasn't a complete setup.
-What nationality are you?
-Singaporean.
Singaporean!
[crowd cheers]
Crazy-rich Asians in the motherfucker!
Fucking Crazy Rich Asians fans!
Singapore!
Fuck me, man!
Thank you, man.
Crazy Rich Asians, or as we call it,
"Yellow Panther."
Now...
Or "Golden Retriever." I'll think of...
I'll figure out the animal.
"Yellow Kitty."
No, too on the nose. Now...
My God.
Fucking Vietnamese...
I tell you, the way they talk
is just a little bit...
A little feyish, a little dandy.
[Ken speaking in foreign language]
You know what I'm saying, right?
Vietnamese is Koreans on weed.
That's all I'm saying, okay?
[Ken speaking in foreign language]
And that is how I came up with Chow.
Now...
[crowd laughs and claps]
[Ken imitates laughter]
I actually would sprinkle in Vietnamese
just to make my wife laugh.
In the movie, in the first Hangover,
when we release Black Doug,
that's all Vietnamese, where I say...
They thought that means,
"Release Black Doug."
It actually means in Vietnamese,
"Chicken, die."
So, it was like...
I really was doing stuff
to make the Ho laugh, so...
[crowd laughs]
And it's equal-opportunity Hos.
You can laugh at that joke, too.
For my first movie...
I actually booked this while working
at Kaiser.
...was Knocked Up, that was directed
by Judd Apatow and Seth Rogen.
Thank you!
The first movie I ever did,
and I shot that shit
while still having my day job.
I shot that during a vacation week
because I'm a good fucking Asian.
You know what I mean?
I'm responsible.
And it was the most creatively fulfilling
experience of my life at that time,
because I got to work with everybody.
Anybody who's anybody is in that movie,
dude.
You had Seth Rogen,
Paul Rudd, Leslie Mann,
Jonah Hill, Jason Segel,
Martin Starr of Silicon Valley,
Craig Robinson, Charlyne Yi...
You had, like,
Bill Hader and Kristen Wiig...
It was The Avengers of comedy,
that's what that shit was.
And I swear to God, the first time I shot
my last day of filming,
it was such a dream.
Judd Apatow said to me, he goes,
"You are my discovery.
You did such a great job.
I'm going to put you in all of my movies."
And he did.
So, I would not be here...
if it wasn't for Judd.
[crowd cheers]
And then the next day
I had to work at Kaiser,
you know what I mean?
I mean, that's how I came up with
the Chow jizz-toss...
"Kaiser."
Toodle-oo, hopes and dreams.
You know?
Like, can you imagine having a moment
like that?
Doing a John Apatow film
and going back to your day job
thinking that you're stuck.
The next day,
I could not stop thinking about that.
I was like,
"Well, maybe right now I'm playing it safe
but maybe it's time for this college kid
to turn pro, you know what I mean?
Maybe I got to fucking...
I got to rethink my life!
Maybe this is the time for me
to pursue acting, full-time.
But, you know, look at me.
I know I look like a fucking
double-chinned Asian Mr. Burns
with bad posture, but I don't know.
I mean, maybe this is the time for me.
Maybe this is a sign."
By the way, I'm thinking all this
while 50 patients are waiting for me.
Not a good look.
[crowd laughs]
And my nurse is desperately trying
to get me to focus.
She goes, "Dr. Jeong, you have a patient
in Room 2 waiting for you."
And I'm like, "Well, nurse, you have
a doctor who doesn't give a fuck."
[crowd laughs]
"I just did a movie, Carol!
I just did a movie, man.
You don't get it."
And, believe it or not,
I quit my day job the next day.
True story.
[crowd claps]
I was scared, man.
I was fucking scared.
Because I didn't have any family support.
Like, my strict traditional Korean dad
who wanted me to be a doctor
before I was born...
No, he was severely
bumping on this shit, dude.
He was just cursing me out in Korean.
[mutters]
"You bring great shame to Jeong family!"
And then after The Hangover...
"We are so proud!
I knew you'd make it, boy!
I knew you'd make it! I believe in you."
[crowd cheers]
"We are so proud of your tiny ding-dong.
So proud.
The smaller the penis,
the bigger the box office!"
[Ken evilly laughs]
Thanks, Papa. Great praise, okay.
And, yes, for those of you wondering,
in The Hangover,
yes, that was real in the trunk.
I'm a grower not a show-er, all right?
It was cold, I swear. All right?
It was cold outside, all right?
But I'm secure about it.
It's how the pencil writes, bitch.
It's how it writes!
Mine can write in cursive.
In cursive!
Oh my God, calligraphy!
Calligraphy! Konnichiwa, bitch!
[crowd claps]
But I tell you, man,
to be Hangover rich and famous
as an Asian kid, man...
Asian parents,
they don't know how to govern that.
You know, my dad went from "father"
to "freeloader," just like that.
[crowd laughs]
I swear to God, as a kid, he was like,
"You better get me good grades!"
After The Hangover,
"You better get me S-Class Mercedes!
Because E-Class,
that's for fucking farmers."
Okay, Papa. Good.
Dude, I would not be here
if it wasn't for the fucking Hangover.
Mr. Chow is the best character
I've ever played.
He's the funniest character ever.
It put me on the map.
Dude...
Leslie Chow.
I mean, it has brought me so much joy.
The Hangover is
the best thing ever to happen
not only to my career,
but my fucking life.
That's why I don't mind getting
recognized for Mr. Chow wherever I go.
Literally, if anyone asks for a photo
or a selfie, I'm always nice about it.
If you look on Twitter,
I'm always nice doing Mr. Chow stuff
because I'm dead inside.
Now...
You guys wanna hear
some Hangover stories?
[crowd cheers in excitement]
All right.
I live in Los Angeles, the rich part,
and I'll tell you...
[audience member] Where?
I'm not going to tell you where, bitch.
I'm not going to tell you
I live in Calabasas.
Don't worry, I can say it.
It's a gated community.
It's fine.
You ain't getting in. It's fine.
You ain't getting in, bitch.
[crowd cheers]
Okay, I was at a Wells Fargo ATM,
withdrawing some cash.
A lot of cash!
And this middle-aged white guy,
this, like, motherfucking guy
with a bald head...
No offense, dude. I'm just like...
Hey, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Dennis, get a load of this guy.
Oh, my God,
that's fucking Locke from Lost over there.
he's got the secret to the hatch!
Look at that guy! Fucking Lost.
Oh, my God.
He's like an ugly Locke from Lost.
And I'm an ugly Daniel Dae Kim,
so it all works out fine.
Daniel Dae "Chins," maybe.
And this fucking white "Ho"-looking
motherfucker
is looking at me from a sedan
with the window half-cracked open.
True story. He's staring at me,
and I'm withdrawing some cash.
Staring at me, withdrawing some cash.
The light turns green so he can go,
"Toodle-oo, motherfucker!"
Every fucking day, you know what I mean?
I was on a plane promoting Hangover II.
First class.
And, uh...
True story.
There's a person in the back of the plane
and there were concerns
he may have had a stroke.
He had some vertigo,
he had some dizziness,
some weakness,
a little bit of slurred speech,
and the flight attendant
was understandably panicked.
"Is there a doctor on the plane?
Is there a doctor on the plane?"
So, you know, I raise my hand
and I was like, "Well, I, um...
Well, it's complicated but..."
[crowd laughs]
"But I used to be a doctor."
She was like, "Sit down, Chow. Jesus."
"Catch that, Phyllis?"
Everyone's laughing at me on the plane.
Dude, even the strokie
in the back of the plane...
Making a bubble
with his drool or something.
But I was promoting Hangover II,
which, actually, I think is
my favorite Hangover movie,
because the cinematography was
absolutely amazing in Bangkok, Thailand.
Anyone from Thailand?
Oh, really?
-Yeah.
-You're a Thai!
-That's awesome. Where are you from?
-Bangkok.
Bangkok!
You look so cute! Look!
Natey, get a shot of him, man!
Look at that!
You know what I call this?
Son of Chow. He looks amazing.
[crowd laughs]
Own that shit, boy.
-What's your name, man?
-Mike.
Mike. What's your last name?
Bayakorbachik.
[crowd laughs]
You're not Thai.
You're Jewish.
[crowd laughs]
I mean, what do you think, Tran?
Do you think that's legit?
I don't know. You're kind of my wife, now.
I don't know.
Why do I feel like the Asians are
getting back at me for some reason?
Not to get off on a fucking tangent, dude.
This is not even related.
But you know what? I got so much shit
from the Asian community
for the first Hangover.
That was controversial at that time,
like, 10 years ago.
Because, seriously,
I had fucking Asian haters, dude.
Asian haters on the internet,
they're the fucking worst, dude.
White trolls are bad.
But Asian trolls,
they're the stickiest, dude.
No, no. For real.
This is a real comment.
I'm not making this up.
This is a real comment
from someone on Reddit,
and is still up there, all right?
You can look it up.
"Ken, if I ever see you in public,
I will choke you within a few seconds
from death
with my bare hands.
Fuck you, you piece of shit
do-anything-for-a-dollar whore."
And that was my mom, all right?
[crowd laughs]
I tell you,
these fucking Asian haters, man.
They hate themselves, dude.
They fucking hated the fact
I had a thick accent
and I had a small penis, dude.
I was born with that shit!
That's not a stereotype!
That's fucking real to me!
How are they mad?
And they want me to apologize for that?
What do I say? "Me so sorry?"
I don't know what to say!
My God!
Dude, I get so much shit for The Hangover!
I did a lot of social justice
in The Hangover!
I was a social justice warrior
in that shit.
Think about that.
I jumped out of a trunk and beat up
the white man three times, all right?
[crowd cheers]
I should be the fucking Malcolm X
of my community.
Not yellow Urkel, all right?
There are Asian teenage boys
that actually blame me.
They think they can't get laid
by white women
because somehow my small dick
has scared the white chick away.
People say that about me!
Dude, stop rejecting this papa shit.
Maybe you're too bold like your father,
never satisfied like your mother,
and that, bitch, is when doves cry, okay?
I loved shooting in Bangkok.
We were there for two months.
I went with my wife and we were there...
Remember that, sweetie?
I remember that.
Good times, right?
[crowd laughs]
And, in the photo credits at the end,
when you're looking at
the forgotten night,
there's a stripper, a nude stripper
that has a ping pong ball.
I don't know if you remember that scene.
She has a ping pong ball,
and she's putting that up her hootch,
and it's coming out like she's
the Serena Williams of pussy pong.
It was a sight to behold.
Like, boom, boom, boom.
And I'm not even kidding,
on the first take,
it hit Bradley Cooper in the mouth.
I'm not even kidding.
[crowd cheers]
That is gospel.
And then, stupid me,
I'm going, "Syphilis, hot boy!"
'Cause that's what I do.
You know what I mean?
That's what I do, you know?
But my whole point is,
a lot of people are asking
like, you know, "Do you have to
do medicine on a movie set
or in a comedy club or anything?"
All the fucking time. I always have...
Dude, so many times I go into doctor mode.
It's like Godfather 3.
"Just when I think I'm out,
they pull me back in," you know?
Everywhere, you know?
Recently, I was at a club in Phoenix.
I don't know if you heard about this.
A lady in the third row had a seizure
in one of my stand-up shows.
It wasn't because of a bad joke,
I'm just saying...
But TMZ reported this,
and my publicist didn't want me
to talk about it, which I didn't.
But I want you to hear,
for the first time, on Netflix,
me talk about it in my own words,
all right?
I'm making fun of people
like I normally do in my act.
"Hos to the left of me,
Hos to the right to me..."
So I'm doing my schtick,
like Asian Don Rickles,
and there's a lady...
[crowd laughs]
There was a lady in the third row,
and she was, like, "Mr. Chow! Mr. Chow!"
I'm, like, "Calm down, bitches.
I'll get to you, it'll be fine."
And they were, like,
"No, someone passed out."
And a lady fell down off her chair
and she was just completely out.
And I dropped the mic,
and I rushed over there,
and went into "doctor" mode,
and it was the most surreal,
sublime experience ever,
because I'm no longer a comedian,
I'm a doctor.
And the whole comedy club were no longer
like a comedy club audience.
We're like an ER of, like,
nurses and aides trying to help her out.
It was so fucking amazing.
And I'm thinking to myself, like,
"Oh my God, I may have to do CPR
on this person."
And I have to assess the ABCs
before you do CPR.
You know,
"Airway," "Breathing," "Circulation."
Not "Always Be Closing."
It's a different thing.
And I actually... If you go on YouTube,
I have done work with the
American Heart Association,
teaching medical students and nurses
how to do hands-only compression CPR.
You don't have to do
mouth-to-mouth anymore.
So it's true. This is a medical fact.
I have two medical facts, all right?
Number one...
The number one medical fact,
look, if you're ever in the position where
unfortunately, you may have to do CPR,
you do chest compressions
to the beat of "Stayin' Alive," all right?
It's like, Ah, ah, ah, ah,
Stayin' alive, stayin' alive
[crowd laughs]
It's true.
[crowd claps]
And I'm thinking to myself,
"Am I gonna have to Bee Gee this bitch?"
And then, fortunately, I did not have to.
She got up quickly.
She had what they call
a "petit mal" seizure.
She's on medication and she had a history
of epilepsy.
By the way,
she allowed me to tell this story.
Her name is Christy.
I actually flew her out
to one of my shows in New York.
She is doing fine.
So everything... Happy ending alert.
Everything is good.
But when we sat her up,
we actually did a mental status exam
with an audience member
who happened to be a paramedic,
and we were asking her questions
because she's a little bit confused
after the seizure.
She was like, "What's your name?"
"Christy."
"Where are you?"
"Phoenix."
"Who are you here to see?"
And then she turns and looks at me,
and then she vomits.
So, it's a normal response.
And within minutes, the paramedics
take care of her and she's fine.
My whole point is,
if you don't like any of my shit,
you don't have to have a fucking seizure,
and a fucking...
You can just walk out, bitch.
I already got paid.
I already got the check.
And you know what?
That's not even
my worst seizure tale, all right?
Dude, I did Ride Along 2
with Ice Cube and Kevin Hart,
and we were shooting in a nightclub
in Atlanta.
Four hundred background actors
in a nightclub
and a person has a severe
generalized tonic-clonic seizure
and the whole nightclub clears out.
So, I'm running towards the patient
and Ice Cube, who is the baddest
motherfucker on the planet...
He's amazing!
He's fucking running
towards the patient, too,
We're like two outfielders
going for the same ball.
And I tell you, he's taking out a belt.
I'm like,
"Whoa, you don't whip the patient, Cube!
No!"
I don't know him.
I'm more of a Reba McEntire fan.
And he's running out to the patient,
and he gets to him before I do.
He puts the belt
around the patient's mouth,
so he wouldn't choke on his tongue.
Ice Cube, not me,
saved the patient's life.
-It was amazing!
-[cheering]
Just a shout-out to Cube.
And to make small talk,
I was like, "So, Ice Cube,
I guess that was a good day."
While Kevin Hart ran away.
"Oh, my God! Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ! Oh, my God!
Snap, crackle, pop!
I gotta get the fuck out of here!"
"Calm down, your snappy midget!
Everything is fine."
Everything.
And by the way, it was Kevin Hart
who actually got me into doing
stand-up again in the first place.
No joke. Yes. Shout-out to Kevin.
He's one of my dear friends.
He's one of my favorite guys in comedy
because he's the only one
shorter than me.
[crowd laughs]
He literally would give me advice.
I mean, Kevin, literally,
every day on Ride Along 2,
he would just remind me,
"You got to do stand-up."
Because we go back 15 years.
And I love when Kevin Hart gives me advice
because he's the only guy looking up,
you know what I mean?
It's just so great.
And I call him "Rice Krispies"
because he's just always making
snap-crackle-pop noises
wherever he goes.
"Oh, man, Ken! Snap, crackle, pop, man!
You gotta go back!
Gotta go back and do stand-up, man!
You're leaving millions on the table, man!
Snap, crackle, pop, ping, pang, pow!
Ping, pang, pow! You gotta do that!
You gotta do stand-up,
and do it like this!
And then you gotta do it like this!
Then maybe you can do it like this!
I gotta do it, man! Ping, pang, pow!"
I was like, "Oh, you're so cute.
Of course I'll do it for you.
I will do it, you're so cute.
Come here, give me a hug."
A lot of people ask me, like,
"Do you still practice medicine?"
I'm like, you know, "Why?"
I mean, look at me, dude.
Like, yeah, sure, I want to get sued
every chance I get.
At Kaiser, depositions were my jam.
Sure, my wife's also a doctor.
Yeah, sure, we want to work
every other week, every major holiday.
We would never see each other, sure.
I want that lifestyle back.
Yeah, sure, I want to voluntarily
put my finger up the holes
of every patient that I see,
willy-fucking-nilly.
[crowd laughs]
Dude, I'm Hollywood, bitch.
I got out of Shawshank, all right?
West Side!
But I will say shit
doctors are afraid to say, all right?
Just a couple of tips.
Stop Googling your shit before you see
the doctor.
It never works!
I had a patient come up to me,
and the patient was like,
"Oh, I looked it up online,
I have right-sided pain.
It's an ovarian cyst."
"You're a dude. Knock it off, all right?"
[crowd laughs]
Okay, ladies...
Okay, get ready, all right?
Ladies, when you see your doctor
for a pap smear,
and this is with all due respect,
make it presentable.
That's all we're saying.
Less Chewbacca, more Ewok, all right?
We don't want That '70s Show up in here.
You don't want to have what we call
a General Ackbar situation
from Star Wars: Return of the Jedi.
You know that fish-mouthed alien?
That was named after a dank vajayjay.
It was.
Because when you put your speculum in,
it goes, "It's a trap!"
You don't want that.
[crowd laughs]
So, to answer your question...
No, I don't do medicine anymore.
[crowd laughs]
No, man, I've gotten to meet everybody
from The Hangover.
I mean, literally, I just got to meet
everybody I've ever wanted to meet.
I got to meet my favorite actor
in the world, Tom Hanks,
at the Golden Globes.
That was amazing.
He's my favorite actor in the world.
By the way, did you think that
my voice as Mr. Chow was my real accent?
Okay.
Tom Hanks... I met him, I said hello.
And Tom was, like,
"Really? You don't talk like that?"
I'm like.
"Really, fucking Forrest Gump? Really?
Are you fucking kidding me?
[crowd cheers]
Do you walk around carrying
a box of fucking chocolates
while talking to a Wilson volleyball,
you Cast Away motherfucker?
I got to meet presidents
because of The Hangover.
I met Bill Clinton while we were
doing Hangover II.
We were in Bangkok.
Clinton was also in Bangkok,
doing God-knows-what.
That's Slick Willie for you,
you know what I mean?
If Obama
is a high school principal,
Bill Clinton is a PE coach
slipping you some ganja,
going, "Don't tell anyone, okay?"
[crowd laughs]
But he has the highest IQ of any
modern-day US president.
He's a political genius.
There is no one more politically smart
than Bill Clinton.
He is so convincing, he is so charismatic,
he is so engaging.
I went to a fundraiser...
He was so persuasive,
I would suck his dick.
I really would.
Just give me a blue dress.
I fucking dare you.
[Ken hums the National Anthem]
I'm sucking his dick for freedom, guys.
And jiggling his balls
for the environment.
I got to meet Obama, which was amazing.
Yes!
Obama.
Not Barack. His half-brother Fred
who runs a Macy's in Queens.
Now...
No, I got to meet Obama
with Zach Galifianakis
who played Alan in The Hangover,
who by the way...
Zach Galifianakis is the
funniest motherfucker alive.
He's my favorite actor
I've ever worked with because...
Like Kevin Hart, we all go way back
doing stand-up comedy.
And when he was doing it,
I always hated following him
because he was always
the funniest guy in the room.
But here we are at the White House,
meeting the sitting president
of the United States
and I have to follow him again.
I'm like, "Fuck, dude!"
Because Zach comes with jokes, man.
He comes loaded with jokes,
and this is the first time
Obama and Zach had met
before they did
the Between Two Ferns thing.
So they were instantly...
Dude, they were on. They were simpatico.
I was watching their fucking comedy
kinship from the beginning.
Zach whips out a two-dollar bill,
and goes,
"Do you have change for this,
for this photo session?"
and Obama is laughing so hard, going,
"Very droll, Zach, Very droll."
And I'm standing to the side
in a suit and a tie
because I'm a good fucking Asian,
you know what I mean?
I'm standing with a suit and a tie
and I'm having what I call my
"Google Image resting face," all right?
Because when you Google-Image
search me, you always get this...
[crowd laughs]
[crowd claps]
And by the way, when it says
"Wear a suit and a tie,"
that's what you do, you know?
Zach is such a rock star,
he's wearing a T-shirt, Toughskins
and some fucking Crocs
and he's like POTUS's
favorite son, all of a sudden.
And then it's my turn. I can't follow him.
I don't have jokes.
I just want to do my photo
and get the fuck out of there.
Obama's like... He looks at the card.
I don't know if he knows who I am.
He's looking at me.
I'm right there.
Secret Service is right there.
He goes, "Oh."
And he does his whole drawl...
[he drawls]
"Oh, it's Ken! Hmm, yeah.
We like Ken, don't we?"
I'm like, "What?"
So, I walk in, he puts his arm around me,
and I'm just...
Same face.
[crowd laughs]
And he's disappointed at me because,
unlike Zach, I'm not doing anything.
His exact words,
"Come on, man. Loosen up, man.
You're a little stiff, man."
Literally, Galifianakis comes in
and he goes,
"This is how
you entertain the president, Ken."
And he and Obama proceed
to verbally roast me for five minutes.
It was a roast battle.
It was like fucking Jeselnik and Ross.
Like, fucking...
It was like...
They were telling me to loosen up.
And I'm like, "Well, I suppose
I could loosen up my tie."
And Obama, I swear to God,
he said the driest...
He said, "No, I've seen your work.
No nudity.
It's a family affair, a family show."
[crowd laughs]
And that's why I voted for Trump. Now...
Because he's a great guy.
Not racist, rarely tweets.
I got a Trump story, too, man.
I had a... I could have met him.
We were both booked to be on Jimmy Fallon
together, a couple of years ago,
when he was a presumptive
Republican nominee,
and I was the second guest.
Dude, I am scared of Trump.
Asians are fucking scared of Trump
like Godzilla.
We are just fucking scared.
Dude, when Trump got elected,
my daughter Zoey...
She was just like,
"Oh, my God. Do we have to bow to him?"
I swear to God. And I'm, like,,
"Yes. Yes, you do, Zoey."
Get your "bow" game on, bitch.
He's the president, all right?
But I was so scared to meet him.
I'm really frightened to meet him.
And they're like, fucking, "Why, dude?"
I'm like, "Think about it, okay?"
Stay with me for a second, all right?
He's a big Hangover fan,
and wanted to meet me.
He's seen my fucking big bush
in The Hangover, all right?
He's seen me naked.
He's seen my shiitake mushroom.
You know what I mean? Just stay with me.
What if he gets really horny and shit?
You just don't know. Horny or hangry
or whatever the fuck he gets.
When he gets aroused,
all that Access Hollywood shit came out.
What if he wants to grab
my almost-pussy, guys?
I don't want to get "Me Too-ed"'
by the president!
[crowd laughs]
And that is when Ken Jeong became woke.
You know, you don't want that.
Don't worry, that's not going to make it
in the special.
It'll be fine.
Because I don't think he's going to be
around for that long, so...
I swear to fucking God.
[crowd cheers and claps]
When Obama is speaking, he goes,
"How hard is it to condemn Nazism?
How hard is it after Charlottesville
to condemn racism?"
You know, he's appeasing to his
racist alt-right base and shit.
Even the racists are like,
"Dude, tone it down, Donnie!
Dude, we get it!"
Even David Duke,
"Whoa, save some racism for us!
We get it. This is not how you're racist."
For real, I was in Palm Springs,
all right? Two hours south of here,
thinking that would be safe,
and I got fucking heckled by
a Trump white-trash supporter, man.
I've never been heckled
by white trash before!
I was just like...
And it gave me no end of pleasure
to say, "As a minority millionaire..."
[crowd laughs]
[crowd cheers]
...you can suck on these Chinese nuts!"
[crowd claps]
"And I'm Korean."
All right, all right.
Gonna get all that...
We'll shake that off, shake that off.
I'll be back as
Mr. Chow, Mr. Chow, Mr. Chow.
-You guys watch Dr. Ken?
-Yeah!
[crowd claps]
And that's why it got canceled. Now...
If I'm going to be honest with you
right now...
This is the most honest I'll ever be,
It is like...
Seriously, our show got canceled
about a year ago,
and I honestly am still down about it.
I am so sad about it.
I created that show.
I was a writer on that show,
executive producer on that show.
We had five Asian-American people of color
on an ABC series.
It was my biggest accomplishment
of my career.
And I'll tell you,
as a guy who had 44 episodes of that show
and I put my heart and life and blood
and sweat into that show.
What could be worse?
I mean, this was like the worst thing
that ever happened to a Hollywood guy,
losing his Hollywood show.
How life could get--
How worse could life get than that?
So there I am, sobbing in my mansion,
eating some Pad Thai
yelling at my houseboy.
And I don't have any gigs upcoming.
I don't have anything.
I have nothing planned.
I was like, "Jesus Christ.
I hope I don't have to go back and do
stand-up at the Ice House or something."
I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy.
You know what I mean? I would hate that.
But then the moment Dr. Ken got canceled,
I got a call from the director of
Crazy Rich Asians.
[crowd cheers]
And literally within an hour,
I'm on a plane to Singapore,
a 17-hour flight...
And, by the way... To shoot my first scene
in Crazy Rich Asians...
And, by the way, that movie is the first
all-Asian-American cast...
Twenty-five years in a Hollywood film...
...since The Joy Luck Club.
Think about this,
my first scene I shot that movie,
the first scene, 24 hours prior,
Dr. Ken had just been canceled.
So, to me, that's all I see when I see
that movie.
And that movie got me
through everything.
Because you know what?
Director Jon M. Chu let me improvise.
All that shit
was just off the top of my head.
Me and...
Me and Aquafina...
Aquafina...
is my daughter.
I love her so much.
I'm Papa-fina to her Aquafina.
We both improvised that shit.
I mean, we were just on a fucking...
It was so therapeutic.
None of that shit was in the script.
Cal State Fullerton is my...
-[crowd cheers]
-You know what I mean?
That's my new "Toodle-oo, motherfuckers,"
you know what I mean?
But it was amazing that I got to
improvise that whole scene
and get away with it.
I mean, it was, like, crazy.
We didn't pay attention to the script
to the point where the director was like,
"What the fuck," you know?
And then you jump-cut a year later.
It is the number one movie,
three weeks in a row.
[crowd cheers]
Insane.
None of us expected that.
To have so much representation
on the screen
means everything to me,
because that's all I wanted Dr. Ken to be.
I wanted Dr. Ken to show
more Asian-Americans on the screen,
and in Crazy Rich Asians,
they did it in such grand style.
Crazy Rich Asians actually allowed me
to let go of Dr. Ken.
So, everything's so full-circle
and so therapeutic.
And what makes it even more full circle
is that the director of Crazy Rich Asians
is in the back,
directing my Netflix special right now.
[crowd cheers]
All right, you don't have to clap
that fucking hard, all right?
It's my fucking show.
All right, my whole point is,
the moral of the story is that
I'm a rich person who just got richer.
Now... Yay, me. Yay, me.
Uptown problems.
All right.
This is how comedians fucking get ready
for their big show.
They have a list of jokes, because
this is how a real comedian does it.
You know, I'm just gonna...
You'll see me just look at some
of my stuff, like a good fucking Asian.
Just kind of like a...
After Dr. Ken, I had a lot of free time,
so I actually went and did jury duty
in Van Nuys.
[crowd cheers]
And what is the point of being famous if
you can't get out of fucking jury duty?
True story, it was a murder trial.
The defendant recognized me.
[crowd laughs]
And he looks at me, like...
"Oh, shit!"
[crowd laughs]
"But did you die?"
"Your honor, sidebar, your honor, please.
Your honor, I can't serve on this jury.
I can't put a fan in jail.
It'll ruin my brand, all right?"
And she's like, "Trust me, a lot
of your fans are in the clink, so..."
Nailed it.
[crowd laughs]
What I loved about doing Dr. Ken
is that I got to actually put
my daughter on the show.
I actually have two kids.
I have two daughters.
Alexa, named after the Amazon Echo...
and Zoey,
named after Kravitz or Deschanel,
depending if you're black or white.
Now...
I got Zoey on the show.
She played the stalker to my TV son.
And her name was Emily
and she is funnier than me.
I actually am kind of like a...
I'm like a tiger mom of Asian...
Like, I want my daughter to be an actor,
I won't lie to you.
Because I think she's funnier than me
and I was really wanting her to...
And she was so good on the show,
to the point that ABC wanted to
make her a series regular.
It was so exciting.
I went up to Zoey. I said, "Oh, my God!"
Isn't it amazing?
Do you want to be on more Dr. Ken?"
She was like, "Do I have to?"
Like, what the fuck?
"You got a fresh-off-the-boat offer
I don't know about, or...?"
[crowd laughs]
"Are you leveraging me
to get on Black-ish, bitch? I mean..."
No, it turned out she just wants to be
a normal kid, man.
She just doesn't even want to be an actor.
She just wants to chart her own path,
not unlike me when I told my father
I wanted to chart my own path.
So, far be it for me
to deny my daughter that opportunity.
So I wrote her out of the show
and it was a great exit scene,
and my wife and I
were just standing, watching her.
She did such an amazing job
and as a father, I couldn't be more proud
of my independent daughter.
But as a producer, if she ever decides to
get back in the game,
I'll fucking crush her, all right?
[crowd laughs]
I get a lot of stuff where people think
I'm kind of the model minority
and it's a lot of... I don't know.
I guess it's a little heavy for me
because, think about it...
Like, oh, you're a doctor,
you're an actor, you're a comedian,
you're an Instagram model.
You can do all of these things.
And the truth of the matter, man...
Like, no, when I was in med school, dude,
I almost failed out of med school
three times, dude.
I was not a smart medical student.
I actually failed my board entrance exams,
like, three times.
I mean, dude, they're all multiple choice,
eight-hour test
and I just couldn't do well
on those exams.
Those tests are fucking racially biased,
all right?
Against Asian students
who don't study very hard.
Now...
And I felt like, you know...
I felt like a phony just walking around
the halls of the hospital in med school.
I felt like I got in
only because it was my birthright.
You know what I mean?
I mean, here's my interview
for med school.
So, Ken, tell me about yourself.
-Well, I'm Korean.
-Stop. Congratulations, you're in.
-That's it?
-That's it.
Small-dick scholarship.
[crowd laughs]
But I think that's why I worked so hard
as a physician.
I worked at Kaiser Permanente
for seven years, and I really did.
I was very hardcore.
I never joked around with my patients.
I took that shit very, very seriously
because everyone was like,
"You always joke."
How about, "You never joked around?"
I'm like, "No."
They were, "Come on, man,
laughter is the best medicine."
"No, fuck that.
Medicine is the best medicine!
All right?
Have you ever tried Klonopin?
It's amazing!"
You know?
And it's not like I was like fucking
Patch Adams or some shit like that,
like a fucking clown.
It's not like I went up to some people
and go,
"Oh, you got herpes,
but I got your nose! Honk! Honk!"
[crowd laughs]
Getting back to my wife.
We've been together long time, right?
A long time.
I've been pimpin' that Ho
for 16 years, and...
You know?
And you know what?
I love you so much.
The pimping was easy.
It was.
You know what I miss about Tran?
I miss, like... I was just thinking
about this the other day.
When we were engaged, you know,
we were motivated as a couple, you know,
we were just trying to impress each other
and, quite frankly,
we're very, very different, okay?
We're very different on the surface,
because she's, like, from San Francisco.
She's uptown, she's cosmopolitan,
well-read.
She's very, very cultured.
Me, I'm a redneck from North Carolina
who loves wrestling, all right?
So we're a little different,
even though...
And the thing is, to impress her...
She's a big sci-fi fan.
So, I read all three
Lord of the Rings books
just to show her I could fucking read.
Well, I didn't read it.
I read the Cliff Notes.
Well, most of the Cliff Notes.
Most of it.
And she's also very outdoorsy and, like,
you know.
So we go for a hike in Eagle Rock
and do all that shit.
Eagle Rock! Exactly.
All right, thank you.
You live in Eagle Rock?
-Yeah, I do.
-That's so cool, man.
Can I get back to my story now?
I'm kidding.
[crowd claps]
Not even...
[crowd laughs]
She's very outdoorsy
and she loves to go hiking.
We would go to Eagle Rock
and shit like that.
It was a lot.
We actually went camping
at Yosemite for, like, 10 days.
I fucking hate camping, all right?
I fucking hate that.
I mean, who wants to take a shit
in the woods,
-you know what I mean?
-[audience member] Yeah!
Think about that!
Who wants to--
Really? You love doing that?
You like digging a hole
and taking a fucking shit in the woods
and putting that dirt back on?
That's your idea of fun?
Not me. I'm more of a
Four Seasons type of gal, all right?
Not me, guys.
I won't even glamp as a millionaire, okay?
But that's the thing.
That's the fun of the courtship,
because you really want to prove yourself.
And, you know, everything changes
the moment we got married.
And the moment I fucking trapped her.
And it was just...
Because when we got home
from our honeymoon,
she was looking at the calendar.
"Oh, my God. I was just thinking, honey,
you love camping so much,
maybe we should go back to Yosemite
next month."
I'm like, "Oh, no, I paid my dues, Ho.
Off to the cinema!"
[crowd laughs]
All right guys,
to be brutally honest, man,
I wanted to do stand-up because...
You know, throughout the last 10 years
of my life,
you have highs and lows,
and everything is all good.
And then you realize, man,
I'm nothing without my wife.
I'm nothing without my family.
It's true.
And the reason why I chose the Ice House
is because, for the very first time
that Tran saw me do comedy,
it was right here at the Ice House.
That's the reason why I wanted to do it.
It's full circle.
And my wife Tran
is a breast cancer survivor,
going on 10 years cancer-free.
[crowd cheers]
Ten years, cancer-free.
And she is the strongest person I know,
all right?
All right, here is her story.
Tran was breastfeeding Alexa and Zoey
when they were one year old
and she found a lump on her breast,
all right?
And then we had to get it biopsied
and it turned out to be benign,
according to the path report.
And we were fine with that.
This is great, it was benign.
We're both doctors.
Okay, we'll see what it is.
Maybe it's an infection,
maybe it's something else.
And it got bigger,
and it got bigger and bigger.
And it wasn't getting better with
antibiotics or supportive therapy.
We got it re-biopsied, actually,
and it came back Stage 3 triple-negative
breast cancer,
with a 23% chance of survival.
Spoiler alert!
She's here right now, she's healthy.
She's doing great.
[cheers]
You are the strongest person that I know,
because two days before
she started her chemotherapy,
where she would lose all of her hair
and become really weak,
she decided, she took her eight-hour
standardized board exam,
the one that I failed,
and she passed it with flying colors!
[crowd cheers]
And I'm thinking to myself,
"That Ho," you know?
It's just so great.
And she has had... She's such a champ.
She has the presence of mind. She goes,
"You know what?
I'm going to beat the cancer,
so I might as well beat that exam."
She is so clutch, man.
She was like Reggie Miller
against the Knicks in '95,
where she's scoring, like,
fucking eight points to beat...
She's a Vietnamese Reggie Miller,
that's what she is.
Or she's Vietnamese John Cena,
but she didn't do this fucking bullshit.
You know what I mean?
Sidebar.
By the way, I hosted WWE Raw
with John Cena years ago
and WWE asked me to host.
They're like, "Do you want to do this?"
"Sure, I'm an actor.
I fake, wrestling's fake.
What could go wrong, all right?"
And then, on the day,
John Cena lifts me up for a body slam,
throws me over the top rope
and the five motherfuckers
who were supposed to catch me...
didn't.
Wrestling is fucking real.
[crowd laughs]
He throws me over the top rope,
I hit the concrete,
my head hits the wooden plank.
You hear the sound of my head
hitting the plank.
I had to call Tran after Raw
went off the air to assure her I'm okay.
My whole point is,
John Cena absolutely sucks.
He does, I'm just saying.
But getting back to my wife,
a fucking miracle happened.
After the first dose of chemotherapy,
after the first dose of adriamycin,
all her cancer went away.
It was amazing.
We did a blood test, all normal.
We did an MRI, all normal.
PET scan, CAT scan,
ultrasound mammogram,
all normal.
It was a miracle from God, Allah,
Oprah or Tom Cruise.
I tell you...
I think it was Tommy, I really do.
Which brings me, by the way,
to my next point,
or my next medical tip.
All right, dude, if any woman who wants to
get a mammogram for any reason,
ask your doctor to get a mammogram.
If you're concerned about breast cancer,
ask your doctor for a mammogram
for any reason.
And if that doctor says you can't get
a mammogram
because you don't fall under the criteria,
go to another fucking doctor who will
get you that mammogram, all right?
That's what I'm passionate about.
We got to stand up to cancer.
And that's what we got to do.
And it was at the same point where we
found out Tran's cancer was gone
I got offered the part
of Mr. Chow in The Hangover.
And I turned it down, actually,
because Tran had 12 more rounds
of chemo to go.
You have to go full circle with that.
You got to go, more chemo,
more radiation, more procedures.
And I'm like,
"No, I don't want to leave my family."
Tran was, like, "You got to do this.
It's only like a four-day trip
out in Vegas, you'll be fine.
This will be healthy for you.
You and I both know on the inside tip
that the cancer is gone."
I'm like,
"No, I don't think I can do that."
And it was actually Todd Phillips,
the writer-director of The Hangover.
He did Old School with Vince Vaughn
and Will Ferrell.
He convinced me to do the movie.
Directors are, by nature, like,
fucking geniuses or evil manipulators.
That's what they are.
Like, in Hangover III,
I was doing a scene with John Goodman
in a Bangkok prison,
and I was just doing this scene,
and there's a Thai toddler who's, like,
three years old,
and basically I was, like,
trying to do some improv in my acting,
hoping that scene will make it in.
So I look at the toddler,
I surprise him, I go,
"What are you looking at,
you little shit?"
And he starts crying.
You know, it was, like...
So, it didn't make it into the movie.
And then, so,
Todd comes out of the video booth.
Like, "Chow, come on!"
And he's, like, yelling at me like a dog.
He never calls me "Ken."
He's like, "Bad Chow! Bad Chow,"
like a dog.
If he had a newspaper,
he'd hit me with it.
And it was, like, "Apologize!"
I said, "I am so sorry."
"Apologize to the mother!"
-"I am so sorry."
-"Good!"
And then he turns around
and whispers in my ear,
"Do it again.
Amazing."
By the way, it was my idea
to get naked in The Hangover.
Did you guys know that?
Yup, that's right.
-Ha-ha!
-[claps]
My wife said it'll be the feel-good movie
of the summer,
because every guy will go home
feeling good about themselves.
That's my Ho, so...
But if anyone, like, kind of broke me out
of my depression, it was Todd Phillips.
And, by the way, like,
I didn't cry for six months, you know,
because I wanted to be strong
for my family
and I actually prescribed myself
antidepressants.
Of all the shit I could prescribe myself,
like weed, oxycodone, all these drugs...
Even the pharmacist looked at my script,
said, "Celexa? Pussy!"
You know?
"Wow, this is the most aggressive Rite Aid
I've ever been to."
And when you're on an antidepressant,
you can't cry.
Lord knows I tried.
I tried stabbing myself in the balls,
manipulating my taint.
Most of my approaches were genital-based.
Now...
But if anyone broke me out of that spiral
and made me cry, it was Todd Phillips.
This guy fucking saved my life,
'cause he went to me...
Every day, he would say, like...
Because he comes from a family
of oncologists, he knew the situation.
He said, "Look, we don't have to
finish the movie with you in it.
We can always do pickups and reshoots
around you."
This is a big, blockbuster
Hollywood movie.
No director will ever offer this,
but he said to me,
"I will make sure that I'll fly you
from Vegas to LA
every time Tran has her chemo."
And he did. He did not have to do that.
It was amazing.
And on the last day of filming,
Bradley Cooper actually drove me
from Vegas to LA
to see Tran and to see how she was doing.
These guys...
Go back full-circle,
Everyone's like,
"Why do you love The Hangover so much?"
Why is it the best thing
that ever happened in my life?
Because it saved my fucking life,
all right?
It was so therapeutic to me.
Even if I wasn't rich and famous,
which I am.
And on my last day of filming,
I got really emotional,
and for the first time in months,
I just started breaking down and crying.
I was like, "Thank you so much, man.
You know, you have no idea
what you did for me."
And I was just teary-eyed,
and I went in for a hug.
And Todd's just like...
because he's not a hugger.
I'm like, "What the fuck, dude?
I just bared my soul to you."
He goes...
I was like, "What the--?"
And then I realized my dick
was on his thigh.
My whole point is, like my dick,
life is short, all right, guys?
Take chances, be brave.
Long story short, Tran is here doing well.
Ten years cancer-free.
[crowd cheers]
Our kids are doing great.
There are new Hos sprouting up everywhere
across the land.
[crowd laughs]
And I have my first Netflix special
because of you guys.
[loud cheering]
For a bit of nostalgia,
I love to do selfie videos at the end of
every show to encapsulate this.
So I just want to kind of do this
really quick for you guys.
It's like doing a movie.
It's a lot of fun.
-Guys, Ice House!
-[crowd cheers]
Doing my first Netflix special!
You guys have a good time?
[crowd cheers]
[claps]
Wow, let me meet some people.
This is a Ho.
And this is a Ho.
But my favorite Ho is in the back.
[crowd cheers]
And this is my favorite club.
Love you, Ice House!
Love you, Netflix!
Toodle-oo, motherfuckers!
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you. Love you guys.
[loud cheering]
Dana Lee! Why don't you stand up, man?
He played my father, DK.
Come on! Come on up here, Dana.
Come on up here.
-You gonna cut this?
-Oh, fuck, yeah, I'm gonna cut this.
No, you're not gonna be in this.
And, by the way, one of the stars of
The Joy Luck Club is here.
We'll just get a camera on her.
I know she doesn't want it.
Give it up her for Ming-Na, right there.
See, Dana? She didn't come up here
like a whore, and just like...
And to make things even more full-circle,
the director of my Netflix special,
Jon Chu...
is right here.
All right, dude, you don't have to
fucking stand for him,
you know what I mean?
I just wanted you guys to wave, man.
This is my fucking show, Jon.
What the fuck?