All right.
I can't take it.
I don't know what he's gonna do next.
People that voted for him,
they don't know
what he's gonna do next.
But they have a different tone. I'm like,
"I don't know what he's gonna do next."
But I think they're like, "I don't know
what he's gonna do next, man!
This is crazy!"
"Then why'd you vote for him?"
"Hey, shut the fuck up."
Yeah. Yeah, that's what he ran on,
so, that makes sense.
I mean, I'm afraid of my phone.
I'm afraid of my phone.
I can't check the news.
I'm terrified to refresh
the news browser on my phone.
You wake up, you're like,
"Do I have coffee first, or do I...
Should I check it now?
I don't know what he did
while I was sleeping."
And there's a nervousness, you know?
Like, it's terrifying.
Because you know it's not gonna be good.
It's not.
You're not gonna do it and be like,
"Okay. Great." It's not gonna happen.
And I couldn't figure out what was
that feeling that I was experiencing
every time I refreshed the news browser
on my phone.
And it must be akin to an abusive
stepfather kicking your bedroom door in
just to go, boom,
"I'm burning the house down!"
And then he walks out
and shuts the door behind him.
And you're sitting there
with your phone going:
"I should go, right?
Where can I go?"
And it's just crazy, you know?
The people he's appointing are crazy.
It's gotten to a point where
I can say things to you
that would never make sense previous...
But now you'd be like, "All right."
Like, I could walk up to you, be like:
"Hey, man. Did you hear they're
making the Grand Canyon a landfill?"
"What?" "Yeah.
Yeah, they're doing that."
"Yeah, I guess that makes sense,
I guess.
But what's their logic?"
"How many times
you gotta see that thing?
They're just gonna do half of it,
and the other half you can still see.
But I bet people go see the garbage, too,
because that's a lot of garbage.
It's gonna be a double thing now."
"Yeah, I could see
why they would do that."
"It's okay to hunt at zoos now."
"What?"
"Yeah, the new EPA guy, I don't know.
I guess it's okay."
You're like, "Oh. Right. I guess that
makes sense with their logic, I guess.
It's gonna be a whole different thing
for the kids now, I guess, so...
But a lot of those animals
are almost extinct anyway.
Might as well just get it
over with, you know?"
Extinction's sort of a proactive term
with these guys.
Some things you never thought you'd say,
like, "Wow, these Nazis are annoying.
Did I just say that?
Is this real life? Did I say that?"
And now, like, you know,
people you know for years
are coming out as Trump voters.
Because they were hedging their bets
for a while.
Now they're like, "I think it's okay
to admit it to my friends."
People you've known forever,
they're like, "I voted for him."
Then that first thought is like,
"Well, now I've got a decision to make.
What the fuck do I do with you now?
Why'd you do that?
Why'd you do that to everybody?"
"Well, come on.
You knew I was a Republican.
I just voted party line. You know,
both of them were bad.
I wasn't gonna vote for her.
She was a crook."
"Was she a crook?
Or was she just a nice older lady
that didn't understand her phone?"
I've got two e-mail accounts on my phone.
I screw up sometimes.
There's no international consequence.
Just usually me going like, "Oh, shit.
Now that idiot
has my real e-mail address."
I'm gonna be hearing from him more
than I want to be.
I try to have a conversation
with these people,
because I know them,
and I don't want this polarization.
At some point,
we're gonna have to bridge it.
So, I'm like, "I don't get... Just explain
to me, really. What... I mean, what...
How are we gonna communicate now?"
He's like, "Come on, man.
We're all Americans."
And I'm like, "No.
Not enough. Not gonna be enough."
"Well, come on, you know,
like everyone loves
Tom Petty and burritos."
"Yeah, that's true,
but I don't think Petty is enough
to bridge this gap.
I just don't think that he has
that power at this juncture."
They're like, "Well, we just
don't talk about politics."
I'm like:
"Here's what bugs me, man:
There are people that had to climb out
of their hate holes to vote for this guy.
They'd never voted before.
They had to figure out where to vote,
and how to do it.
They had to take time away from hating,
which was hard for some of them...
and vote for this guy,
and now you're aligned with them.
You're on the same side as them.
You're part of that."
And they're like, "Well, I bet you
that guy likes Petty.
I mean, I think if you...
Seriously, man. If you just talked to him,
stayed away from politics.
They're just people, man."
And I'm like, "Well, what? You mean
I've gotta go to Chipotle with that guy?
Sit there and be like, 'Wow, you prefer
the bowl over the burrito?
Hmm. Interesting.'"
"Yeah, I like the bowl."
"Oh, yeah."
"Yeah, Tom Petty? You like Petty?"
"Aw, I fucking love Petty."
"Oh, that's cool. That's cool."
"I hate Jews, though. I hate Jews."
Yeah, it's going south quick.
I, uh...
"You know, maybe we shouldn't
talk about politics."
As if that's politics.
I don't know, man. Look, I will admit...
If this guy does anything good,
I'll admit it.
I'm not saying he's gonna be good
for people that didn't vote for him.
And it's still okay to say that
in this country. I did not vote for him.
But for us, it's not gonna be good.
It's always gonna be horrible.
We're not gonna one day wake up
in the next three and a half years
and go like,
"Holy shit. This turned around."
It's not gonna... It's not...
We're just gonna have to eat that.
We have to suck that up
and fight the fight we can.
But it's not gonna be good. But...
if he does anything good, I'll admit it.
That said, if it's much worse
than we ever anticipated,
which is really fucking bad...
people that voted for him
are gonna have to apologize.
That's all. They've just gotta apologize.
I'm just gonna need a little eye contact.
Look.
Look, even if we only have eight minutes
before the missiles hit,
I'm gonna need a little eye contact,
and a few words.
Even if it's like, "Oh, man!
I didn't think he'd do this!
This is crazy, bro!
Sorry!
Petty rules though, right?
Fucking Petty."
Cue "Free Falling."
And look, you know, the sad part is...
It's not sad, but it's that if you're
like-minded as I am,
no one's got our backs in government.
That's hard.
Now we've gotta have
each other's backs,
and, you know,
we should do that anyways,
but now you might have to
step up in public.
Because one thing the popular vote means
is that there's no social mandate
on being a douche bag in public.
So, it might be on you to say things
like this sometimes:
"Hey, you know,
it's still not okay to do that."
You might have to find courage.
I don't always have courage.
I'm not the most courageous guy.
I'm sort of an alpha pussy.
Um...
Yeah, we exist. We exist, yeah.
There's the classic alpha male,
just the meathead, rage-filled, like:
And then there's the alpha pussy
who makes fun of that guy.
You're like, "That guy's a douche bag."
"Why don't you say it to his face?"
"Because I'm saying it to you.
This is our hierarchy. That's theirs.
This is how that works."
I don't know how much time I have left.
Not in this set, in life.
I'm not sick, I'm not dying.
But I don't know.
I'm at that point where you hit...
You get... I'm, like, 53,
and you start to wonder,
how much time do I got left?
And it's playing into my
decision-making process.
If my girlfriend wants to watch
a movie I don't want to,
I'm like, "No, I don't want to die
during that. I don't want to...
I'd hate that to be the time.
Let's make a better choice.
I think we can make a better choice."
If someone comes up to me like,
"Oh, man, you don't listen to Phish?
You gotta listen to Phish."
"I don't know how much time I've got left.
I really, you know..."
And what if I like it? That's like
the rest of my life, right?
I've got no more room in my heart
or my mind for another jam band, man.
I mean, I've got half the Grateful Dead
catalog in there,
and three or four Allman Brothers songs.
I'm maxed out. I'm filled up."
And if you're ever
asking me this question:
"Have you seen that documentary with... "
Stop right there.
I don't know how much time I got left.
There's too many documentaries.
Let's slow down on the documentaries.
We're all loaded up.
We've got enough for now.
I'm not trying to discourage anyone.
There are some good ones.
But there are some bad ones.
Sometimes I think documentary
filmmaking's just a Hail Mary pass
for someone almost giving up
on the medium.
I don't want to hurt anyone's feelings,
but just because you have an iPhone
and your cat is sick
doesn't make you a genius.
"I'm gonna call it One Out of Nine.
It's about my cat dying,
but it's also about me accepting failure.
I think this is much better than the one
I made about my dad's struggle
to buy pants in an unfamiliar store."
I just don't know
how much time I have left.
And I don't think I'm afraid to die.
I'd prefer it happens quickly.
Like the transition,
I just want it to be like:
I'd like my last words to be
something like, "Wait, what?"
That'd be preferable.
But the reason I don't think I'm afraid
to die is a weird reason.
It's a weird reason.
Because I've always had
this recurring image in my head.
I never understood it until now,
and I think I misinterpreted it before.
I'll share it, because
I don't know what you'd do.
But it's a recurring image I get,
and it always is just me
hanging from a cliff.
That's where we enter,
me hanging from a cliff.
I don't know why.
There's no one around.
I don't know what happened,
but I'm hanging from a cliff.
And I never picture myself
climbing back up.
It's only a matter of time
before I'm like:
"Oh..."
And I think that's because
I'm not afraid to die.
I think it's because
I'm not a control freak.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, anyone can scramble back up,
but it takes real courage just to let go.
And I don't have a god in place.
It just wasn't put there.
You know, I'm 53, and I don't
think it's gonna happen.
The wheels would really have to come off
for me to find god at this age.
But I think I'm spiritual, maybe.
I don't know.
No. Probably not.
Like, when did this question
become so popular?
I get it three or four times a week.
"Hey, are you meditating?
Do you meditate?"
What's happening? When did...
Why is everyone asking me that?
Does that happen to you, or is it crazy?
Are you meditating?
Like, are you guys part of the same team?
Why do I...
No, I'm not fucking meditating.
I know what it is, but I'm not doing it.
I've done it.
I did not get the desired results.
I know how to meditate. I get it.
You've got to sit quietly and comfortably.
Be mindful.
That's another word getting way
too much usage.
Be mind...
When did that become a word?
That's everywhere.
Be mindful.
And what is that? It's a meditation word.
Be mindful. Be mindful of your breath.
And this is me meditating,
the one time I did it.
Mindful of my breath.
Be mindful of your breath,
and thoughts will come.
But don't lock onto them.
Don't attach yourself to the thoughts.
Just let them go by.
Let the thoughts come,
but let them go by.
So, I'm mindful of my breath.
Let the thoughts go by.
I don't know what the hell he's gonna do.
Ooh.
I don't know how much time I have left.
Oh, okay.
My dad's an asshole.
That one's not going by.
That one's staying.
In all honesty
I got where you needed to be.
The one time I meditated successfully,
I cleared my mind.
I cleared my ego. Everything was open.
I hit that point of Zen.
And all I could hear was my breath
and my heart beating,
and right at that moment I thought:
"This could fucking stop at any second."
And I ejected right out of it.
Because that is not
the desired result of meditation.
And I don't know how to have fun.
How do you have fun?
How do you guys do it?
I don't think I would have come
to this show.
Like, if Marc Maron's playing, I'm like:
Ehh...
"I like him, but I've gotta go down
to the... I don't know."
I think it's genetic, really, you know?
Like my dad's alive.
Uh... Wrong tone? Is that the wrong tone?
Um...
Wait, let me try again.
I'm blessed to, uh...
To have my father still with us.
But sometimes, some days,
it's like, "When? When?!"
But... No, that's negative.
But do you remember...
Remember the day you realized
your dad was an idiot?
Do you remember that day?
It's a pretty important day.
You spend a lot of time thinking,
"He's great. My dad's great.
He's the greatest guy in the world,"
probably longer than you should.
And then one day
the fucking other shoe drops,
and you're like, "Holy shit."
When did he turn into an idiot?"
You know?
My father used to be a doctor,
and screwed that up somehow.
But he was a bright man and he did his job
and I was very impressed with him,
and, I don't know, something went wrong.
I don't know.
Like, I got a phone call from him once.
He was all upset, and I'm like,
"What's the matter, Dad?"
And he goes, "I just don't understand
why I didn't win the lottery."
"Wait, what?"
"Yeah, I play every day.
I don't get why I'm not winning."
I'm like, "Oh, my God.
When did you become a fucking idiot?"
I said to him, just to feel him out:
"So, what would you do, Dad,
if you won the lottery?"
He just immediately goes:
"Well, I'd do everything I wanted to do.
I would do everything I want to do."
And I go, "Like what?"
And there's a beat, and he goes,
"Yeah, you're right."
That quick? That quick?
So, like, it's genetic, and I don't want...
Like, I'm already there.
That's it. Nothing? Can't do nothing.
I don't know what people do.
What am I supposed to do, you know?
I play guitar. That's nice.
I'm just happy I never wanted to be
a professional guitar player,
because now my hobby isn't haunted
by failure, you know what I mean?
Like, my guitar isn't some sort of
broken dream vessel, you know?
Is that too hard for this crowd?
A little too hard?
A little too close to home? I apologize.
Might be a couple dudes
in the audience like:
"Oh, fuck, Maron.
I just started playing drums again.
I brought you a CD tonight."
And you're like,
"It's from 2002, but we were good."
Yeah.
I don't know what to do. What do you do?
There's things I'm supposed to like.
You know, I'm a smart guy,
and relatively sophisticated.
I'm interested in things.
Like when people go like,
"Do you want to go to the museum?"
Inside I'm thinking like, "Ugh. No."
But, like...
You don't say that. You're like,
"What's going on down there?
What's going on?"
And I don't want to close my mind.
I've looked at a lot of art.
I like art, and I just...
But I think I've seen enough.
I think I'm all done.
Is that wrong? I don't want to be...
I don't want to discourage anyone
from doing it.
I'm just... I'm done, I think.
And also, there's a problem
I have at museums.
If I go to a museum, right when I walk in,
and get to the desk
where you pay for the ticket,
"the donation," "the suggested donation."
Right when I'm putting money down,
I'm just like:
"Oh, my God, I'm exhausted.
I'm exhausted.
I don't know what just happened.
Is there a mid-century bench
that's not part of an exhibit
that I could maybe just
take a little snooze on?
A little nappy?
I can see half a painting
in that room over there,
and I don't know what it wants.
I don't know what it needs from me,
and I'm tired. I'm just tired."
I get the feeling when
I go to Home Depot.
You ever go to Home Depot
to buy a little thing?
"I need an extension cord.
I'll just go to Home Depot."
Don't do it.
You just walk in and you're like,
"Oh, my God, I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
Is there any constructed piece
of mattress furniture
that I could just lay down on a second?"
And I think they both come
from the same place.
It's a deep, like, knowledge that there's
just a lot of things I don't understand,
and I'm probably not going to.
But what do people do?
I don't know. What do you do?
You binge watch things.
I don't know where you get the time.
I don't know what's going on.
I can't handle the media landscape.
Too many options. Too much shit.
Like my analogy
for the media landscape is like:
You ever driven past a landfill?
Just like a giant mountain of garbage?
It doesn't even look like garbage anymore.
There's that weird dirt in it.
You have that sort of like...
But you see pieces of garbage.
And it's got those horrible birds
flying over it.
You're driving by and only have
two thoughts, in no particular order:
One is like, "Oh, my God, look at that.
That's disgusting."
But the other thought is always,
"I bet there's some good stuff in there.
I bet you there's a box of money in there
that someone just forgot.
Or maybe some old stamps,
collectible stamps.
Or maybe a ring that's still on a finger!"
That's like the media landscape.
If you can find that ring
on that finger...
I mean, oddly, you know, I'm old enough...
This is not an old guy thing, but I
remember when there were three networks,
and that was okay. That was enough.
Why'd we... Why is it like it is now?
There weren't many choices.
We weren't getting all the information,
but we were all kind of on the same page,
give or take a show or two.
Right?
I mean, now someone...
I've had people ask me if I've seen a show
and not only have I not heard of the show,
but when they tell me where it's on,
I don't even know what that is.
When did that happen?
Someone comes up to you all excited.
"Hey dude, are you watching Turd Journey?"
"Wait, did you say Turd Journey?"
"Yeah, Turd Journey.
There's 40 episodes of Turd Journey on."
"What? Wait, Turd Journey?"
"It's not what it sounds like.
It kind of is,
but it's about more than that.
You gotta check it out."
- "Where's it on?"
- "Oh, shit. You gotta download Clomper.
Do you have Clomper?
It's an app for your phone or computer.
You become part of the Clomper community.
You can watch all 40 Turd Journeys.
And Savage Dicks.
You ever watch Savage Dicks?
That's on Clomper.
It's not what it sounds like.
It kind of is, but it's about more.
And there's some Savage Dick-
Turd Journey crossover. It's hilarious."
I'm like, "On Clomper?"
"Yeah, you gotta download Clomper
for Turd Journey. Savage Dicks."
- "Clomper?"
- "Yeah, Clomper.
Oh, shit. They have Clomper Docs now.
They have Clomper Docs.
There's this one called One Out of Nine
about this guy's cat dying.
But it's about more than that.
It's about his cat dying,
but it's really about him failing.
It's pretty good.
And it's got a surprise ending.
Spoiler alert!
Yeah, it turns out the cat gets better,
and the guy gets sick."
Clomper Docs.
Clomper.
"I don't know how much time I've got left.
I don't think it's gonna happen."
I don't do things.
I don't do stuff.
I don't know why I don't do stuff.
I kind of know why.
All right, example.
I got an opportunity to see
the Rolling Stones. I was given tickets
to see the Rolling Stones
the first date of their last stadium tour.
San Diego, right? The first day.
I was given tickets on the field.
And the day I was given those tickets,
my first thought was like:
"Fucking parking's gonna...
That's gonna be a clusterfuck,
parking down there at an arena.
Are they even equipped for that?
Do they have lots?
What's up down there?
What?"
And my friend Dean was like,
"Oh, we're going.
It's the Stones."
And I'm like,
"Yeah, but I don't... All right."
Then I had to examine, why didn't
I want to go see the Stones?
And there was a couple levels of excuses,
like part of me was like, "Well, you know,
Bill Wyman's not playing bass anymore,
so, they're not really the Stones."
He hasn't played for 20 years.
That's like saying "I haven't bought
a Stones record since Brian Jones died."
It's just not a viable excuse.
So, I thought about it more
and I realized:
"Oh, you know what it is?
It's because they're old."
Now, I'm not being an ageist, right?
I just didn't want it to be sad.
I have a lot of belief and faith
and love for the Rolling Stones.
They're bigger than life.
They're my favorite band.
They'd been there for me forever.
They need to stay the Rolling Stones.
I can't go to a Rolling Stones show
and be like, "Oh, no."
I can't let that happen.
I was concerned.
I was concerned for the Stones.
I'm like, "I don't think they
should be doing it anymore."
But we went. Dean and I went.
Parked on the fourth level
of the structure.
And we get down to the field,
and there's people of all ages.
Dean's looking around.
"A lot of reading glasses out."
There were guys older than me,
guys my age, young people,
because they're the Stones.
The greatest rock 'n' roll band in
the world. Mythic. The Rolling Stones.
I think I was the only one
who was concerned.
I'm like,
"I don't know how this is gonna go.
I don't know. A little worried."
Everyone's like, "Yeah!" and I'm like:
So, I was really worried.
So, the opening band does their thing.
They bring them out. "The Rolling Stones!"
They all come out. I'm like: "Uh..."
So, then there's Keith. Keith's doing
a good job of being Keith at 72.
His hair is its natural color.
He's not dangling shit from it anymore.
He's looking good.
He's doing a few of these.
A couple of these.
But not pushing it. Doing a good job.
From what I could see of Charlie,
he's looking good. He's solid.
Gray hair, solid on the drums.
Looking good.
Ronnie is a problem. Ronnie's a problem.
His hair is dyed. He's running around.
It's a little embarrassing.
But he's the kid. He's 68, so...
I'm gonna give Ronnie a pass.
Now, if you're a real Stones fan,
I believe that some part of you
just tolerates Mick Jagger.
All right? You know...
You know he's important.
He's the Rolling Stones.
But you know, he's Mick Jagger, so...
So, when Mick came out, it was different.
Mick comes out,
and right away he's like:
And...
And, like, part of me was like,
"Oh, my. Yeah, I...
Isn't he a little old to be...?
Like...
I was like, "I don't know if he
should be doing that. A man his age."
I was embarrassed, you know?
But then I settled into it.
I was like,
"He's Mick Jagger. He does that.
If anyone's gonna do that,
let Mick do it."
So, I settled in and I was like,
"All right, okay. It's not sad."
It took them three songs
to pull it together, but I like that.
Rock 'n' roll's dirty. It's fucked up.
Let them figure it out.
So, by the fourth song I was
up on my chair like:
You know?
But then something happened.
Well, it was kind of rough
and beautiful at the same time.
So, they're gonna do "Moonlight Mile"
from Sticky Fingers,
a challenging song for the Stones
at any age.
He's gotta do falsetto. It's a slow song.
They put him way out in the audience
on his own platform.
Mick with a guitar.
I think the other guys were
kind of concerned. They were like:
You know, and I'm watching him,
and he's doing it.
He's hitting it, man.
He's hitting the falsetto. It's working.
He's in it.
And out of nowhere, I just start crying.
I'm crying.
I look like those black
and white photographs
of those 16-year-old girls in the '60s.
Tears are running down my face.
In the middle of that moment,
something horrible happened.
They've got the big screen.
They go right in on Mick's face.
Like right here.
And there it is, 50 feet big.
And I'm like, "Oh, God!
Why are you doing that to Mick?"
You could see everything,
all the lines and dyed hair.
I'm like, "Stop it! Take it down!"
It was sad. I was like, "This is horrible.
Why are they doing that?"
And I just kept looking at him.
And all of a sudden it just hit me.
I'm like:
"Whoa, wait a minute. This is amazing."
That these guys
are still doing those songs,
now with all this experience,
and pain, and wisdom,
and just life behind them.
It brings a depth to it
that wasn't there before.
It's fucking unbelievable.
They're still the huge Rolling...
It's, like, beautiful.
I started thinking about it like:
"It's a lot riskier for those guys
to be doing this shit now
than it was in 1972."
I mean, in 1972, if Richards
was, like, fucked up on heroin,
and he fell into a Marshall stack
in the middle of the show,
and they had to cancel it,
half the audience would be like:
"Ha! Fucking Keith!
Man, he was so fucked up.
They couldn't even finish.
I love it. I love it."
They didn't care.
But now they're old,
and they're doing this shit.
And they're running around.
Like there were points where I'm like,
"Take it easy, fellas.
Don't go crazy."
Because Mick's running.
He's running from side to side.
I was like, "Slow down,"
because what if it was just like, "Yeah...
Keith.
Keith, help me. Keith.
Oh, my God. It's happened.
It's happened."
Like,
if that happened, an entire generation
of people would just be out there going:
"Oh, fuck. It's over.
Mick is down.
We're dying.
We're dying."
He didn't go down, though.
He did not go down.
They stayed.
They stayed the Rolling Stones.
Now...
I'm gonna share something with you.
I'm not proud of it, but Dean,
my buddy Dean,
he's in his 50's, too. He's 50.
We watched the concert and they left.
And we knew they were gonna
do one encore, right?
Me and Dean are sitting there.
They come back out.
And they go into "Satisfaction."
And I swear to God, at the same time,
we look at each other like:
"Let's go.
- Let's do it. Let's beat the crowd."
- Dean lit up. He's like, "Yeah, let's go."
We've got a mission. We're running.
We're like, "Let's go." And we get out.
We've gotta get out of an arena.
We hear them go into
"You Can't Always Get What You Want."
And we could hear that they'd brought
on stage like an entire choir.
I'm like, "Shit, a choir."
Dean's like,
"We can hear. Just keep going."
We run up the stairs, and we get
to the car, and we're driving down.
As we're pulling out of the garage,
we see the crowds break.
There's this wave of people
coming out of the arena,
and we're like, "Shit, do it."
And we get out, we get on the highway,
we beat the crowds free and clear.
And...
But I think that might have been
the highlight of the night.
It might have been better
than the concert.
We enjoyed the concert, but we could
not have been more excited.
We were like, "Dude!
Dude, we're out! We're out!
That concert was amazing,
but we're out, we're driving!
Put a Stones CD in.
Let's put a Stones CD in.
Play Exile.
That concert was good,
but it's not Exile."
It was a good moment.
Sometimes you do get what you want.
Um...
I don't know why I'm hung up
on this mortality thing.
I don't know why.
I think it's because I had a near-death
experience not too long ago.
I almost died. Uh... Well, I went running.
And, um, I hadn't done it in a while.
And it was scary. It was touch and go,
as far as I could tell.
I was very close to death.
I don't know what you do,
but I don't exercise much.
I may look in shape, but not really.
I go through periods
where I don't exercise at all.
And it takes a lot to get me to exercise.
I don't know what happens with you,
but with me,
the exercise thing is like three phases
that have to happen
before I actually exercise.
Like, phase one usually is just me sitting
at home alone, doing nothing.
And out of nowhere I just look down
and I go, "Oh, fuck me.
Goddamn it. What the fuck
is wrong with me?
Goddamn it.
Why can't I just exercise? It's bullshit.
I've gotta get back in shape.
I've gotta get back in shape."
Then some part of your brain is like,
"What do you mean, 'back'?"
Like, somewhere in my mind,
I think that
there was a period of time
where I hit the gym three,
four times a week.
I was running, hitting weights,
a little ripped.
But in reality, I don't think
that time ever happened.
I don't think it ever existed.
I think it's a mythology
I've created for myself
to judge myself against
when I want to hate myself
because I have a little bit
of time on my hands.
That doesn't always get me out.
There's the next phase,
which is you wake up and you're like:
"The only way I'm gonna do it is
if I get new shoes.
I gotta get new shoes.
Those shoes don't even work anymore.
Those... I've gotta get new shoes.
You've gotta get the magic shoes."
There's no magic shoes.
There are no shoes that wake you up
because they put themselves on your feet
and started the process.
"Hey, what's going on? Wait.
Pants. We need pants."
You get the shoes,
you put them in the closet,
and you see them
when you get your other shoes.
They're like, "Are we doing it?"
"Shut up. We'll do it when I want to.
That's how I talk to sneakers.
I don't know who you are
or what your life is.
But the way it has to happen,
the way it happens to exercise, really,
is that you have to be seized by the need
to do it in a moment.
Like, the spirit has to move you like,
"I gotta go. I gotta do it now."
And you have to do it right then,
because that's your portal.
That's your window back in.
You've gotta do it when that hits you.
And it hit me.
It was 2:30 in the afternoon.
And it was 102 degrees outside.
Now, I hadn't run in, like, two years.
I didn't let that stop me.
I'm like, "I can do it. I can do it.
I can run."
So, I put on my magic shoes,
and I grabbed my driver's license
for easy tagging.
I don't know about you, but I always
take the driver's license.
I got my iPhone, I'll get outside.
"Oh, shit, I better get the license.
If I go down..."
They're not gonna crack an iPhone
for a terrorist cell.
They're not gonna do it for a
mid-level celebrity dead on a hill.
Better take the driver's license.
I'm out there running the hills.
I haven't been out there in...
I don't even notice how hot it is, because
it's so hot sweat's not even building up.
I get ten minutes in and all
of a sudden my hands go numb.
And I'm like, "What's happening?"
Then I can't feel my arms,
and I'm like, "This isn't good."
And then my heart starts going:
And I'm like, "Holy shit."
I had to take a knee.
I had to take a knee, outdoors,
and appeal to a God that I don't have,
and say, "This doesn't happen here.
This doesn't happen outside.
This is an indoor thing, and it's quick.
Not outside.
In a bathtub, in my sleep,
something like that.
Not out here."
As I was sitting there I was like:
"How many men's last words are
'I got this'?" You know what I mean?
What was I doing out there?
Dumb pride, you know?
And then I got up.
I had this fear that I would be
found just laying there outdoors.
Like, some hipster couple
with their dumb dog...
would just find me laying there.
They'd be like, "He did not have it.
Did not have it today.
Oh, look. It's, like, the first day out
for those shoes. Look at those shoes."
"Come on, buddy.
Just stay away from him. It's not polite."
It didn't happen. And I tell you what,
I got up. That's how stubborn I am.
I got up, and I still did... I didn't run.
But I did the entire route.
And then I called the doctor.
The next day I called the doctor
because I'm 53
and I should when that happens.
They set me up with a cardiologist,
so, I go to the cardiologist.
When you go to the doctor,
you want something to be wrong.
Not a major thing, but enough to not
make you a fucking lunatic.
So...
I go to the cardiologist.
And I don't get it, man.
They can put people in space,
we can take money out around the world,
they make all these developments,
they can clone things.
But they can't get a handle
on this vessel.
This is a closed system,
confounding for some reason.
Cannot figure it out.
Right? Isn't it crazy?
So, I go to this doctor,
they do all the tests.
They do a stress test,
cardiogram, blood test.
They do an ultrasound of my heart.
And, uh, it's a girl.
Um...
You know,
sometimes you don't wanna know.
But, you know, I kind of knew.
I think a lot of you knew.
They do all these fucking tests,
and then the doctor comes out.
And he's like, "Yeah, you're great.
You're in perfect shape. No problems.
Perfectly fit. Everything...
All the tests are good."
And I'm like, "What?
What does that mean?"
He's like, "You're healthy."
And I'm like, "What happened out there?
On the hill, when my hands went numb,
my arm went numb,
and my heart was skipping?
What was that about?"
And a doctor, a real doctor,
looked at me and said:
"Who knows?"
"Shouldn't you know?"
"Look, we'll see if it happens again.
Let me know."
"No, I'm gonna call you
before I go running.
And you can come
and follow me in your car.
How would that be?"
"Who knows?"
I shouldn't have told my mom about it.
'Cause that gave her a reason
to check in with me.
I don't wanna be negative.
But my mother's just inappropriate.
She's always been inappropriate.
No boundaries.
It's disturbing. It's just disturbing.
It is.
And now someone's taught her
how to use emojis. It's no good.
It's never the right emoji.
She's very partial to the smiley face
with the heart eyes.
And that's not the right one
for your 53-year-old man son.
That's not the right one.
It's just not the appropriate emoji.
All caps.
All caps texts, all caps e-mails.
She doesn't know
how to make little letters.
She knows how to change
the color of the e-mails,
but she doesn't know how
to make little letters.
If the NSA is looking at all her e-mails,
my mom's nickname is All Caps in Florida.
Not a national security threat,
but she does make her 53-year-old
man son uncomfortable
when she sends an all-caps text
that says, "I love you."
Smiley face heart eyes.
What am I supposed to do with that?
Look, I love my mother.
But I'm not in love with her.
I don't think I am. I, uh...
Huh.
Inappropriate though.
Like, one time, she sent me
a manila envelope.
Like, a manila envelope
in the regular mail.
No phone call, no heads-up.
I didn't know what it was.
But I knew it was from her,
'cause it had her needy scrawl on it.
So...
I opened it up, and there were
two notarized forms in there.
And I thought,
"This should've been a phone call.
I don't even know what this is."
But this looks like a phone call,
or maybe a heads-up:
"I'm sending some notarized forms to you."
This was breakfast I was eating.
And they were two documents.
One was her desire to be cremated...
and have her ashes spread somewhere
over the Southwest.
Which I thought was good. It was broad,
and it gave me options.
Theoretically,
I could drive 10 minutes into Arizona,
and just be like, "Adios, Mama." You know?
The other document...
was the DNR document.
Look, people have to do this.
It's important.
But I could've used a phone call.
So, this is
the do-not-resuscitate document.
Now, I didn't know that there's a list
of people, in order of preference...
who can do the unplugging.
I didn't know that.
I'm not pissed off,
but I'm not number one.
It's my little brother.
My little brother.
Why does he get to kill her?
That's why she didn't call me.
How is she gonna explain that to me?
Her first born, who she's in love with.
She did not trust me
with that very delicate responsibility.
Then I started thinking,
"Me and my brother aren't getting along.
Maybe this is just her way of trying
to get us to do something together."
That's what I thought.
But what did she think?
Did she think I was gonna
jump the gun or something?
What'd she think was gonna happen?
That I'd be in the hospital room,
she's on the machine,
and I'd be talking to my brother like,
"Come on, do it, man. Just pull it.
Pull it, bro. Just fucking do it."
"Marc, she's still talking."
"I know.
But enough already, right?
Let's wrap it up."
My mother does not love that joke.
You know, some people think
that, like, comedy takes courage.
I don't know if that's true.
I guess it is at some point.
I don't even know
if what I'm doing is comedy anymore.
But I certainly don't have a lot of fear.
But I'll tell you what,
part of my process...
I'll share it with you.
I don't write jokes.
I write, you know, compulsive thoughts,
you know, on Post-its. Now...
these take courage.
Because I do these
while I'm driving. Now...
This is more dangerous than texting,
'cause I need both hands.
I gotta hold the pad down on the wheel.
Then I gotta write,
and I gotta focus
on the important thought.
So, my life is put at risk,
and the life of others, for these.
So, I figure I should share them.
Since, you know, many lives
were hanging in the balance.
Don't... Don't get too crazy.
All right, so, this one just says, um,
"My comfort zone is uncomfortable."
That's worth dying for, right?
Right, worth...?
This one says, "I want people to like me,
I just want to know why they do."
I think that was worth
taking out a pedestrian or two.
Here's one. This is interesting.
"The monster I created
to protect the kid inside me
is hard to manage."
Not funny, but it's a thinker, right?
It's a thinker.
It makes you think,
"Wow. That should be in a book
with other things like that."
Oh, this one just says:
"The trepidation
of the Dave Matthews fan."
It's hilarious to me
that people respond to just that.
'Cause you know who you are.
It's not easy for them. It's not easy.
They can't be out with that,
you know what I mean?
You can't put that into the world.
You don't know
how that's gonna be received.
Not good, generally.
The only place the Dave Matthews fan
can truly be comfortable
is when they're wearing sandals
and cargo shorts,
jigging around in an arena...
with other like-minded people.
"I hope these mushrooms
aren't bunk again."
I don't need to shit on Dave Matthews.
I don't need to take time to do that.
I personally don't like him.
But this came from a true, honest,
beautiful, human moment.
I'll share that with you.
But I do need to address
the Dave Matthews thing.
I listen to a lot of music.
I'm very open minded.
I can listen to Parliament in the morning,
Bert Jansch in the afternoon.
And maybe some Gram Parsons.
Whatever, I mix it up.
I'm not just dropping names to be hip.
I have an open mind
when it comes to music.
But I cannot get through two of his songs.
I can't get through. I...
And I try. I try.
By midway...
By midway through the second song,
I get a type of boredom
that's not even normal boredom.
It's like there's an edge to it.
It's like an aggravated boredom.
Like the boredom sets in,
and then I'm like, "God, fuck. What the...
Why? Why?"
Like, I don't know what that is.
But I know people like him.
And, you know, good for you.
I know it's hard for you guys.
It's very hard to defend that.
And the moment that I had,
which was kind of beautiful, was...
It was great.
I was in Iowa City doing a gig.
Oh, yeah?
It's a very interesting town.
I've never seen a town more separated
into, like, full on sports meatheads,
and then the writers' program, you know?
So, like...
There's just people that are just like,
"We're gonna win!"
And then people like, "I'm still sad
about David Foster Wallace.
I'm never gonna get over... " And somehow,
there's a perfect yin yang to the thing.
This complete...
Okay, so, I'm getting coffee in Iowa City.
There's a guy getting coffee
in front of me. He's ordering.
There's a barista there.
And the guy ordering coffee says
to the guy making coffee:
"What are you doing this weekend?"
The guy making coffee looks up,
and he's like,
"Oh, I'm going to a concert."
Then the guy ordering coffee goes,
"Really? Who are you going to see?"
And then the other guy stood up,
and I saw it in his face.
"Dave Matthews Band."
And I was... I felt for him.
It was courageous.
He put himself out there. That's hard.
You know,
you don't know how it's gonna land.
It hung there for, like,
two, like, really tense seconds.
And then the other guy goes,
"Oh, I fucking love Dave Matthews."
And I was so happy for them,
that they had this moment.
I knew in my heart they were both wrong.
I knew that.
But I was happy for them.
'Cause I'm a big-hearted, tolerant person.
Oh, yeah. This one.
This one just says:
"I expect relief and life-changing impact
from everything."
That's a lot.
Then there's a second thought,
because there's a line here.
So, I must have stopped driving
and just sort of like:
The other one says, "The space between
despair and orgasm is hard to fill."
And that's not a time thing,
that's a philosophical idea.
So...
Some guy...
Some guy sent me a hat.
He sent me a hat. Look, I don't know how
hat companies stay in business, you know?
It was a gift, I guess, you know.
And I know, I'm a guy.
I've been the guy on the street,
just standing there.
You see a hipster with a hat,
and you're like,
"Oh, I gotta get a fucking hat."
I've been that guy.
But I don't know
how they stay in business.
Anyways, this guy sent me a hat.
It was a big hat. It was a fancy hat.
It was a Stetson hat.
I didn't know the guy well.
But it was a gift. It wasn't a cowboy hat.
It was like a...
Like a 1800s derby looking hat.
Nice hat.
But I would've had to change
my entire life...
you know, to accommodate that hat.
I just...
I knew two things when I opened that box.
I'm like, "That is a nice hat."
I Googled it. It's a $100 hat.
And it's never leaving the house
on my head. It's never going out.
Not gonna happen for that hat.
Because... All right,
I'll be honest with you.
Yeah, I'll tell you. All right.
I've been the guy...
in a store that sells big stupid hats.
Standing in front of a mirror
with a big stupid hat on,
saying, "Oh, hell yeah.
This is my hat.
I fucking love this hat."
It's good and important that you have
someone you love there at that moment...
to helpfully say, "Don't buy a hat."
It's not gonna stop you, though.
'Cause you're gonna be like:
"Oh, no, baby. This is my hat.
Come on, are you crazy?
Look at this fucking hat."
And then she'll say, "All right.
Do what you want. Do what you want."
And you buy that hat. You buy that hat.
And the confidence you had
in front of that mirror
doesn't even last four blocks...
out of the store. You walk out like:
"Why's everyone looking at my hat?
Is it too big?
Am I not a big enough man
to wear this hat? Did I just fuck up?
Was she right? Is this a shitty hat?
Am I a shitty person?
Why'd I buy this hat?"
But now you're in. You've bought the hat
and you've gotta go home.
You're gonna have to make
some decisions...
around that hat.
Usually the first one is something
along the lines of, like:
"Hey, you know, I think I'm just
gonna make this a house hat.
I'm just gonna wear it around the house.
Maybe outside, if I go outside.
But you know, baby, it's too nice.
I don't wanna lose it.
Or, you know, scuff it up.
I'm just gonna wear it around the house."
And she's like: "Uh-huh."
"That's what I'm gonna do with the hat."
And you do it.
You eat breakfast in the hat.
You sit on the couch, listen to records,
wearing your big dumb hat.
Maybe you put it on naked
to get her to like it.
Like, "What about now?"
And she's like, "No, no. Take it off.
It's stupid. Dumb decision."
Eventually, it starts working your brain.
You're like, "Why'd I get this hat?"
That's the day it becomes a wall hat.
You're like,
"I don't wanna throw it out. It's so nice.
I'm gonna hang it up like a picture."
And you put a nail in the wall,
and you hang up your stupid nice hat.
With the other artwork on the wall.
It's a wall hat.
People come over, they're like,
"That's a nice hat. You wear that?"
"Not anymore. It's too nice.
Could you not touch it, please?
Please, don't put it on.
Just leave it by the...
Just put it back. Thank you."
It stays up on the wall,
until one day you realize...
Maybe in the middle of a bowl of cereal...
You're like, "Why is that up there?
That was a mistake.
That was a shitty decision.
That's a little shame gallery.
Why do I have to be reminded
that I bought that dumb fucking hat
every day when I sit at this table?
Fuck that hat."
That's the day it becomes a closet hat.
That's officially closet hat day.
And it can stay in there
for a long time. Years, even.
And then one day,
you're cleaning out that closet,
all the hate for the hat comes back.
You're like, "Aw, fuck this hat.
Goddamn it.
I thought I got rid of this."
And that's the day
it becomes a Goodwill hat.
And three days after
it becomes a Goodwill hat,
a hipster guy walks into Goodwill.
And he sees the hat,
he's like, "Holy shit.
That's a nice hat. That's a $100.00 hat.
Six bucks? Hell yeah."
And he puts it on his head,
and it looks like they've been
together for centuries.
Perfect symbiosis, on a soul level.
Everything makes sense.
Two things have been brought
together to make a whole.
And he buys that hat,
and he leaves a happy man.
And then somewhere along his route,
there's an old guy across the street
looking at him going,
"I gotta get a fucking hat."
And that...
That is how the hat companies
stay in business.
Wow, I think I just wrote
a children's book.
"The Hat by Marc Maron.
This is my favorite book my mom got me.
It's about a stupid, silly, sad man
who wants a hat.
He's in the store,
and he wants to get a hat.
But she doesn't want him to.
She doesn't even really like him.
But he gets the hat anyways,
'cause this man is a stupid,
silly, sad man.
And then he leaves the store,
and he keeps getting smaller,
and smaller, and smaller.
Until it's just a hat on the ground.
And then he just shows up at home.
I don't even know how that happened.
He's so silly. And then he says:
'I'm just gonna
wear the hat in the house.'
Then why did you buy it, stupid?
So, he's just wearing it in the house now.
He wears it eating cereal.
He wears it on the couch.
He wears it outside.
He wears it in a tree.
And then...
Then he wears it naked.
He's naked in just a hat.
And she still doesn't like him.
She hates him, I think.
And then he decides he doesn't
like the hat anymore.
But he's going to hang it on the wall?
Like a picture?
He's so stupid, and sad and silly.
He hangs it on the wall.
His friends come over.
He says, 'Don't touch my hat.
Don't put it on.
Take the hat off.' He's getting mean,
the stupid, silly, sad man.
Then one day he's sitting at the table
looking at the hat, and he's like:
'I don't like that hat.'
And then he puts it in a closet.
And that's where the magic shoes are,
from the other book.
That's his other book.
So, it stays in the closet
for a long time,
'cause he gets a cat,
and then the cat gets old.
And then the cat goes away,
and then he gets another cat.
And then he decides to clean the closet.
And he sees the hat,
and he's mad at it again.
He's like, 'I hate this hat.'
And then he brings it to another store.
But it's a sad store.
All the other things in the store
are crying.
There are machines
that don't even mean anything anymore,
and they're crying in the store.
But my grandma told me
this one's a toaster oven.
Crying toaster oven.
The hat loses all its color.
It's sad.
But then the man
with the curly mustache comes in.
And he sees the hat, and he's so excited.
And it gets its color back.
And then he puts the hat on,
and they're perfect together.
They both turn a nice color.
The book has a lot of colors.
And then...
he buys it, and he leaves,
and it's sunshine out.
And it's so nice, and he's so happy.
And then there's another man
and he wants a hat.
And it's going to start all over
with that man.
And then the man with the mustache
flies away with his mustache.
I love this book.
The Hat by Marc Maron."
Okay. Let's get down to it.
So, what's going on with me?
I'm dating a painter, and it's going well.
She's, like, a real painter.
Abstract painter.
Big canvases. Big colorful canvases.
It's so nice to go out with somebody who...
I... No part of me thinks like:
"I could do that." Like, no part of me.
It's a very healthy thing
to not have that in a relationship.
But she does these amazing paintings,
and I'm in awe of her.
She's just this little, you know,
woman who, like, doesn't talk a whole lot.
And I don't know where it comes from.
Just huge, beautiful, abstract canvases.
I'll have a day, I'll go by her studio,
and I'll look at them like:
"Holy shit, where does that come from?
That's fucking amazing, baby."
She's like, "Oh, thanks, baby."
And then she goes,
"Well, what did you do today?
What'd you do today?"
I'm like...
It says... It says,
"We will all be immortalized as content."
It's pretty good, right?
I almost killed a kid.
But it's going good.
And I don't know. It's weird,
because, like, sometimes I don't know
the point of a relationship.
She knows
that I feel that way sometimes.
Because, look,
I'm, you know, twice divorced.
Got no kids.
I own my house.
I don't need to be married again.
I don't need to live with anybody.
I don't need kids.
I just wanna do
whatever the fuck I wanna do.
And that's not a great dating profile.
Um...
But she's hanging in there.
You know, we're doing okay.
But I don't always know
what the point of a relationship is.
And I ask people, like,
"What's the point?
What's the point of a relationship?"
And they say things like,
"You don't wanna be alone."
And I'm like, "I don't know.
What's so bad about being alone?
You just nap more, you know?
The hours between, like,
5 and 7 p.m. are rough
'cause that's when you're just
sitting there thinking:
'Other people have other people.
And they're probably eating dinner
together right now.'"
And that's when
you pull up Clomper porn, and...
jerk off and nap.
And then you wake up
and it's dark out. And you're like:
"It's like a whole different day.
I'm gonna play guitar."
And then people say,
"Well, you don't wanna get old alone."
And I'm like,
"You're not really selling me."
And then it always comes down to this one,
"But you don't wanna die alone."
Ooh.
And my first thought is always like,
"We'll get a fucking nurse." Like...
Seriously.
We'll get a nice Jamaican lady. I mean...
Who would you rather have
at your deathbed?
Someone who loves you just like,
"Oh, my God!
This is so awful. It's so sad.
I'm so sorry, baby.
I'm so sorry. It's so sad."
Or just a woman looking at you going,
"It's okay, baby.
It's okay.
Let go, baby.
Let go."
See, I could've ended there, right?
That felt like a good ending.
Applause. I could've gotten right up,
bowed, waved.
"Thank you." But no,
I'm still sitting here like an idiot.
Because I think it's cynical.
I think it's a little cynical.
And I've gotta live with this thing
for the rest of my life.
Whatever I do on this thing.
And I don't wanna leave it that cynical.
I got a kitten.
And I say kitten like that.
I don't know when I decided to do that,
but I'm committed. I say "kitten."
I don't know why, but I choose to do it.
So, I got a kitten.
I did not want the kitten.
I did not want it.
And neither did my two older retired cats.
They did not want the kitten.
We were fine, the three of us.
Just hanging out comfortably.
Monkey on the chair laying there,
Lafonda laying over here.
Me sitting there just looking at them
like, "Everything good?"
They're like, "Yeah, we're good."
"You want to play?"
"Nope. That shit's behind us.
Don't even think about picking up
that laser pointer.
Don't make us chase a lie for 15 minutes.
We're onto the red dot, man.
We're onto it."
They didn't want a kitten.
They did not want a kitten.
But I came home one night after working.
Doing comedy. I lock up the house,
I turn out the lights,
I'm about to go to bed.
And out on the front porch I hear:
And I'm like, "What?"
And I go pull the curtain back,
and there's this little two-month-old
black kitten sitting there.
Aw...
That's the proper response.
That is not the response I had.
My response was, "Oh, fuck.
Now I gotta fucking love you now?"
And oddly,
that's how all my relationships start.
But I don't... Why my house?
Why my house? Why?
I live way out east in L.A. County.
I'm up in the hills.
There's coyotes, there's skunks,
raccoons, possums, cars.
I saw no pregnant cats.
I saw no other kittens.
I don't know where it came from.
Why my house?
And when I'm confounded, I'll go mystical.
So...
It went from,
"Why my house?" to, "Who is that?"
Which one of my dead friends
that I didn't have closure with
has come back in this form...
to make things right?
And that is one thing that that kitten
did not anticipate,
was being brought into
a human man's house,
be held tightly, and have
the human man say:
"Who are you?
Who are you?
Who are you?"
I got no answer. 'Cause it's a cat.
But he fucked up my couch inside a week.
Destroyed an arm of the couch
inside a week.
So, I'm pretty sure it's Dave.
Dave died many years ago.
There was some undone shit between us.
And I didn't think I'd see him again,
'cause he was dead.
But now he's living with me in the form
of a black kitten I call Buster.
It's nice to be hanging out
with Dave again, you know what I mean?
We went to high school together,
and we kind of reminisce
about high school.
It's mostly me talking, you know?
And he just plays with a fake mouse.
And...
I'm like, "Remember that time
we got drunk and saw Van Halen?"
He's like:
I'm like, "I knew you did, man.
That was a good time."
Old cats, not happy.
Monkey, not happy.
Kitten's pouncing on him constantly.
Pouncing on him.
So, every time I look at Monkey,
he's like, "Why? Why? Goddamn it.
Why, Marc? I don't get it... Goddamn it.
I didn't need this shit.
I don't know how much time I have left."
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you so much. I appreciate it.
Great crowd. Real honor. I love you guys.
Thank you very much.
All right, that's good.