Miranda!
Please welcome to the stage
Miranda Sings!
Miranda, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be on stage!
I can't go on stage right now. I'm busy!
Busy doing what?
Hello. I'm waiting for this
scab to form so I can pick it.
Uh, change of plans.
Please welcome to the stage
Colleen Ballinger!
Oh, my God!
Hello, everybody!
This is crazy!
We're doing a Netflix special
at the Kennedy Centre. What?
This is nuts!
Oh, my gosh.
And you guys are never gonna
believe me when I tell you this, but...
I'm pregnant.
There's a tiny little
penis in there.
Is that weird?
Are there kids here?
You know, pregnancy
is the most beautiful,
magical, wonderful thing
in the whole world...
for everyone who isn't pregnant.
I am so miserable.
This is awful.
No one tells you how
much this is gonna suck.
I am so grumpy.
I am in so much pain.
I am constipated.
And I've been to the doctor,
I've seen the baby.
He's down here.
So then, what's all this?
People come up to me
and they want to rub my tummy,
and they're like,
'Oh, how sweet. A baby,'
and I'm like, 'That's not a baby.
I haven't pooped in two weeks.'
'But keep rubbing.
Maybe it will help.'
I'm very excited to have this little guy.
I can't wait to be a mom.
But I'm gonna admit something
to you guys tonight.
I am so nervous.
I'm so nervous to have him.
But I'm not nervous for the
reasons you might think.
I'm not nervous 'cause I have
to push a baby out of my parts
and they're all going to rip into pieces.
I'm not nervous
because I'm going to be
responsible for
another human being.
I'm nervous because this kid
is going to have my genes,
and I looked like this
when I was a baby!
That's not photo shopped.
That's my actual face.
And I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, 'Oh, that was
probably just an awkward phase.'
You know, all babies look
weird in pictures sometimes.'
Oh, no. I was a very ugly
baby, and I have proof.
This is also me as a baby.
And this is me as a baby.
And my personal favourite...
This is me as a baby.
And to any of you
out there who think,
'Oh, you know what?
It'll get better.
You know, you'll grow out of that,'
you must be forgetting that
this is what I do for a living.
So no, it doesn't get better.
And if this kid looks anything
like me when he comes out,
I'm gonna be like, 'Put him back!'
Just kidding.
I'll love him no matter how ugly he is.
I'll just love him less.
Oh, how am I going to
explain that to my child?
He's gonna be so confused.
He's gonna think he lives in a
house with a mommy and a daddy,
and sometimes mommy disappears
and a crazy girl with lipstick
and a camel toe
chases him around the
house with a camera.
Like, what's he gonna
tell his friends
that his mom does for a living?
What's he gonna do?
Show them this picture?
His friends are gonna be like,
'My mom's a doctor.'
'Well, my mom's a teacher.'
And he's gonna be like,
'My mom does this.'
Oh, God. Why did I give him that voice?
Just assuming he's doomed.
Oh, God.
We can get rid of that.
You know, uh, I've
been doing that...
for ten years now.
I've been doing Miranda.
Whoo!
So long of doing a character
that everybody hates.
Everyone hates me. It's true.
I have made a career off of
people hating my character.
Are there any parents
in the audience tonight?
Hey! Thanks for coming.
You guys hate me the most.
No, don't worry, though.
If you're a parent and you
feel like you were just dragged
to some dumb YouTuber's
show tonight,
you were. Gotcha.
But also,
I try really hard to make my
show enjoyable for everybody.
So yes, there are some
jokes for the kids tonight.
But there's also a lot of
mature, inappropriate jokes
that will go over
the kids' heads.
No offence to you kids,
but you guys are... dumb,
so they'll go over your heads...
and then the parents will have
something to laugh at, don't worry.
Uh, but it is true.
I get a lot of hate from the mothers.
Hi. Uh...
You all say the same thing to me
when you meet me, too, the moms.
And I think
you think this is a compliment,
but you always say...
'I don't know why
my kid likes you.'
Fighting back tears.
I remember this one time I met a girl
at a mall, and she was so sweet.
I was so excited to meet her.
She watched my videos.
She was a big fan.
But her mom was standing, like,
two feet from us and she looked pissed.
So I went up to her
to introduce myself,
and she goes,
'Oh, I know who you are.'
'If I have to hear your voice in my house
one more time, I swear to God...'
And I was like...
'Thank you.'
I did an interview with this guy once,
and he was so rude.
He did not want to be
talking to me at all.
And at the end of the
interview, he goes,
'All right. I have
one final question.'
I interview a lot of comedians.
'Is there a reason why
they're funny and you're not?'
True story. He said that.
And in my head, I was like,
'Well, is there a reason
why you're a dick?'
But I didn't say that
because there are kids here.
I said something better.
He said, 'Is there a reason why
comedians are funny and you're not?'
And I said...
'Thank you.'
So I'm very uncomfortable when it
comes to confrontation and hate,
but I'm a little bit better at it
when I can hide behind my camera
like a coward.
So I write songs about
the hate that I get,
and I would love to sing one
for you guys tonight if that's cool?
Yes! Awesome.
I've got my ukulele.
So...
I have to warn you,
all of the lyrics to this song are
hate comments that I have received.
So there's a lot of bad words,
and there is some crude
language in this song.
So to all of the mothers that
I'm about to offend, um...
thank you.
'Why are you a YouTuber?
I'm not a hater. I just hate your vids.
And your voice.'
'You look uglier than my ass.
No ofoinse.'
'Does she have cancer?
Because I don't want to
make fun of her if she does.
She's so effing annoying.'
'Your cloths are so ugly.
Maybe you need to go into a model class.'
Your cloths look like pyjamas.
'You don't know
what you're wearing.
You look good to you.
You look bad to me.'
'# 'Roses are red, violets are blue #
# Pornhub is down
Colleen Ballinger will do' #
# 'Her face is a rip-off, so sad' #
# 'Nice fonking forehead' #
# 'Butt #
# Head' #
# 'Toltoly stupid' #
# 'I hatte you with a passion'
Thumbs up #
# 'Her face scarets me
She neds more make-up' #
# 'She has a uniboob' #
# 'I'm pretty sure her vagina
Smells like cat food' #
That one's accurate.
# You might think that I'm hurt
Or I'm feeling abused #
# But I'm not, I'm getting paid
From your comments and views #
# So keep the comments coming #
# But here's some help #
# Before you go insulting people
Maybe learn how to spell #
# Dum-da-dum #
# You sound so dumb, dumb, dumb #
# You sound so dumb #
'What the duck is wrong with her face?
Duck, duck, duck!'
'There are eight-year-olds watching this.'
'She looks fat but still pretty.'
# 'I think she might be a dude' #
# 'You remind me of a raisin
'Cause you have wrinkles #
# And everyone hates you' #
# 'You look like Maranda'
'You look like Mirada' #
# 'Are you Mirinda?'
'Are you Amanda?' #
# 'Are you Mirrranda?'
'Are you a Marinade Sings? No ofens #
You know, I'm not a marinade,
so, none taken.
# You might think that I'm hurt
Or I'm feeling abused #
# But I'm not, I'm getting paid
From your comments and views #
# So keep the comments coming #
# But here's some help #
# Before you go insulting people
Maybe learn how to spell #
# Dum-da-dum #
# You sound so dumb, dumb, dumb
You sound so dumb #
Everybody! # Dum-da-dum #
There you go. # Dum-da-dum #
# You sound so dumb, dumb, dumb #
# You sound so dumb #
One more time! # Dum-da-dum #
# Dum-da-dum #
# You sound so dumb, dumb, dumb #
# You sound so dumb #
There you go!
There you go.
You know,
I get a lot of hate, as you can see.
Uh, but you know what?
The hate doesn't really
bother me that much.
I'm usually able to let the hate
just roll off my shoulders.
But every once in a while,
there's just one
comment that gets to me.
This has happened
more frequently recently
because I'm pregnant
and I'm very emotional.
I cry at everything now.
Um, so recently,
I was upset about
some of the hate
comments I was getting,
and I needed to do something
to make myself feel better.
So I did something
that I know you all have done,
so you cannot shame me
when I tell you what I did.
But I Googled myself.
See,
I thought if I Googled
myself, I would feel better,
but that's not what happened.
What happened was
I noticed these words in bold.
These are the most frequently searched
things on Google.
So I thought I would play with this
and see what you guys
were searching about me,
and I typed in, 'Is Colleen Ballinger...'
And the most frequently searched
thing on Google
when you type in,
'Is Colleen Ballinger...' is...
'dead.'
So that did not
make me feel better.
So I tried something else.
I typed in...
'Did Colleen Ballinger...'
And the most frequently
searched thing on Google
when you type in,
'Did Colleen Ballinger...' is...
'die.'
So...
I tried something
a little bit more obscure,
and I typed in,
'Where was Colleen Ballinger...'
thinking there is no way
that this could
be about me dying.
Well, I was wrong
because it was...
'buried.'
So thank you. I love my fans.
So when Googling myself
did not make me feel any better,
I did something that I've been
doing since I was a little girl
every time I feel low.
I wrote in my diary
about my feelings.
Now, this is actually what
inspired my most recent book,
called My Diarrhe
by Miranda Sings.
Some of you brought it.
Thank you.
You guys are the best!
So, yes, I recently
came out with a book,
and it's all of Miranda's
diaries duct-taped together.
Now, the entire
inspiration for this book
was my actual diaries as a child
because they are
horrendously embarrassing.
So I thought, to celebrate
such a special night,
we're doing a Netflix special,
we're at the Kennedy
Centre, this is epic.
I should read to you
some of my most
embarrassing pages
from my diaries as a child.
What do you think?
Yes!
I was gonna do it
even if you didn't scream,
so thank you.
So this is one of my diaries
from when I was a child.
And I found some, uh,
just very embarrassing pages
to read to you guys from.
This is from when I
was about 12 years old,
um, this picture
that I'm about to show you.
Let's take a look.
Yep, there it is.
Oh, God.
So it says...
-It says, 'What's wrong with me?'
-Nothing!
And I'm on the
'road to nowhere.'
I want you guys to get
an idea in your mind
of what I looked like
during this time of my life,
this emo, depressed little girl.
So I brought a picture of
myself for you guys to see...
what I looked like then.
Let's continue.
Here we go.
'Dear Marsha...'
Oh, by the way, I never called
my diary 'diary' for some reason.
I always gave it a name.
I think I thought it would make
me feel like I had friends.
So here we go.
'Dear Marsha.'
Sorry I haven't written in a while,
but I have been very busy.
Here are all the things
I have been doing.
One, went to church.
Two, started sixth grade.
Three, got lots of
new Beanie Babies.
'Four, lost my Tamagotchi.'
'Five, practised miming.'
Now, this sounds like a joke,
but I legit took mime
classes as a kid.
Uh, I have proof.
This is me...
as a child mime.
Um, I was home-schooled.
Okay, moving on.
So five was 'practised miming.'
-And then, 'Six, my cat ran away.'
-Aww.
'Seven, found my cat.
It's dead.'
Aww.
'I have been doing a
lot more stuff, too,
but I'm tired and
can't write anymore.'
I most likely will only write
when I'm having
problems, or puberty,
or I'm just bored from now on,
so don't expect many letters.
'Good night. Love, Colleen.'
Well...
You guys are cheering
'cause you think it's over.
I'm sorry, it's not.
There's more.
So, uh, I did write when
I went through puberty.
So I want to show you one of my
favourite pages from that time.
'Personal note. My boobs are popping
out and they are killing me.'
And I drew a picture in case anyone
wants to know what that looks like.
It hurts.
So puberty did not do me well.
I had a really hard time during
puberty, as most kids do.
And you will see that
reflected on this next page.
'Hate, hate, hate,
hate, hate, hate, hate,
hate, hate, hate
times a million.'
This is my feelings
towards life.
'Lava lamps are really cool...
Colleen Ballinger.'
So...
Now, when I was looking for pages
to read to you guys tonight,
um, I found this one page in my
diary that is so embarrassing,
so mortifying,
that I could not
possibly read it myself.
That's how bad it is.
So I'm going to have the help
of my best friend, Kory DeSoto...
to come read this to you.
This is Kory.
Kory.
They love Kory!
I do, too.
He's the best.
So Kory...
is my best friend, and he has
been for many, many years.
Now, Kory and I
met doing theatre,
and we have a strange obsession
with bad theatre and bad acting.
So I have requested that he
read the worst page of my diary
as a bad-acted monologue
for you guys tonight, so...
Oh, by the way, before
he gets started,
I just want to let you know
that this is no ordinary journal.
This is my prayer journal.
So these are my thoughts to God.
Keep that in mind.
Scene.
'Precious Daddy...'
'I need you to provide me'
with a lot of patience right now
because I keep on getting these
dirty looks from this girl...
'Taryn.'
'At the last prayer circle, she asked
for us to pray for her grandma.'
But if she keeps on giving
me these dirty looks,
'I am not gonna pray for her.'
'Sorry. Satan got a hold of me there...'
Oh...
'Anyways...'
in other news, let's
talk about boys...
or lack thereof.
Am I a mutant or something?
Why can't I get a boyfriend?
'Good times...'
'Not really.'
'Amen.'
Give it up for Kory
DeSoto, everybody!
Okay.
Now,
I could keep reading to you
from my emo high school
and junior high diaries,
or I could read to you from
my favourite childhood diary,
which is the poop diary.
Unfortunately, this is
exactly what it sounds like.
My mother, she has four kids,
and she was trying
to figure out a way
to get closer to
us, to bond with us.
Um, she wanted us to open up
to her more about our feelings.
So she came up with
this brilliant idea.
'I know. I'll put a diary
next to the toilet,'
and that way, whenever
they're doing that,
'they can write to me
about their feelings.'
She thought this
would help us to bond.
Now, obviously, this
wasn't the greatest idea,
and I have proof, because I'm
going to read you some pages
from the poop diary.
So these are conversations
between me and my mother, okay?
So the first page here,
it starts with my mother.
She asks me...
'How is choir going?'
And I said...
'Fine. I have diariah again!'
'Every time I eat
cheese, I have...'
Arrow to 'diariah.'
So...
My mom's great idea
wasn't really working.
Um, but she didn't
give up, my mother.
She knew this poop
diary would work,
so she tried again.
And I'm gonna read
to you another page.
This one actually
starts with me.
I said...
'That turkey stuff you
made for your diet dinner
smelled better than it taste.'
And then she said,
'Yes, it did.'
And I said,
'I have diariah!'
So...
it was a good attempt
from my mother,
but obviously, the
poop diary backfired.
But you know what? Actually, my
mom and I are really close now,
so maybe it worked. Moms, try
out poop diaries with your kids.
By the way, I thought
this was a normal thing
that everyone had in their homes
until I was about 16 years old.
So that was an
embarrassing conversation
to have with my
friends in high school
and be like, 'Uh,
where's your poop diary?'
Ah.
Anyway, let me get rid of this.
So...
listen up.
I know why you guys
are here, all right?
So who's excited to
see Miranda Sings?
All righty.
Let's see if she's ready.
She's not, so I'm
gonna do another song.
But maybe if I sing this,
Miranda will come out to play.
Now, I am a musical
theatre dork.
My background is in theatre.
I love theatre.
And so when I first started
doing Miranda ten years ago,
my entire show was
just Broadway songs.
So I would like
to pay my respects
to the beginning
of Miranda Sings
and sing a theatre song for you
guys right now, if that's cool.
Perhaps if I sing this,
Miranda will come out to play.
This is 'Defying Gravity.'
# Something has changed within me #
# Something is not the same #
# I'm through with playing by the rules #
# Of someone else's game #
# Too late for second guessing #
# Too late to go back to sleep #
# It's time to trust my instincts #
# Close my eyes and leap #
# It's time to try defying gravity #
# I think I'll try defying gravity #
# And you can't pull me down... #
# So if you care to find me #
# Look to the western sky #
# For those who told me lately #
# Everyone deserves a chance to fly #
# And if I'm flying solo #
# At least I'm flying free #
# To those who'd ground me #
# Take a message back from me #
# Tell them how I am defying gravity #
# I'm flying high #
# I'm defying gravity #
# And soon I'll match them in renown #
# And nobody in all of Oz #
# No wizard that there is or was #
# Is ever going to bring me #
# Down #
# Bring me down #
# Oh, whoa! #
Hey, guys. It's me, Miranda.
I'm so excited to be here
at the Kennedy Centre tonight.
Are you guys excited?
You'd better be excited
'cause you're here to see
the most miraculous,
amazing person in
the entire world,
Miranda Sings!
It's true.
I'm the most
incredible person ever.
I'm a famous singer, dancer,
actor, model, magician,
other things...
But you guys are in
for a treat tonight
'cause not only do I do all
of those amazing things...
Oh, no. That stuff doesn't
even matter anymore.
You guys are in the
presence of greatness
because tonight,
standing before you
is the very next
Virgin Mary!
It's true. I am with child.
I am expecting a little
brat pretty soon.
Now, obviously, I would
never do the nasty,
which means I am the
next Virgin Mary.
But I have some
sceptics out there.
Some people don't think
I'm actually the next Virgin Mary.
Well, I'm about to prove it to you.
You are in the presence
of freaking greatness.
Watch this.
Hit it!
# Halle... # Oh, shoot.
# Hallelujah #
# Hallelujah, hallelujah #
# Look at me, I'm a pregnant queen #
# Baby's coming soon, my poor tookie #
# But it probably won't hurt
because God chose me #
# To be the next Holy Virgin Mary #
# Well, you don't think
I'm the next Virgin Mary? #
# A lot of magical things
Have been happening to me lately #
# To prove I'm the chosen one #
# Currently have two brains in me #
# So I'm double smarter than everybody #
# When I sneeze, I pee simultaneously #
# I don't need a table
I just use my belly #
# Haven't pooped in weeks
And I'm still alive #
# Got a tiny little penis in me
At all times #
# I see everything, I've got four eyes #
# And my booty's looking thick
'Cause I've got four thighs #
# Do the waddle, do the waddle #
# Before he comes out
He needs to repent #
# He's kicking and grabbing me
Without my consent #
# Stop grabbing my tookie
Or I'll make you pay rent #
# If he keeps it up
He could become the next president #
# Virgin Miranda #
# The holiest of all #
See, just proved it.
I am the next Virgin
Holy Miranda, all right?
Now, when I announced
this on the internet,
I had a lot of people
being very offended
that I said I was
the next Virgin Mary.
Which is ridiculous!
Look at these comments.
People are saying things
like, 'I'm affended.'
'This video offiended me.'
'Ew, Ur preginanit.'
But you know what?
I realized people
are gonna be offended
whether I'm preginanit or not.
Because everybody is offended
by everything these days.
It's ridiculous!
You can't do anything
without offending someone.
It's so annoying.
Like, I can't even post
an Instagram picture
without ticking someone off.
Look at these, okay.
This picture
offended the vegans.
offended the mothers.
This picture offended... everyone.
So friggin' annoying.
But then I realized something.
I was doing it all wrong.
Because you can actually
say whatever you want
and do whatever you want
and not get in trouble for it,
as long as you say
two little words.
No offence!
That's right. 'No offence.'
Hit it!
Listen up, leotards. I'm about
to teach you two magic words
that make it so you can
say whatever you want,
whenever you want,
and not suffer consequences.
# Feel like you're offending everyone
These days? #
# Feel like you're losing friends
No matter what you say? #
# There's a way to say offensive things
And not look bad #
# Just say these two little words
And no one's allowed to be mad #
# I hope you get a paper cut #
# No offence #
# Even your grandma thinks you suck #
# Your face looks exactly like your butt #
# No offence #
# I bet Comic Sans is your favourite font #
See, that's all you gotta say.
In a normal situation,
you go up to someone
and say, 'You're ugly.'
That's really rude.
But if you just finish it off
with, 'You're ugly. No offence,'
they can't get mad.
See? Now,
some of my haters have
yet to learn this lesson.
They're saying very rude,
offensive things to me
and not saying, 'No offence,'
which is really titting me off,
and I'm gonna show you right
now what I'm talking about.
People are telling
me that I did porn
in order to get pregnant.
Which is not true.
I would never
participate in the nasty.
Now, I need to prove it to you
so I can prove that I'm
actually the next Virgin Mary.
So I'm gonna prove I would
never participate in a porn.
Now, what you might not know
is that porn is
happening all around you.
Even right now, there are people
being porn in this very room,
and I cannot have that.
So I'm going to need two
volunteers right now.
Hmm.
Let's see here.
Um, how about you right
here in the red pants?
I need one more.
There's a lot of you.
Um, how about in the skirt, right here?
Yeah, in the skirt.
Come on up.
Hello.
-What's your name?
-Calita.
Calita!
Wow, do you have a dragon?
Is that you, the
Mother of the Dragons?
No.
I got you confused
with someone else.
So anyways...
Hi. Okay.
So...
Listen, in order to talk
about this first type of porn,
I'm gonna need my pointer.
I really want to make sure you
guys are paying attention, okay?
So just give me a second.
Okay.
Listen up.
Calita over here
is wearing a nice button-up shirt
all the way to the tippity top,
nice long sleeves,
pants that go all the
way down to the floor.
This is very nice.
Very conservative.
This is a perfect example of not porn.
This...
is porn, okay?
Her skirt is so short,
all it will take is one
really big gust of wind
and we'll see all the
creases and crevices.
And the top goes so low we can
the entire chesticle crack.
This is a perfect
example of porn.
-So what's your name?
-Sarah.
Exactly.
No offence.
So here we have porn, not porn.
Porn, not porn.
Do not fret, Sarah. I'mma help you out.
I know you're a Mirfanda.
However, give Calita
a round of applause.
Thank you.
Go away.
Get off. Okay.
Come here, Sarah.
Oh, this is bad news.
Listen, you are in the presence
of a biblical holy figure, okay?
I cannot have my Mirfandas
walking around dressed porn-y,
so I gotta fix this.
Lucky for you, I brought
something with me tonight
in case there was a Sarah here.
I use this whenever I see
someone looking porn-ish.
Okay?
This is the stretchy
solution to porn.
So what you do is, whenever
you see someone dressed porn,
you just put this
on their head...
and then you just...
Like this. See?
Very nice.
However...
she is such a severe
case of the porn.
Turn around.
This is so tight, we can see the
entire shape of the badonkadonk.
Inappropriate!
Which means this needs
to go, all right?
This is never going to work.
There is only one
thing that we can do
for someone who is
this porn-y, okay?
This I only do in severe cases,
so please,
help me...
and pray for Sarah.
Okay?
Thank you, Sarah.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Okay. Listen, I can't have that.
I can't have my Mirfandas
dressing porn-y, okay?
You represent me now.
So everybody, look to your
left, look to your right,
see if anybody's dressed
porn-y right now.
Put a hand on them
and pray for them.
Let's get rid of the porn
together, one prayer at a time.
Very good, yes.
Very nice. Oh, this girl's praying
for her mom in the front row.
What the heck?
The mom's all happy.
She's like, 'I am porn.'
Okay.
Now, listen, I wish that was the
only type of porn that there is,
but there's lots
of types of porn.
And this next type of porn
is the most common
and the worst one of all.
It's porn-style dancing.
I know you kids.
You like to go out to
da club and bust a move.
But I don't want to see you doing
any of these nasty booty shakes
and booty twerks.
It's disgusting
and inappropriate.
The only type of dancing
my Mirfandas should be doing
is my type of dancing.
So if you know it,
I want to see you do it.
This is 'Do The Miranda!'
Hit it!
All right, Miranda
Sings in the house!
Get up out of your seats.
I want to see you dancing
right now, having a good time.
All right. Here we go.
# Hey, you over there
With the porn-y hair #
# I got what you need #
# Hey, you there, bro
With the camel toe #
# Come and just follow my lead #
# A new dance is here
And I fear, my dear #
# That you're all looking like hoes #
# So cover your backs
And your chesticle cracks #
# 'Cause here is how it goes #
# Lift your legs up high
Poke your neighbour in the eye #
# Paint a rainbow in the sky
Wipe it till it's dry #
# Then twerk like me
But don't make it slutty #
# It's as easy as can be, so follow me #
# Let's do it again #
# Do the Miranda #
# Oh, yeah #
# Do the Miranda! #
Very nice.
I see lots of you know
how to do the Miranda.
Very good.
I saw some of you
not participating.
Mothers.
So congratulations.
You will never get a boyfriend.
No offence.
Okay, listen.
We have a lot to
discuss tonight.
I can't spend this much
time on freaking porn,
so we got to move on
to the next thing, okay?
Because, listen, there's one
thing that the Virgin Mary had
that I don't have yet.
This is a problem, okay?
She had a Joseph.
I don't have a Joseph
yet to my Mary.
So I got a question for you.
Where my baes at?
# I'm about to break it down #
# Sing along if you know it #
# All right, here we go #
# Every time I look around
All I ever see #
# Is people being jealous
And they wanna look like me #
# I've got Tyler, Ricky, Joey
And the Dolan twins too #
# My uncle and Lohanthony
But I'm my favourite boo #
# Got a lot more
But I forgot who they are #
# Sorry, not sorry
Just a superstar #
# Got lots of baes
Are you wondering how I do? #
# Take a little listen
I'll find a bae for you #
# Hey, where my baes at? #
# Where my baes at? #
# I got so many baes, man #
# I'll teach you how to get one too #
# Where my baes at in the house? #
Whoa, so many baes.
You know what, guys?
I'm not joking around.
I really need to find a bae.
I am six months
pregnant already,
so I need to find a
daddy to this kid.
Love you, Patrick!
Hi, Patrick.
Hey, Miranda.
Patrick, what are you doing here?
I haven't seen you
in, like, six months.
Uh... Well, I...
I heard the, um...
That you, uh...
That you're with
child, and, um...
I thought maybe you could
use some protection.
Patrick...
It's a little late for that.
Besides, we can't be together.
You know this.
Netflix owns the rights to you,
and the show got cancelled.
I could get sued.
So you need to go.
I don't want to get sued.
I don't have insurance.
Go away. Hurry.
Before anyone sees. Yes.
Please go, Patrick, please.
Oh, don't give me that.
I didn't cancel the show!
Just kidding. I'm grateful
for the experience.
I love Netflix so much.
You know, I can't eat this.
It makes the baby
kick me in my tookie,
so does anyone want it?
What about in the balcony?
Do you want it up there?
Get ready.
That was for you.
Now, listen, okay.
I wasn't kidding.
Before I was rudely
interrupted by Patrick,
I really do have a surprise
for you guys tonight.
We all know I need to get
a daddy to this baby ASAP,
so I called up my number-one bae
and said I was doing
a very special show tonight
in Washington DC at
the Kennedy Centre.
This guy has millions
of subscribers,
millions of views,
very, very famous.
My number-one bae.
Do you know who it is?
Joey Graceffa!
But he said he
couldn't come, so...
That would have been
great, though, huh,
if he was here.
The parents are all
laughing at their kids.
They're crying.
You know what?
He's not here, but you guys are.
Who wants to be my bae tonight?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop. Are you kidding me?
I see so many girls
raising their hands.
I'm not a Lebanese.
Boys, please. No offence.
Let's see here.
We got lots of options. Ooh.
How about in the white
sweatshirt up there?
I need two more.
Two more.
Who do we got? Who do we got?
Okay, in the black hat.
I need one more.
Come on up, white
sweatshirt, black hat.
One more.
So many good options.
Okay, how about in the
purple shirt right here?
Come on up.
Ooh, hello.
Look at this sexy bae.
What is your name?
Nathan.
Nathan. Love that.
I love your face hairs.
Where are you from?
Barrie, Ontario.
Barrie, Ontario?
Oh. Sounds like an infection.
Oh, hey, Daddy.
What's your name?
My name is Anthony.
-Andronen? What?
-Anthony.
Anthony!
Okay.
You did not say that the first time.
Just saying.
Anthony, where are you from?
I'm from Bayonne, New Jersey. 'Bay.'
-Bayonne. I'm the bae.
-Ooh.
I get it.
Whatever.
Good talk. Okay.
Oh, hey. You're much
shorter up close.
Um, what's your name?
Aldair.
Are you related to Andrew
over there, All-dayer?
Yeah.
'Sure. That works.' Aldair.
I love it. It's
like, 'All-dayer!'
'I could do an all-dayer!'
Good. Okay.
Cool.
Um, where are you from, Aldair?
My mom's belly.
What do you do for a living?
Uh...
watch you on YouTube.
We have a flirt in
the house tonight.
Okay, Aldair.
Love that.
Now, I have three
very sexy men...
boys on stage.
All of them...
are ready and excited to be
the father to this child.
Um, so you can all handle
this responsibility, you think?
Promising.
Okay. Now, here's the deal.
I can't have all three
of them being the daddy,
so I'm gonna pick one,
but how I'm gonna do that
is I'm gonna woo them
with my charms and my talents
and my vocal abilities.
And whoever I have the
most chemistry with
will become the
daddy to this child.
So all you guys have to do
is stay right where you are.
I will come to you,
so just come...
Oh, yes. You can come to me.
I will be doing all of the work.
If the chemistry is
there, it's there.
-All right? Are you ready for it?
-Absolutely.
Hit it!
# What up, everybody? New year, new me #
# You can smell me coming
Like asparagus pee #
# I'm so sexy, I'm just like a zit #
# That's what everybody stares at
And you want to touch it #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# You see me walking by
And you are shook #
# Summer loving, had me a blast #
# Summer loving, happened so fast #
# Met a boy, crazy for me #
# Met a boy, cute as can be #
# Summer dreams #
# Ripped at the seams #
# But #
# Oh #
# Those summer #
# Nights #
Wow.
There is so much chemistry
on stage right now.
Like I said,
I can only pick one bae to
be the daddy to this child,
so I'm gonna get out something
called the bae-ometer.
The bae-ometer also
happens to be my hand.
So I'm just gonna take it,
put it over their head,
and the bae you think
I had the most chemistry with,
cheer for, okay?
So here we go.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
Oh.
This is so awkward. I won.
But give them a round of applause.
They did such a good job.
Call me when you're
older, Aldair.
Thank you. Go away.
You can leave now. Get away.
Well, now I'm single.
So...
Don't worry, guys, okay?
Don't worry.
I can handle the responsibility
of being the mother
and the father to this baby.
Easy-peasy.
I have been preparing for
this moment my entire life.
I was born holy.
Born the holiest of holes.
And I have proof.
I have been acting
like and dressing like
biblical characters
my entire life.
I have pictures from when
I was a wee little tot
dressing like every famous
biblical character there ever was.
Look at this.
Here is me as an angel,
me as Moses,
me as mother Mary,
me, the prostitute.
See?
Every single biblical
character I have played.
Not only that. Look
at this picture.
That's me with the
circle around her.
I'm putting on a
play in the backyard
with some neighbourhood friends.
'What's the play?'
You might ask.
The crucifixion of Jesus Christ.
See, there's the
cross, right up there.
We're about to kill that little boy,
and I am really ticked off.
Not only did I do plays and
act like a biblical character,
but I also always
was very charitable,
and I was very compassionate.
Here, you'll see me
being compassionate,
not only towards
people, but to animals.
Here, I'm playing with my
favourite pet I ever had.
Right there, Charlie the Fly.
Next.
Oh. This is me doing
some charity work.
As you can see, the hardest
charity work there is,
hanging out with a girl
with really ugly bangs.
So...
That was a tough day for me.
Emotional.
Next.
Oh, here's me doing
more charity work.
I'm singing for complete
strangers for free.
Look, they love it.
This guy on this end,
he's like, 'Yaas!'
So... Next.
Oh, this is great
'cause it shows
how everyone has
always adored me,
setting me up for a
life of being adored
by everyone as the
Virgin Miranda.
These boys love me.
They adore me.
They want to be with me so bad,
they can't even keep
their shirts on.
So these are my cousins.
You know, growing up, for me,
was always really easy
'cause I was always the most
popularest girl in school,
president of the drama club,
homecoming queen, prom
king, everything, so...
Being home-schooled is great.
And it really helped prepare me
to become the Virgin Miranda.
But you know what?
I don't want to stand up here
and just brag about
how amazing I am.
I need to show you
So how would you
guys like if I did
some charity work
for you tonight?
That's what I thought.
I'm gonna give you the best
gift anyone could ever receive
in the entire world.
I'm going to make all
of you internet famous!
That's what I thought.
Now, listen.
I'm gonna do a
video for you guys,
so say hello to the internet!
# Say hello to the internet #
Hello! We're so famous!
There you go, guys.
Wow!
You guys are gonna get
so famous from that.
Millions of people will see that
if I ever choose to post it.
It's crazy.
Oh, shoot. I just realized something.
Oh, no!
I just made you all
internet famous,
and that means you guys are
all gonna start getting haters.
It's true!
When you get famous on the
internet, you get tons of haters,
so I need to teach
you guys how to deal
with these freaking
bullies online, okay?
Because, listen, you could
be minding your own business
and post an innocent
little video.
Something like this.
Where My Baes At?
A classic music video,
and you could end up
with hate comments like this...
'If she were any more inbred,
she would be a sandwich.'
See what I'm saying?
It doesn't end there.
Look at this one.
'You suck @, go to @.
No one likes you, okay,
so stop singing and @.'
Okay, listen. The worst
part about this hate mail
is not the fact that
they said a bad word,
it's not the fact they
told me to go die,
it's the fact that it
was written by a baby!
Look at that.
You can't trust
babies these days.
Look at this one.
'Ugly piece of @.
I hope you @-ing die.'
Now, Joe Bob responded to
his own comment and he said,
'Subscribe to me, please.'
No, thank you.
See what I'm saying?
You're gonna get hate like
this every single day,
and it doesn't matter what
kind of videos you post online.
They hate on all of them.
Look at this incredible video.
The Slurpee Bath video.
This is quality content, folks.
And I got hate on this.
Look at these comments.
'She looks like the type of girl
who would microwave her hamster.'
That was one time!
Next.
'What the @ you trying to
do to people, dread?'
You in some kind @-ing
mad people home owa?
Lord, have mercy.
Girl, hush your blasty mouth.
Nah. Set-ups. Only squawk,
squawk, squawk, squawk.
'You a @ parrot. Hush.'
Well...
MaddiNawwy is ticked off.
Next.
'You remind me of me. LOL.'
Now, at first, I thought
this was a fan mail
until I realized
it was from Anus!
I don't want to
remind you of an anus.
It's not even the
best part of the butt.
Now, the worst hate
mail I ever even gotted
was on one of my most incredible
music videos of all time,
Shake It Off.
This is a classic.
But I did get hate on it,
and here it is.
'The entire video,
I was wondering how she was
covering her monster size p-word.'
Are you kidding me?
I'm circumcised.
Next.
'Miranda, I'm little Russian boy
and I say you are slut and ugly.'
How rude.
Now, listen.
There is one more hate mail
I have to share with you.
It's the perfect
example of a hater.
Here it is.
'My dad came in, and
I switched to porn
because it was
easier to explain.'
So frigging wrong.
That's the type of hate I
deal with every single day,
and it's the type of hate all of you
guys are gonna have to deal with,
now that you're famous.
But you know what?
I know how to deal with this.
All you've got to do is say,
'Haters, back off.'
Let me hear you say it.
Haters, back off!
Exactly! You say, 'Haters, back off,'
to anyone who's bullying you,
anyone who's hating on you.
Your moms, your pets,
your carpets, your uncles.
I don't care who it is
'cause you know what?
Nobody bullies my Mirfandas,
except for me.
It's true.
Now, you know what?
I've been doing a lot of incredible
things for you guys tonight,
but now it's time
for me to do you
the greatest honour
of your lives.
I'm going to baptise you
all in the name of myself.
Are you ready for it?
This is gonna be an
incredible moment for you.
Now, in the church of myself,
how you baptise someone
is you show them
all of your talents.
So I'm gonna show you
that I'm not just a triple threat.
I am a five threat.
Acting, singing, dancing,
modelling, magician.
And I'm about to do
all five of my talents
on this stage to
baptise you all.
The first of many talents
is my modelling abilities.
You guys are about to see me
do the most incredible modelling,
runway walk, fashion show
you've ever seen in your entire life,
so get ready to have your
minds freaking blown.
Get ready for this.
# Your strip is served #
# Model, model, model, model #
That was incredible.
But you guys are not baptised yet.
Oh, no.
I know you probably are feeling
very baptised and holy,
but you won't be baptised and
holy until I do all my talents.
So the next talent is my dancing ability.
Who wants to see that?
Good, 'cause you're about to.
I'm about to blow your minds.
I'm gonna do every trendy,
iconic dance move that
has ever been created.
Hit it!
I'm about to prove I'm the
best dancer in the world.
Get ready!
# Dab, dab #
# Running man, running man
Run, run, running man #
# Whip and the nae nae
Whip and the nae nae #
# Floss, floss #
# I don't need a dentist
I floss #
# Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot #
Stop.
This isn't good enough.
I really need to step
it up a notch here
if I'm gonna baptise
you guys, okay?
I can't keep doing one talent at a time.
We'll be here forever.
So to finish everything off
and to make sure you
are fully baptised,
I'm going to do
all of my talents,
the remaining
talents I need to do,
at one time.
My acting, my singing,
and my magicianry.
Are you ready for this?
Once I do this,
you will all
officially be baptised,
and you will be part of the Holy
Church of the Virgin Miranda.
So get ready to have
your minds exploded.
But first, I need the help
of my assistant, Patrick.
Welcome him to the stage.
It's all right.
As far as I know, I still
don't have the rights to you,
so just, um, close your eyes
when you're looking at him,
but keep them open when
you're looking at me so that
it's like he's not here.
So try that.
All right. So I'm about to
do an incredible magic trick.
This is going to go around
my neck and lock shut.
Patrick is going to take
this very sharp sword.
He's gonna stick it
through my neck, like so,
whilst I am singing,
and it will not affect
my vocal chords at all.
Not only that,
I'm gonna be doing the best acting
you've ever seen in your life
because the best type
of music to act to
and to sing to at the same time
is opera music.
So I'm gonna be singing a
famous opera song in Italian.
So get ready to have your
minds freaking blown.
Hit it!
Stick it in me whenever
you want, Patrick.
# O mio babbino caro #
# Mi piace bello #
# Bello #
# A pizza with meatballs and pepperoni
And a sausage #
# Yo quiero Taco Bell #
# Mi struggo #
# E mi tormento #
# O Dio #
# Vorrei #
# Morir #
Aah!
Thank you, guys!
You've been a great audience.
You're all baptised.
Have a great night.
'Why are you a YouTuber?
I'm not a hater. I just hate your vids.
And your voice.'
'You look uglier than my ass.
No ofoinse.'
'Does she have cancer?
'Cause I don't want to make
fun of her if she does.
She's so effing annoying.'
'Your cloths are so ugly.'
Maybe you need to
go to a model class.
Your cloths look like pyjamas.
'You don't know
what you're wearing.
You look good to you.
You look bad to me.'
# 'Roses are red, violets are blue #'
# Pornhub is down
Colleen Ballinger will do' #
# 'Her face is a rip off, so sad' #
# 'Nice fonking forehead' #
# 'Butt...' #
# '...Head' #
# 'Totally stupid' #
# 'I hatte you with a passion
Thumbs up' #
# 'Her face scarets me
She neds more make-up' #
# 'She has a uniboob' #
# 'I'm pretty sure
Her vagina smells like cat food' #
That one's accurate.
# You might think that I'm hurt
Or I'm feeling abused #
# But I'm not, I'm getting paid
From your comments and views #
# So keep the comments coming
But here's some help #
# Before you go insulting people
Maybe learn how to spell #
# Dum-da-dum #
# You sound so dumb, dumb, dumb #
# You sound so dumb #
'What the duck is wrong with her face?
Duck, duck, duck, duck!'
'There are eight-year-olds...
watching this.'
'She looks fat but still pretty.'
# 'I think she might be a dude' #
# 'You remind me of a raisin #
# 'Cause you have wrinkles
And everyone hates you' #
# 'You look like Maranda'
'You look like Mirada' #
# 'Are you Merinda?'
'Are you Amanda?' #
# 'Are you Mirrrinda?'
'Are you Marinade Sings? No ofens' #
You know, I'm not a marinade,
so none taken.